[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.59,0:04:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.59,0:04:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.59,0:04:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十五集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.62,0:00:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.17,0:00:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, happy Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.37,0:00:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今晚去弗里特利餐馆咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Fratelli's tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.65,0:00:19.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了  奶油糕饼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, cannoli canoe.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.79,0:00:22.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢  很合身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like it. Nice fit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.06,0:00:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面料时髦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Swanky material.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.71,0:00:26.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  你看起来又壮又性感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you look so strong and sexy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.94,0:00:30.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个奥运会摔跤健将  同时又是个款爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like an Olympic wrestler, but with money.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.40,0:00:33.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-到你的了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Your turn. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.19,0:00:35.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节是我最喜欢的美国节日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is my favorite day in America.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.11,0:00:36.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节快乐  美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy Valentine's Day, gorgeous.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.95,0:00:39.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're huge!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.70,0:00:42.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天啊  -是啊  肯定好看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God. - Yeah, those will work.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.54,0:00:45.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真漂亮  -你今晚戴着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Beautiful. - You can wear 'em tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.12,0:00:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备了惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.04,0:00:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你终于要带我去跳莎莎舞吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't tell me you're finally taking me salsa dancing!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.22,0:00:55.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫·布伦纳是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And who's David Brenner?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.73,0:00:57.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斯维加斯的传奇人物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Only a Vegas legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.18,0:01:00.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是魔术师吗  我可喜欢魔术师了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is he a magician? 'Cause I love magicians.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.18,0:01:01.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个喜剧大师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a comedian.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.36,0:01:04.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜剧大师  可今天是情人节啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A comedian? It's Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:07.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是去跳莎莎舞呢  别去看喜剧嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought we were going salsa dancing, not to watch a comedian.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会爱死他的  相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna love him. Trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.15,0:01:10.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙可逗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The guy's hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.59,0:01:12.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  说一个他的段子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, tell me one of his jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.65,0:01:14.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可不说段子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He doesn't do jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:15.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那他有小木槌吗  -没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Does he have a mallet? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.92,0:01:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他怎么打头逗笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So then how does he get hit in the head?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.12,0:01:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不需要打头逗笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He doesn't get hit in the head.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.79,0:01:22.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他观察在场的观众们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He- He makes observations.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.98,0:01:24.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后用幽默的方式说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He tells the truth in a funny way.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.62,0:01:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  他上过无数次《鲁豫有约》了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. He's been on Johnny Carson a hundred times.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.86,0:01:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁豫又是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who the hell is Johnny Carson?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.05,0:01:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爷啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, for God's sake.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.64,0:01:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和歌洛莉亚不是一辈人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria and I are from different generations.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.51,0:01:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我很难跟她交流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I won't lie- It isn't always easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.44,0:01:35.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个星期  她还以为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, last week she thought
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.46,0:01:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"西蒙和加韦科"组合是我的律师呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Simon and Garfunkel were my lawyers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.68,0:01:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.31,0:01:40.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.88,0:01:41.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没听懂笑点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.76,0:01:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是因为我没小木槌逗你笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe that's because there's no mallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.10,0:01:47.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我现在就想用木槌捶死你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I wish I had a mallet right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.35,0:01:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...打算待在加州北部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}...was to stay in Northern California.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.36,0:01:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没告诉她  需要多长时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you indicate to her how long that you were gonna take?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-情人节快乐  -情人节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy Valentine's Day. - Happy Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.43,0:01:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-情人节快乐  爹地  -情人节快乐  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy Valentine's Day, Daddy. - Happy Valentine's Day, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.14,0:02:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现什么特别的了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Notice anything different?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.87,0:02:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真有爱  -有爱而已吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, that is cute. - Cute?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.66,0:02:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们花了很长时间打扮呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We spent a lot of time on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.79,0:02:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没看出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't see how.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.41,0:02:09.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是拆了一条羽毛围巾而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just cut up one of your boas.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.38,0:02:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我们重新改造了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh- Actually, no. We repurposed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走的是名人混搭风\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was sort of a Bob Mackie meets Martha Stewart project.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.55,0:02:16.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们还以为能给你个惊喜呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Well, we just thought it would be a nice surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.80,0:02:18.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实没什么好惊喜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's hardly a surprise. I mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.31,0:02:20.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逢年过节你都会把她打扮一番\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you dress her up for every holiday.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.09,0:02:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨晚给她洗澡时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was giving her a bath last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.68,0:02:23.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现马丁·路德·金的妆还在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I still saw traces of Martin Luther King behind her ear.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.89,0:02:25.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你不喜欢  我们懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Not in the spirit. We get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.26,0:02:26.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm-I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.64,0:02:28.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你弄得很好看  只是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It's adorable. I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.64,0:02:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很担心我的结案陈词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm really nervous about my closing argument.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.65,0:02:31.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都练了好几个星期了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you've been rehearsing for weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.34,0:02:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会发挥出色的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.90,0:02:33.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿如此吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's hope so.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.66,0:02:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我在想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, and I was wondering-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:36.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你一整天都要在法院里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}since you're gonna be in court all day-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.18,0:02:37.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吃巧克力就先吃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can open the chocolates.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.20,0:02:40.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Score.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.45,0:02:44.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.62,0:02:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲太太  情人节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy Valentine's Day, Mrs. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.58,0:02:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  谢谢啊  你真贴心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Dylan, thank you. That is so sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.88,0:02:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是所有老女人都像你这样有气质就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, all women should look as tasty as you when they're old.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.42,0:02:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话听着怪怪的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Huh. Conflicted.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.17,0:02:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  宝贝儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.72,0:03:00.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份礼物代表了我对你的钟情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Take this sweet gift as a token of my affection,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.89,0:03:02.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你的爱慕和无尽的爱意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my unending love and admiration-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.89,0:03:04.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  真大啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Yay, it's big!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.27,0:03:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.27,0:03:11.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱死了  这是我见过最漂亮的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love it. It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.06,0:03:13.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得用紫外灯照着看看[精液斑斑]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, you gotta put a black light on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.04,0:03:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会美得让你犯晕呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It'll blow your mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.86,0:03:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  原来你还会画画啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow! Dylan, I didn't know you could paint.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.82,0:03:19.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  我只是照了张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I didn't. I just took a photo
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.71,0:03:20.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后用软件处理了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I put it through this program
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.83,0:03:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把它变成画了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that turns it into a painting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.49,0:03:25.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们还真的做过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you two actually did...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.95,0:03:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那个  -嗯嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- that. - Uh-huh.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.08,0:03:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.10,0:03:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把它挂在我床头吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go put this over my bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.46,0:03:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not- No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.21,0:03:34.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西不能进你闺房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't need to be in the bedroom at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.29,0:03:36.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你保管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.30,0:03:39.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他比我浪漫吗  迪迪仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did he trump me? D-Money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.55,0:03:42.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说呢  他把一张照片做成了一幅画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You tell me. He made a painting out of a photograph one time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.80,0:03:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我只是送一张贺卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have hand-picked a card,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.47,0:03:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷在浴室的镜子上画一颗心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}drawn a heart in the steam on the medicine cabinet,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.81,0:03:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后带克莱尔去弗里特利餐厅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and taken Claire to Fratelli's,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.89,0:03:51.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吃意大利家常菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a family-style Italian restaurant,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.50,0:03:54.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,17年来一成不变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for 17 years in a row.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.15,0:03:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问  他比我浪漫多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, he got me. He got me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.79,0:04:09.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  宝贝  -待会儿见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye, honey. - See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.00,0:04:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.85,0:04:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你这是闹哪出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, what is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.96,0:04:17.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今晚也不是非要去弗里特利餐厅啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, we don't have to go to Fratelli's tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.50,0:04:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  那你有什么好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, what do you have in mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.88,0:04:25.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嘛  觉得你可以去酒店开房爽一晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I thought you might enjoy a night at a hotel.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.22,0:04:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  不过你在家带孩子行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would, but would you and the kids be okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.85,0:04:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也和你去啊  -好的  我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I meant together. - Yes, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.23,0:04:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然懂  明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. I know. I know. I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.44,0:04:36.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  你意下如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.53,0:04:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你今晚就别想睡了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you're not getting any sleep tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.40,0:04:43.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你今天上班时好好歇着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so you might want to take a nap at work today.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.80,0:04:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一向如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I always do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.20,0:04:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil? Sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.70,0:04:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我们要玩点儿情色的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As long as we're talking about being a little bit naughty,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.52,0:05:00.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得来点儿角色扮演怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what would you say to a little role-playing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.69,0:05:03.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-角色扮演啊  -嗯嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Role-play? - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.26,0:05:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm in.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.17,0:05:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去安排孩子们今晚住别人家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll set up sleepovers for the kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.80,0:05:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我下班后来接你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'll swing by after work to pick you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.85,0:05:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  要不你到酒店的酒吧去找我呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. Why don't you meet me in the hotel bar
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.80,0:05:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你能不能在哪儿钓到我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and see if you can pick me up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.90,0:05:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点  小姐  你会唤醒一头沉睡的"雄"狮哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Careful, lady. You're gonna wake up a sexy sleeping giant.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.43,0:05:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我可以扮演雷金纳德·阿普比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perhaps I'll be Reginald Appleby,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.23,0:05:28.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位来参加马球比赛的英国绅士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}an English gentleman in town for a polo match.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.78,0:05:29.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.70,0:05:33.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不  一位来自香港的优雅商人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or...Honorable businessman from Hong Kong.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.89,0:05:35.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说就性趣全无了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kinda wrecking it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.79,0:05:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了的  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not a big deal, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.33,0:05:42.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是个拿皮鞭的驯兽师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just train tigers for a living.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.80,0:05:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太重口味了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Too... No?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.08,0:05:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是玫瑰花瓣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are these rose petals?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.40,0:05:58.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  为了纪念我们的爱情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, to commemorate our love.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.44,0:05:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被迫和解[安定下来]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had to settle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.71,0:06:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈或许会认为你是"被迫"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, your mom might think so,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.94,0:06:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过其他人都觉得我是个贤夫哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but a lot of people think I'm a catch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.09,0:06:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是说那案子  我差点儿就要成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. The case. I- I was this close to nailing it,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.38,0:06:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我的委托人临阵退缩  和解了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then my client gets scared and settles.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.87,0:06:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾  来颗巧克力吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. Maybe you'd like a chocolate.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.70,0:06:15.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是一颗也没偷吃哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Notice that I have not eaten any of the chocolates.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.47,0:06:18.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盒子原本有两层的  你我心里都清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There were two levels. You know it and I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.73,0:06:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太受打击了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is so frustrating.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.98,0:06:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我精心准备了有史以来最强的结案陈词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had one of the greatest closing arguments of all time-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控诉"大政府"如何欺压"小人民"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}all about the big government rolling over the little guy,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.52,0:06:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我还想好了如何推向高潮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I even had this great moment at the end...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.20,0:06:31.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会指着国徽高呼  "可耻啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where I would point to the state seal and I'd say, "Shame!"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.68,0:06:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你洗澡时是在练这个啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's what you were doing in the shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.77,0:06:35.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时还担心呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was a little worried.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.77,0:06:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是曼尼来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, that's Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.79,0:06:39.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应今晚照看他  希望你别介意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said we would watch him tonight. I hope you don't mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.25,0:06:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想到你今天会这么倒霉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't know you were gonna be going through all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.84,0:06:42.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  有个孩子在挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's fine. It might be nice to have him around.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.93,0:06:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他总是能逗我发笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He always make me laugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.25,0:06:46.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.25,0:06:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界又冷酷又无情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The universe is cold and loveless.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.35,0:06:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  情人节过得不好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-oh. Bad Valentine's Day?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.46,0:06:54.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我追寻我的爱人  菲奥娜·冈德森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I went for the gold- Fiona Gunderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.80,0:06:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倾心吐胆地为她写了首诗  放在她桌子上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I poured my heart and soul into a poem, left it on her desk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.89,0:07:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至把纸边烧了一下  让它更好看些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I even burned the edges to make it look fancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.56,0:07:02.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不喜欢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And she didn't like it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.72,0:07:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, she loved it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.89,0:07:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可有个叫德卡斯的小崽子说是他写的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But this kid Durkas told her he wrote it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.10,0:07:08.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  那你为什么不告诉她真相呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Manny, why-why didn't you just tell her the truth?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.69,0:07:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那时已经走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She was already gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.12,0:07:12.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他俩要去我最喜欢的餐厅约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And she's on a date with him at my favorite restaurant,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.57,0:07:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美奶昔餐厅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great Shakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.32,0:07:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you know all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.38,0:07:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在信里邀请她去那儿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I invited her in the poem.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.24,0:07:17.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那诗句之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right after the line of,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.30,0:07:20.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"五大湖水深千尺  不及我爱你之情"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"My love is deeper than the Great Lakes."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.20,0:07:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这简直无法容忍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, well, this is unacceptable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.33,0:07:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, boy. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.55,0:07:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  其实没什么难的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's not that big of a deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.85,0:07:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我们这么干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.55,0:07:27.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去美奶昔餐厅  找张桌子坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna shoot over to Great Shakes, get a table.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.68,0:07:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼去追回他的挚爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny can reclaim the love of his life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.46,0:07:31.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我去弄点好吃的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You and I can get a couple Mudslides.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.22,0:07:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德卡斯也在那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Durkas is gonna be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.37,0:07:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小崽子可壮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've seen the kid do a pull-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.36,0:07:38.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  今天是情人节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Manny, it's Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.84,0:07:40.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不是逃离爱情的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not the day you run away from love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.45,0:07:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是追逐爱情  收获爱情的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the day you track it down, tie it up and take it home.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.47,0:07:44.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我们能成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, if we can pull this off,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.82,0:07:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你的小女朋友就能倚在吧台前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you and your little lady friend will be belly up to a ice cream counter
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.71,0:07:49.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪漫地共享一杯奶昔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}having a milk shake with two straws.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.34,0:07:50.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.07,0:07:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.98,0:07:55.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.15,0:07:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科学家也无法解释这个现象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scientists- They don't know why this is true,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.95,0:07:59.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可确实如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.70,0:08:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大屁股的女人能长寿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Women with big rear ends live longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.74,0:08:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但夸女人屁股大的男人会短命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Man who tell 'em that don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.54,0:08:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们听过这么件事没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you read about this man,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.54,0:08:13.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个91岁的老头在德州抢银行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a 91 -year old bank robber in Texas?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.75,0:08:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走进银行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He goes into a bank-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.46,0:08:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我要干什么来着"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"The hell did I want?"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.72,0:08:23.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们照下了四千张他逃离银行的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They had over 4,000 photos of him escaping from the bank.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.89,0:08:30.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  他很逗  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? He's funny, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.90,0:08:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能坐你旁边吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mind if I join you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.28,0:08:46.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫克里夫  克里夫·比克斯比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm Clive. Clive Bixby.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.24,0:08:50.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了  我叫朱莉安娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I can see that. I'm Juliana.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.54,0:08:53.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里夫  你是来这儿开会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Clive, you in town for a convention,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.17,0:08:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是只是老记不住自己的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or do you just forget your name a lot?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.96,0:08:58.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感小野猫爪子挺锋利嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pretty kitty has nails.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.67,0:09:00.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.18,0:09:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来参加交易会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm in town for a trade show.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.18,0:09:08.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我设计高级电声转换器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I design high-end electroacoustic transducers.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.47,0:09:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow, that is very...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.60,0:09:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}specific.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.10,0:09:16.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是我能让东西叫出声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a fancy way of saying I get things to make noise.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.61,0:09:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what's your story?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.99,0:09:24.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是选美佳丽吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Miss America Pageant in town?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.69,0:09:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟女人搭讪很顺溜啊  克里夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're a pretty smooth talker, Clive.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.99,0:09:30.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全身上下都很"顺溜"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm pretty smooth all over.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.04,0:09:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  本餐厅禁止吸烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sir, there's no smoking in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.04,0:09:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  其实我也不抽烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's fine. I'm not actually a smoker.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.51,0:09:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真像个小童子军  克里夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're quite the Boy Scout, Clive.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.26,0:09:44.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你  今晚你有没兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tell me, would you be interested in
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.58,0:09:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来赢一枚小勋章呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}earning a merit badge tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.47,0:09:50.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会捆绑  会打结吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know anything about tying knots?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.77,0:09:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或许不该找你聊天的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I probably shouldn't be talking to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.81,0:09:57.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是有妇之夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a married man.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:01.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好  我就喜欢有妇之夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just so happen to like married men.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.99,0:10:03.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说你妻子吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tell me about your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.13,0:10:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她非常漂亮  必须的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she's beautiful, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.20,0:10:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  既然她那么漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Well, if she's so very beautiful,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会跟我在一起呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why are you here with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.99,0:10:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她总是很疲惫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because she's always so tired...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.99,0:10:14.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她总是忙着使唤我干活儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she's always making lists of things for me to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.50,0:10:17.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许如果你听她使唤  她就不会这么累了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe if you did them she wouldn't be so tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.05,0:10:20.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她吩咐的事根本做不完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh no. She can make list for days.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.50,0:10:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说回你的性感双唇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But back to your mouth and how sexy it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.97,0:10:25.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  我倒是想说回那些"使唤"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm-mmm. I wanna go back to these alleged lists
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.53,0:10:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你那唠叨的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and your nagging wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.82,0:10:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是在说你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not talking about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.85,0:10:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那个意思  再重来一次好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't mean that. Can we try this again?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.85,0:10:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.52,0:10:40.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那既然你妻子这么漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So if your wife is so beautiful,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:43.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会跟我在一起呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why are you here with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.40,0:10:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.74,0:10:49.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太疼她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I respect her too much...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不忍对她下手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to do to her...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.74,0:10:54.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像对你般地蹂躏她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what I'm going to do to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.83,0:10:56.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  中大奖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, jackpot.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.98,0:11:00.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会儿就回来  克里夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be right back, Clive.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.81,0:11:11.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现她了吗  她在这儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you have eyes on her? Is she here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.06,0:11:14.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两点钟方向  坐在后排桌子的金发女生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two o'clock- blonde at the back table.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.35,0:11:16.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白  发现目标了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yep. I have a visual.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.98,0:11:19.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再用这种军事用语了  完毕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's not talk like that anymore. Over.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.65,0:11:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  就这么干  我要去赢回我的爱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, this is it. I'm off to win the heart of my beloved.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.16,0:11:26.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是件好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, this is nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.33,0:11:28.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没法好好过自己的情人节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, if we can't have our own Valentine's Day,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.57,0:11:30.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮别人过个好节也不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's nice that we can give somebody else one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.29,0:11:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小卡  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, Cam. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.87,0:11:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  忽视了你的精心安排\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sor- I'm sorry I have not been attentive.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.87,0:11:35.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去五个月来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been spending the last five months...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.58,0:11:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呕心沥血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}pouring my core beliefs
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.91,0:11:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写出了自己最棒的讲稿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}into the greatest speech that I will ever write,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.08,0:11:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一切努力却付诸东流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then that moment gets taken away.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.42,0:11:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy. How'd it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.84,0:11:45.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不来  德卡斯在那儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't do it, not while Durkas is there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.69,0:11:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有种天生的自信  我对他又敬又怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He has the natural confidence. I admire it and fear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.88,0:11:51.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会搞定他的  我们得计划一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We will deal with him directly. We need a plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.55,0:11:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢再戏剧化一点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you be more dramatic?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.85,0:12:00.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得计划一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We need a plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.06,0:12:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在俄勒冈州\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In Oregon,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.48,0:12:07.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立法会颁布了一项法令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the state legislature ratified a, uh, bill...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.14,0:12:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规定从今往后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that from now on
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.70,0:12:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人和动物发生性关系将被视为犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it is a crime to have sex in Oregon with a farm animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.19,0:12:17.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俄勒冈的女人是有多丑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How ugly are the women in Oregon?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.99,0:12:21.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  他太逗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's funny, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.39,0:12:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  没说错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. See?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.71,0:12:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看得出来  你肯定不是从俄勒冈来的  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can tell you're not- you're not from Oregon. -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.09,0:12:28.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你美极了  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You are gorgeous. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.21,0:12:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你带你爸爸来看我表演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you for bringing your father to the show.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.72,0:12:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  我是她丈夫   大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. I'm her husband, Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.26,0:12:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没开玩笑吧  -没呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No kidding. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.14,0:12:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他结婚的感觉如何啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's it like to be married to someone
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.64,0:12:38.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙估计和《圣经》一样老了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who was there when the Bible was written?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.10,0:12:43.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们那时候叫什么  就叫《箴言录》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What was it called then? Just "The Testament"?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.60,0:12:47.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  真是有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's, uh- That's- That's good stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.36,0:12:49.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他就想关灯睡觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, now he's trying to turn out the light.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.66,0:12:58.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有电话找您  在那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phone call. Over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.91,0:13:03.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂  -喂  您好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello? - Uh, yes. Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.23,0:13:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是德卡斯先生吗  -是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mr. Durkas? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.00,0:13:06.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是唐·卓立\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is Don Jolly...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.38,0:13:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是"美奶昔"公司的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the Great Shakes corporate office,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.69,0:13:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个好消息告诉您\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I have good news for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.27,0:13:12.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您被抽中参与我们的调查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have been selected to take part in a random survey...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.71,0:13:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且您将获得现金奖励\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you could win cash and prizes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.72,0:13:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您有兴趣参加我们的活动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does that sound like something you'd be interested in?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.85,0:13:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.63,0:13:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我们只是问您几个小问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, just a few simple questions for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.88,0:13:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您能否根据自己的喜好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you please rank your favorite ice creams
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.96,0:13:26.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把美奶昔的冰激凌排一下序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at Great Shakes from least favorite to favorite?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.44,0:13:28.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实也不太熟悉产品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know 'em by heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.18,0:13:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您右手边应该就有一本菜单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There should be a menu right there to your right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.32,0:13:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你右边  好了  开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To your right. Mm-hmm. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.66,0:13:37.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Hi, Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.62,0:13:39.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  菲奥娜  我能坐下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Fiona. Can I join you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.83,0:13:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以吧  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I guess so. -Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.87,0:13:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必担心他会出轨  那是肯定的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you don't have to worry about him cheating. That's for sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.70,0:13:48.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他出轨了  你肯定会发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because if he does, you'll catch him...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.97,0:13:51.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他回家时嘴里肯定有两副假牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when he comes home with two sets of teeth in his mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.67,0:13:53.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.52,0:13:56.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我们说说  他在新婚之夜表现如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So tell me, on the wedding night, what-what did he do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.07,0:13:58.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是不是说想换个舒服的做爱姿势\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did he say he wanted to change into something comfortable
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.04,0:13:59.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就一睡不起了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and go into a coma?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.20,0:14:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想去去洗手间  -别去嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Listen, I gotta use the men's room. - Nuh-uh.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.95,0:14:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须去一趟  马上就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gotta use the men's room. I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.73,0:14:04.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪儿  等会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where you going? Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.16,0:14:06.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是开玩笑的  我就是干这个的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm only joking. That's what I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.81,0:14:08.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我可年轻多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you're way younger than I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.73,0:14:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是看着显老\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just don't look it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.11,0:14:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里夫  我有点儿小东西给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Clive, I have a little something for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.29,0:14:23.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.41,0:14:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.29,0:14:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的胸罩  -我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- My bra. - Oh, my g-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.84,0:14:33.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小内内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.63,0:14:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天  -嗯嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- My God. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.63,0:14:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我们拿着这些上楼去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you say we take this upstairs?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.13,0:14:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这比吃意大利菜好太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is so much better than cheesy garlic bread.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.76,0:14:49.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-巧克力味  -好的  继续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Chocolate. - Uh-huh. Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.22,0:14:51.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-香草味  -我正记着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Vanilla. - I'm taking copious notes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.22,0:14:53.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您继续说  德卡斯先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Keep goin', Mr. Durkas.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.14,0:14:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果诗不是泰德写的  他为什么骗人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, why would Ted say he wrote the poem if he didn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.98,0:14:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为你是校花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe because you're the cutest girl in school,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.98,0:15:00.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你回眸一笑就倾国倾城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you have a laugh that makes science lab seem like recess.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.05,0:15:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你愿不愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you be more or less inclined
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.37,0:15:08.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去"美奶昔"公司做客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to visit a Great Shakes establishment...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.22,0:15:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你事先知道你的愿望都会被满足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if you knew your satisfaction was guaranteed?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.73,0:15:12.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是个傻逼问题  -不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's a dumb question. - Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.10,0:15:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这问题不傻逼  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It is not a dumb question, Mr. -
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.52,0:15:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死  他挂了  -那你不必装那口音了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Tarnation! He hung up. - Then you can drop the accent.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.52,0:15:20.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪尔加多  你在这儿干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Delgado. What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.61,0:15:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在讨论诗歌呢  你想背诵一下你的作品吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Discussing poetry. Maybe you'll like to recite some of yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.38,0:15:25.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不背什么东西呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna recite anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.99,0:15:27.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承认吧  那首诗根本不是你写的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just admit you didn't write the poem.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.08,0:15:29.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what he's talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.66,0:15:31.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧滚蛋  别逼我揍你一顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get out of here before you get your butt kicked.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.50,0:15:33.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要过去一下  -不  我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm going over there. - No, I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.21,0:15:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂  先生  先生  转回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa! Whoa, sir! Sir? Turn around.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.09,0:15:41.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  你无权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sir, you have no right
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.94,0:15:44.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他人的作品据为己有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to claim ownership of another person's work.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.22,0:15:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你算老几\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.29,0:15:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个律师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.28,0:15:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有律师啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have a lawyer?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.64,0:15:50.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谎是一回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It is one thing to lie,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.02,0:15:53.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你竟然接着又欺负这位年轻人  简直不可饶恕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but then to bully this young man- it's unforgivable.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.73,0:15:55.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是当今世界的不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this is what's wrong with the world today.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.73,0:15:57.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大块头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The big guy...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.90,0:15:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自以为能凌驾于小家伙之上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}thinks that he can roll right over the little guy...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.90,0:16:03.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到小家伙说"够了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until the little guy says, "Enough."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.70,0:16:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那正是这位小家伙要做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's what this little guy's doing-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.32,0:16:07.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在此时  此刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}right here, right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.57,0:16:09.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能别再叫我"小家伙"了吗  我还不算矮的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we stop calling me "Little guy"? I'm in the 40th percentile.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.03,0:16:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  看我的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shh. I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.84,0:16:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰德·德卡斯  显然没有写那首诗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ted Durkas clearly did not write that poem.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.83,0:16:18.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我清楚  他心里也清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it. He knows it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.04,0:16:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好问问自己  菲奥娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Deep down in your heart, Fiona-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.58,0:16:24.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定也清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know it too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.64,0:16:31.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可耻啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shame!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.14,0:16:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  随便了  我是偷了他的傻逼诗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine! Whatever. I stole his stupid poem.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.22,0:16:34.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你偷的  -我就说嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You did? - I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认罪吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.00,0:16:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么做  是因为我有此深情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I only did it because I had the feelings,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.48,0:16:41.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不知道如何向你表达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just didn't know how to show 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.52,0:16:45.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  从来没人对我做如此甜蜜的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? That's the sweetest thing anyone's ever done for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.65,0:16:48.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've gotta be kidding me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.49,0:16:51.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走吧  这妞儿是个二逼青年  -绝对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let's get out of here. This chick's crazy. - Seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.20,0:16:53.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没见过你如此霸气啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've never seen you like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.44,0:16:55.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法想象那种感觉有多爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have no idea how good that felt.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.33,0:16:58.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节快乐  律师先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, happy Valentine's Day, counselor.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.46,0:17:01.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发展得真快啊  朱莉安娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is all happening so fast, Juliana.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.09,0:17:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  而且我午夜之前必须赶回家陪老公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, and I have to be home to my husband by midnight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.13,0:17:06.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  纠结的剧情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, a twist.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.63,0:17:11.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  菲尔  我的外套卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil! Phil, my coat is stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.30,0:17:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔是谁  -不  别闹了  认真点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who's Phil? - No, not now! Seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.06,0:17:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的外套卡住了  -宝贝  快把外套脱掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- My coat is stuck. - Oh, oh. Honey, take off your coat!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.35,0:17:17.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开什么玩笑啊  快拔  -我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you kidding me? Pull it. - Oh, my goodness.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.73,0:17:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拔  用力  用力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pull it. Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.10,0:17:22.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  这回完了  这回完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, boy. Not good. Not good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.11,0:17:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  好了  好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.78,0:17:28.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快上来吧  就当是爬楼梯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on up. Treat 'em like they're regular stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.82,0:17:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事了  -快过去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's okay. - Come on through.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.57,0:17:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节快乐  您真美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy Valentine's Day. You look lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.12,0:17:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-您也美  我没别的意思  -我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So do you. Not in a weird way. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.29,0:17:36.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  嗨  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are you? Hi. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.95,0:17:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-情人节快乐  -让我来弄弄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy Valentine's- - Let me just get in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.48,0:17:39.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来弄弄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me get in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.25,0:17:40.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay? - Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.54,0:17:42.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  汤姆  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Tom. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.21,0:17:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How are you? Honey
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.09,0:17:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  还记得我同事汤姆·麦克森吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, you remember Tom Mickleson from the office
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.48,0:17:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有他妻子  苏珊  -记得  你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and his wife, Susan. - I do. Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.82,0:17:49.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的外套卡住了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is your coat stuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.68,0:17:53.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  卡得死死的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It is. It really is. It's in there pretty darn good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.35,0:17:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何不脱下来呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you take it off?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.63,0:17:57.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...觉得很冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I'm freezing cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.68,0:17:59.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  让我试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At least let me give it a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.27,0:18:01.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不必了吧  -没事没事  看我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, I don't think... - No, no, no. I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.98,0:18:03.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-邓菲先生  夫人  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mr. And Mrs. Dunphy? - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-巴拉班校长  -你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Principal Balaban. - Hey, how are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.84,0:18:08.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里夫·比克斯比是谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's Clive Bixby?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.80,0:18:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个推销扩音器的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, uh, he makes speakers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.24,0:18:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是来参加交易会的  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's actually in town for a trade show. - Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.70,0:18:16.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天  你被卡住了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My, are you stuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.14,0:18:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  有点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I am. A little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.00,0:18:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何不把外套脱了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you take off that coat?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.02,0:18:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怕冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I'm chilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.33,0:18:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是卡死在这儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really jammed in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.33,0:18:24.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让我过去试试  我帮你  -不必了  我们没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let me in there. I'll get you. - No, I think we're okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:27.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲太太\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mrs. Dunphy?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.13,0:18:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.34,0:18:32.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  这位是卢克的数学老师  帕斯沃小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi! Luke's math teacher, Ms. Passwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.43,0:18:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"拍死我"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Passwater."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.76,0:18:38.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老杰  别在意他说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, Jay, papi, don't pay attention to what he's saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.68,0:18:39.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's just being funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.81,0:18:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他说的是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because he points out the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.49,0:18:44.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观众们笑是因为他们也觉得确实如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those people were laughing because they saw it too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.13,0:18:46.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干嘛在意他们怎么想  -我不在意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What do you care what they think? - I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.04,0:18:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在意你怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I care what you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.78,0:18:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  你是我的爱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you. You're my valentine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.53,0:18:51.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是现在而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.44,0:18:52.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我80岁了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But what about when I'm 80
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.83,0:18:54.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐在轮椅上  插着氧气管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm in a wheelchair, on oxygen?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.88,0:18:56.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还会要我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You still gonna want me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.46,0:18:57.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我如此肤浅吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think I'm so shallow
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.43,0:18:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老了我就会抛弃你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'm gonna leave you when you're old?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.48,0:19:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我胖了100磅  你会抛弃我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if I gain a hundred pounds? You gonna leave me then?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.94,0:19:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不会  -你怎么犹豫了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - What's with the pause?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.18,0:19:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这假设不公平啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's not exactly fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.80,0:19:10.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我变老是必然的  可你不一定会变胖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I have to get old. You don't have to get fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.33,0:19:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我想变胖  就能变胖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I want to get fat, I get fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.82,0:19:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好  如果你胖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fine. And if you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.93,0:19:14.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会守着你  不信你试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be there. You'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.23,0:19:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你看我怎么变胖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, watch me. Watch me, how I get fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.73,0:19:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能变胖的  -那我也会守着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can get fat. - And I'll be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.18,0:19:23.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.43,0:19:26.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还想回去看戏吗  -不去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You wanna go back in? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.44,0:19:27.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个更好的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a better idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.70,0:19:31.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去跳莎莎舞吧  那家伙也不怎么有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go salsa dancing. This guy's not that funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.75,0:19:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.33,0:19:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  好了  我打给维修部了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're good! We're good! I talked to Maintenance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.63,0:19:39.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们  他们马上就来  大家忙去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're- They're- They're coming, so go on ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.86,0:19:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  回头见吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you guys. See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.34,0:19:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校里见  见到你们真开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you in school. Good to see you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.47,0:19:45.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维修部的人会解决的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maintenance is gonna take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.22,0:19:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得救了  -好吧  好吧  他们要多久才到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So we're fine. - Okay. Okay, how long till they get here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.39,0:19:50.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是骗他们的  没人来救我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was faking it. No one's coming for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.47,0:19:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去找人啊  快点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then, go and get them! Hurry!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.82,0:19:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻是我这辈子最糗的时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was the most embarrassing moment of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.35,0:19:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire! Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.40,0:20:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stand by.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  腰带卡住了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, did you get your belt stuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.62,0:20:05.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.08,0:20:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那把外套脱了呗  我帮你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take your coat off. Here, let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.90,0:20:08.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别别  老爸  我没事  -得了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, no, Dad. Dad, I'm fine. - Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.82,0:20:10.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你里面没穿衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you, naked under there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.95,0:20:14.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我靠  -没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Aw, geez. - It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.91,0:20:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让我来吧  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got this. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.37,0:20:19.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-克莱尔  照我说的办  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Claire, follow my lead. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.54,0:20:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.63,0:20:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇塞  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wow. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.47,0:20:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -我以前也有同样的经历\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thank you. - It has happened to me before.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.03,0:20:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真有一手啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was impressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.35,0:20:39.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里夫  下次玩点正常的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take it down a notch, Clive.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.73,0:20:42.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吧  -嗯  挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You okay? - Yeah. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.06,0:20:44.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. - I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.40,0:20:46.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-情人节快乐  -情人节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy Valentine's Day. - Happy Valentine's Day.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.23,0:20:47.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  -再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Chao. - Okay. See ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.69,0:20:48.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  晚安\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye. Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.99,0:20:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀妈呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. That's-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.78,0:20:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  再见吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry. See you, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.91,0:20:58.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.58,0:21:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  我就是想告诉你  你昨晚真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, I just wanted to tell you how great you were last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.54,0:21:05.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  -对不起  我把油弄得到处都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, Phil... - Sorry I got the, uh- the oil everywhere, but, hey"
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.59,0:21:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  -幸好不是自家的床单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, sweetie. - They're not our sheets, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.76,0:21:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  还记得卖车的人怎么说的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey- Honey, remember when the salesman told us...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.92,0:21:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说"丰田塞纳是适合全家人的车"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that the Sienna was built with the whole family in mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.26,0:21:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家人都听见你刚刚说的话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Well, the whole family just heard that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.55,0:21:18.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,囧  看来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh- Uh- Guess-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.18,0:21:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来蓝牙对讲挺好用的嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess the Bluetooth works.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.27,0:21:23.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯嗯  -你们用油干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mmm. - Why did you have oil?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.44,0:21:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为啊  小弟  我们在做炸薯条啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because, buddy, we were making French fries.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.77,0:21:28.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你卧室里炸啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In your room?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.36,0:21:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不你们播张DVD看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you guys just pop in a DVD?

