[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.09,0:03:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.09,0:03:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.09,0:03:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第七集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.67,0:00:09.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒啦  太厉害啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo! Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.36,0:00:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.23,0:00:20.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.73,0:00:24.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厉害了  曼尼  厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo, Manny! Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.44,0:00:26.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我听说曼尼想学击剑时  我心想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, when I heard Manny wanted to fence, I was, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.65,0:00:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨手笨脚的孩子  配上致命的利器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Sure. Uncoordinated kid, lethal weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.69,0:00:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能有比这还糟的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How can this go wrong?"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.96,0:00:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你的看法又如何呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think now?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.18,0:00:39.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的小佐罗真让我骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm proud of our little Zorro.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.61,0:00:42.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说我也教过他几招  但他的确有天赋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean I worked with him a little, but the kid's got skills.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.41,0:00:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是与生俱来的  他爹就是个剑术大师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's in his blood. His father was a master swordsman.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.55,0:00:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堪称剑道里的艺术家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was an artist with his sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.33,0:00:51.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他英姿焕发  挥剑抬足的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, the way he throws the sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.03,0:00:52.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是传奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, he was legendary.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.79,0:00:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我在享受和你儿子的父子时刻吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know this nice moment I'm having with your son?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.86,0:00:57.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有点破坏气氛了  -对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're kind of wrecking it. - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.01,0:01:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道剑术起源于12世纪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you know that fencing goes back to the 12th century?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.73,0:01:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道什么比击剑还呆吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what's even nerdier than fencing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.05,0:01:06.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解它的起源\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Knowing when it began.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.91,0:01:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不认为你是呆子  艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think you're a nerd, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.49,0:01:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴吧  呆子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up, dork.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.02,0:01:12.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  乖儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. That's my boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.36,0:01:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不如用起重机帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would this be easier...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.31,0:01:17.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这玩意吊起来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if we suspended you from a crane?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.46,0:01:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家庭录像谁都会拍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Any monkey can shoot a home movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.16,0:01:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只有我能拍出家庭电影的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I pride myself on shooting home films.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.74,0:01:25.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是小卡  你做事总是做得太过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, Cameron, you always just take things a little too far.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.24,0:01:25.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.96,0:01:27.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你侄子的周岁生日  -说那事儿不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, your nephew's first birthday. - That's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.70,0:01:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带了台鼓风机去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You brought a wind machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.34,0:01:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老实说  -卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- To be fair, - Cameron,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.32,0:01:32.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我本来是要  -那可是鼓风机呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- my vision was-  - you brought a wind machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会在婴儿床上装轮子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who puts wheels on cribs?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.75,0:01:44.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay! Sorry. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.47,0:01:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.96,0:01:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不不  我手机没电了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, no, no, no! My phone died.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.04,0:01:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  大概是你手机电池没静电了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No biggie. Your battery probably just statically defracticated.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.84,0:01:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.50,0:01:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给它充点静电就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It means you can recharge it with static electricity.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.28,0:01:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你头发上蹭蹭就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just rub it on your hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.21,0:02:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.56,0:02:04.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前去朋友家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I used to go to the houses of my friends,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.28,0:02:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见他们小孩得的奖杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd see their kids' trophies,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.59,0:02:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里都特别不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it used to bug me, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.79,0:02:09.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我家从来没得过奖杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because there was never a trophy in my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.93,0:02:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到她的出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not until this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.24,0:02:15.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手劲真大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's a good grip.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.70,0:02:20.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我换换位置吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we switch seats?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.21,0:02:22.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  别人在看你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, people are staring.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.97,0:02:24.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道父母不该在意这些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know you're not supposed to care,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.77,0:02:26.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是家里有个有特长的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's kind of cool to have a kid in your house
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.61,0:02:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉挺不错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who's the best at something.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:28.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂我的意思吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what I mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.74,0:02:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我家小孩都很棒  -他们是最棒的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, our kids are great. - They're the greatest.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.62,0:02:37.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们真幸运  -没错  不过呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gosh, we're blessed. - We are. But, um,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.47,0:02:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说他们有什么特长吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are they the best at something?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.02,0:02:41.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd have to think about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.46,0:02:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要艾丽克斯想做的  她都能做到最好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Alex is great at every single thing she tries,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.10,0:02:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以她总会找到自己的特长  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- so, you know, she'll find her specialty. - She will.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.69,0:02:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于海莉嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Haley is-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.57,0:02:55.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉长得多漂亮啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley is so pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.74,0:02:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-美若天仙  我女儿美若天仙  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gorgeous, gorgeous girl. - Oh, gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.95,0:03:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她可以嫁个有特长的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So she can meet someone who's the best at something.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.85,0:03:01.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.77,0:03:04.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  还剩下卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then, uh, I guess that leaves Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.88,0:03:10.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是有点输在起跑线上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We dropped the ball a little bit on that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.19,0:03:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  有那么一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.34,0:03:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.61,0:03:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请为我们的胜利者曼尼·迪尔加多鼓掌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How about a nice round of applause for our winner, Manny Delgado.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.74,0:03:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼晋级了总冠军争夺赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny now moves on to the championship,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.61,0:03:36.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将对阵卡罗琳·马可\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where he'll be competing against Caroline Markum.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.87,0:03:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在四点半准时到场观看比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll see you all back here at 4:30.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.08,0:03:41.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了  -儿子你真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. - Bravo.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.27,0:03:48.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说的和她一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What she said.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.07,0:03:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸比曼尼还激动啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. This means more to Dad than it does to Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.05,0:03:54.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这可是他成为冠军之父的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, it's his chance to be father of a champion.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.11,0:03:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  以前也有过机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, second chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.93,0:03:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道那次是怎么错过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We all know how the first time went.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.48,0:03:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说错什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did I say something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.60,0:04:03.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  才没呢  我只是太为曼尼高兴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. I'm- I'm very happy for Manny.That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.49,0:04:06.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事都能扯到她身上  神啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything's always about Claire. Geez.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.38,0:04:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们过来支持我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanna thank you guys for coming by and supporting the kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.06,0:04:10.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是最棒的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys are the best!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.92,0:04:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么受伤的总是我  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why, Claire?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.07,0:04:16.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.49,0:04:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么去了那么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That took a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.73,0:04:22.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她20分钟前就睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's been asleep for 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.37,0:04:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不弄醒她  我不得不悄悄溜走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It just took me some time to sneak out without waking her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.50,0:04:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你第一次在这里过夜那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kind of like the first time you slept over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.50,0:04:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那是要溜出去开会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had a meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.34,0:04:32.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们来谈谈让你心烦意乱的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Let's talk about why you got your panties in a bunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.42,0:04:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你姐之间到底怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up with you and your sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.47,0:04:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么都没有  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing is up. - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.13,0:04:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是和滑冰那事有关呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or could this have something to do with... ice skating?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔和克莱尔小时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When Mitchell and Claire were kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.68,0:04:45.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人想听这个故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is interesting to no one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.98,0:04:47.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  让我讲完  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse, please. Let me finish. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.10,0:04:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在米奇尔10岁时  -11岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- When Mitchell was 10 - Eleven.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.11,0:04:51.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔13岁时  他们是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Claire was 13, they
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.09,0:04:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一对实力雄厚的冰舞小将  -是花样滑冰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- were competitive ice dancers. - Figure skaters!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.11,0:04:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  还是换我来说吧  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, for God's sakes, I'll tell the story. Yes,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.03,0:04:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我姐和我真心是一对完美搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my sister and I were actually a very good team.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.03,0:04:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的组合叫"柔情似火"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were called "Fire and Nice."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.03,0:05:04.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的红发象征火焰  克莱尔代表柔情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was Fire, because of the red hair, and Claire was Nice,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.41,0:05:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是为了讽刺她一点不温柔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because it was ironic and she wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.83,0:05:08.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔到现在还耿耿于怀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Mitchell is still upset
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.19,0:05:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为克莱尔在某场比赛前临阵脱逃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because Claire quit the team right before some meet.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.21,0:05:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么某场  那是13岁以下地区总决赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Some meet." The 13-and-under regional championships.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:16.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我人生黄砖路尽头辉煌的翡翠城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just the Emerald City at the end of my yellow brick road.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[《绿野仙踪》典故]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.39,0:05:18.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇  你成功了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wow. You did it. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.80,0:05:21.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功地把滑冰描述得更基情了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You made figure skating sound even gayer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.01,0:05:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你老爸那么为曼尼骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, seeing your dad so proud of Manny...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.72,0:05:26.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都没有不爽吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}didn't stir up any resentment?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.89,0:05:29.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才没有  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mm-mmm. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.69,0:05:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你总是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fine. You always do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.78,0:05:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断压抑自己的情感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Instead of letting your feelings out, you bury them,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.96,0:05:35.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到某一刻再伤人地爆发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then they bubble up later in hurtful ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.11,0:05:38.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  你说对了 听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know what? Yes. All right, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.06,0:05:40.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或许仍有些不满\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I might still be holding a little resentment,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.91,0:05:43.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可那很丢人  又显得心胸狭隘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but that's... embarrassing and petty
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.88,0:05:46.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再那样也不合适了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it's not a good color on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.29,0:05:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你不适合黄颜色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's kind of like you and yellow.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.04,0:05:50.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是很喜欢我穿黄色衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You love me in my yellow shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.08,0:05:52.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黄色让你看起来像个太阳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It makes you look like the sun.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.13,0:05:54.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆发了  伤人地爆发了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bubbling. Hurtful bubbling.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.38,0:05:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你知道我那早为何溜走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now you know why I left early that morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.05,0:06:00.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你不是开会  小卡  我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew you didn't have a meeting, Cam. I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.05,0:06:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这手机肯定出了什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There must be something wrong with this phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.06,0:06:07.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都在头上蹭一个钟头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've rubbed it on my head for, like, an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.06,0:06:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.48,0:06:14.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你真是个怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you're such a geek.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.19,0:06:16.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我没把头皮磨秃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At least I didn't give myself a bald spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.69,0:06:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.05,0:06:19.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  别这么刻薄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, don't be mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.26,0:06:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  你也别那么容易掉入陷阱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, stop making yourself such an easy target.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.24,0:06:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  老弟  就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This feels right, buddy. I'm telling you, this feels right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.53,0:06:26.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们要去哪  -去创造天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What are you guys doing? - Pursuing excellence.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.74,0:06:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们帮卢克列了个成功潜力表\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We make a list of areas the boy might excel at
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.34,0:06:31.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后选择了棒球  -不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and... baseball. - Love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.00,0:06:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  书上说一万小时的训练就能练成天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. I read it only takes 10,000 hours to achieve excellence.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.13,0:06:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经练了  你大概练多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've already got, what, how many hours playing ball?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.90,0:06:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我练一个赛季了  得有六千小时吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I played, like, one season, so, like, 6,000 hours?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.30,0:06:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得你们没选数学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. I can see why you ruled out math.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.89,0:06:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然想要卢克成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, of course I want Luke to be successful.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.89,0:06:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不喜欢揠苗助长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I don't think that a parent can just force that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.98,0:06:54.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你只要有信心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you just have to have
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.33,0:06:57.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们会发现自己的闪光点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}faith that the kid's gonna find his own way.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.98,0:07:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  能成为我儿子  已经够卢克骄傲了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Besides, Luke already is the best at something- being my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.28,0:07:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话说出口来就弱掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It sounded a lot less lame in my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.91,0:07:09.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我预感这将会进展顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have got a good feeling about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定是打棒球的料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is gonna be your sport.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.00,0:07:14.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年你说过我是打篮球的料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Last year, you said basketball was my sport.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.71,0:07:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我说过很多让我追悔莫及的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I've said a lot of things I wish I could take back but I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.00,0:07:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What I can do...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.01,0:07:25.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有当一个能够帮助你登上顶峰的爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is be the dad you need me to be to help you become masterful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.18,0:07:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想登峰造极吗  -大概吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You wanna be masterful? - I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.47,0:07:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好孩子  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's my killer! Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.72,0:07:32.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一万小时的训练计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our journey of 10,000 hours...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.89,0:07:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就从简单的投球开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}begins with a single pitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.23,0:07:38.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看好你哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I believe in my boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.36,0:07:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放弃你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I ain't gonna quit you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.40,0:07:42.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投一个过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's burn one in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.40,0:07:44.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  你开了一个好头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's good. That's a good start.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.25,0:07:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你休息一下  我去捡球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you rest that cannon while I run this down, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.04,0:07:53.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量往这个方向投球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, let's keep all the batters right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.54,0:07:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该把护裆穿上  真该把护裆穿上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, should've- should've worn my cup. Should've worn my cup.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.25,0:07:59.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全垒打[打进家里]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Home run!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.13,0:08:01.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球肯定在这里的某处  老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This one's really in here, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.14,0:08:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  第一个小时真是非常非常不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Very, very, very, very good first hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.72,0:08:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手套给我  我给它上点油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Toss me your glove. I'll put some oil on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.70,0:08:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Everything okay? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.57,0:08:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚告诉奶奶  曼尼今天有多厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was telling my grandmother how great was Manny today.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.10,0:08:32.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是在吵架啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So that wasn't angry talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.48,0:08:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  傻瓜  我聊得开心呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, silly. That was happy talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.58,0:08:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始了解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm beginning to understand
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.63,0:08:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥你们南美那么多暴力冲突了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why there's so much conflict on your continent.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.52,0:08:39.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.84,0:08:43.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.91,0:08:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(172,124)\fn方正小标宋简体\fs22}曼尼倍儿棒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.30,0:08:46.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰喜欢为特殊时刻制作纪念衫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay loves to make T-shirts for special occasions.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.93,0:08:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  宝贝  给他们瞧瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, baby. Show them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.93,0:08:51.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几年前  我孙女海莉跑五千米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A few years back, my granddaughter Haley ran a 5K,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.83,0:08:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我做了一些这样的衬衫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I had a few of these made up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.83,0:08:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(136,139)\fn方正小标宋简体\fs22}海 莉 彗 星
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.68,0:08:55.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好玩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.38,0:09:00.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴你那么为曼尼骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love it when you're so proud of Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.50,0:09:01.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实  老实说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I'm not gonna lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.15,0:09:03.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见他把那些小孩打得落花流水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seeing him out there slicing those kids to pieces,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.11,0:09:04.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, it gets to ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.72,0:09:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多谢你  宝贝  -很抱歉打断你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gracias, mi amor. - I'm sorry to interrupt.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.61,0:09:11.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事  -小冠军  给你点小东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's okay, papi. - Hey, champ! I got a little something for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.12,0:09:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也正要给你个东西  拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I have something for you. Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.79,0:09:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再需要它了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will not be needing it anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.96,0:09:21.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那决赛怎么办  -我要退役了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But the finals? - I am retired.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.77,0:09:27.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  等下  等下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.24,0:09:30.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能退役啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't retire.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.74,0:09:32.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这不好玩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just not fun anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.87,0:09:34.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是你一时冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's probably just butterflies.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.70,0:09:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你没问题的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. You're gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.54,0:09:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  如果他不想比  那是他的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, if he doesn't want to, it's his decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.41,0:09:41.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定个鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, the hell it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.33,0:09:43.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得太紧张  就别逼他做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He shouldn't be doing anything that makes him nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.67,0:09:45.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  我支持你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Papi, I support you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.35,0:09:48.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是紧张  我只是不想和一个女孩对决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not nervous. I just don't want to fight a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.62,0:09:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.91,0:09:52.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢过一个女人会是我荣誉册上的污点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Defeating a woman will be a mark on my honor.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.06,0:09:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.70,0:09:55.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们男人总是比我们女人厉害吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because men are always so superior to woman?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.82,0:10:00.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你厉害得连话都说不全了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So superior that you cannot even finish your sentence?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.97,0:10:02.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.36,0:10:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你常称自己为女人的贴心小情人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you always call yourself the lover of women,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.71,0:10:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不和那女孩比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but if you don't compete with this girl,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:13.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明你根本不尊重我们女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're showing me and all the woman that you don't respect us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.49,0:10:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.78,0:10:18.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  拿回你的剑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, so, take back your sword...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.01,0:10:21.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-像个公牛一样打败她  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and go fight this girl like a bull. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.39,0:10:23.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说大声点  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can't hear you! - Okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.09,0:10:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再大声点  -那真是我最大嗓门了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can't hear you! - That's really as loud as I can go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.63,0:10:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何成为一名好的推销员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What does it take to make a great salesman?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.43,0:10:31.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实没什么窍门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's no big secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.34,0:10:34.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要遵从销售的基本法则  "一定要成交"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just follow the ABC's of salesmanship: Always Be Closing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.01,0:10:35.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不要忘记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't ever forget
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.99,0:10:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的房屋卖点就藏在你身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}great home ideas just keep lurking, mostly nearby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.68,0:10:41.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们通常会质疑房产经纪人的诚实度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Often people question realtors' sincerity.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.18,0:10:43.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你马上装作生气  冒犯者就会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take umbrage. Violators will-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.18,0:10:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  什么词是X开头的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, shoot. X- X-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.94,0:10:46.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间屋子真心棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this is the great room,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.94,0:10:49.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使"棒"这个词已经配不上这间屋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}although "Great" hardly seems to do a room like this justice.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.94,0:10:52.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请忽略这幅诡异的弯弯曲曲的画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Weird, squiggly painting not included.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.28,0:10:53.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-其实我挺喜欢这画的  -我也喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I actually love it. - I do too.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.67,0:10:54.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.68,0:10:57.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橱柜都是定制内嵌的  你会发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, all custom built-ins, and you will notice just-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.99,0:11:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房子采光充足  多好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just tons of natural light, so that's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.58,0:11:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做成这笔生意吗  当然想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did I need the sale? Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.22,0:11:03.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我为之担心吗  当然不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was I worried? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.54,0:11:05.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥  因为  因为啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? Because. Because why?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.79,0:11:09.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不会推销我不相信的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I won't sell anything I don't believe in.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.21,0:11:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我信了  你也会信的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And when I believe, you believe.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.76,0:11:15.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能把皮毛大衣卖给一个爱斯基摩人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could sell a fur coat to an Eskimo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.88,0:11:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  很抱歉  这个房子很漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, Phil, I'm sorry. It's a beautiful house.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.05,0:11:20.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我不确定这是否适合孩子居住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm just not sure how kid-friendly it is,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.15,0:11:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有两个小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we have two small children.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.72,0:11:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是这些楼梯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, these stairs alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.54,0:11:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  这地方酷毙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, this place is awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.77,0:11:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在不行  卢克  -你看后院了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Not now, Luke. - Did you see the backyard?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.82,0:11:27.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足以放下十间树屋呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's got room for 10 tree houses.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.60,0:11:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卧室的天花板上有窗户\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the bedroom's got a window on the ceiling.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.29,0:11:31.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望我们也能住在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wish we could live here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.90,0:11:35.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我希望你回露台去  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I wish you'd go back out to the patio where- - Do you really?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.28,0:11:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我家房子比这差多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. Our house sucks compared to this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.12,0:11:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实差太多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It really does.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.62,0:11:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们回来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.41,0:11:47.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去换衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna get changed and
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.32,0:11:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后一起去看曼尼的比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then we'll go back to Manny's match, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.96,0:11:52.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸不希望我去  -什么  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad doesn't want me to go. - What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.13,0:11:54.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得你曾担心咱儿子很没用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Remember when you were all worried that our son's a dud?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.31,0:11:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我印象中可没说"没用"什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. That's not exactly the way I remember it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.21,0:11:59.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验证明  他很有天分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turns out he's a natural.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.18,0:12:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪方面  -推销\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- At what? - At selling.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.43,0:12:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住宅房地产的泰坦巨神们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Titans of residential real estate.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.72,0:12:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  哥就说你们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's right, I'm talking to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.66,0:12:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桑迪·布鲁斯特  斯奇普·沃思南  麦卡宾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sandy Brewster, Skip Woosnum, J.J. McCubbin.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.94,0:12:13.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到后浪的脚步了吗  那是卢克·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hear those footsteps? That's Luke Dunphy,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.73,0:12:16.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要把你们拍死在沙滩上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he's gonna drink your milk shake.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.61,0:12:19.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可思议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.28,0:12:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对吧  -难以置信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Right? - Incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.99,0:12:22.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后买家将在一个小时内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, the buyer's coming back
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.08,0:12:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她丈夫一起过来  我需要卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in an hour with her husband, and I need him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.95,0:12:25.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你  这孩子是个天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am telling you, that kid is a genius.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.79,0:12:28.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的招财小神童驾到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's the rainmaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.42,0:12:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的iPod怎么在嘴里  -给它充电呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why is your iPod in your mouth? - I'm charging it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.83,0:12:35.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex. Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.80,0:12:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你一点也不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, there's no part of you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.98,0:12:43.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你姐姐消除误会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that wants to clear the air with your sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.14,0:12:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.70,0:12:45.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我尊重你家的处事方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fine. That's your family's way. I'll respect that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.81,0:12:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你该知道  这对爱你的人来说很难受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you should know, it's hard on the people who love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.48,0:12:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  -你让我们压力山大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cam - We feel the tension.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.97,0:12:52.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的话句句伤人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We hear the words that cut like knives.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.44,0:12:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  我带了切好的橙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, guys! I brought orange slices.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.07,0:12:56.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我受不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know what? I can't bear this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.07,0:12:58.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  米奇尔仍然对你小时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, Mitchell still resents you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.66,0:13:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退出花样滑冰队的事耿耿于怀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for quitting the figure skating team when you were kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.36,0:13:02.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐们  请跟我进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ladies, come inside with me, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.76,0:13:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩把问题解决了  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Work it out. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.83,0:13:07.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  小卡  -他说的是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks, Cam. - Is he serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.85,0:13:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你今早才用话攻击我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that what your little jab was about this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.08,0:13:12.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  是  好吧  是这么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. No. Yes. Okay, yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.46,0:13:13.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我仍然有点小生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I'm still a little angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.37,0:13:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你夺走了我的辉煌时刻  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, you know, you stole my moment, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.34,0:13:18.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是  21年前  -对你来说无所谓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, 21 years ago. - Okay, but it doesn't matter to you...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.34,0:13:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你有你自己的光辉时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you had your own moments.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.17,0:13:22.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是啦啦队队长  参演校园剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You had cheerleading and high school plays
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.27,0:13:23.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还与球队四分卫搞亲热\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and making out with the quarterback.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.80,0:13:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你也和他搞过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh come on, You made out with him too.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.40,0:13:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  但我们是偷偷摸摸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but we had to keep it a secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.81,0:13:29.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该退出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You shouldn't have quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.95,0:13:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太自私了  -想知道我退出的原因吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It was selfish. - You wanna know why I quit?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.06,0:13:35.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为了保护你  -保护什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I quit to protect you. - From what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.19,0:13:36.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到荣誉  名声还是记者招待会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Glory? Fame? Press conferences?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.82,0:13:38.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  我那时比你重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Come on. I was bigger than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.86,0:13:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比你重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was bigger than you,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.71,0:13:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕你举不动我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I was afraid you wouldn't be able to lift me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.74,0:13:43.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练习的时候你摔了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were dropping me in practice,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.18,0:13:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不想让你  -就摔过两次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And I didn't want you to  - I dropped you twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.37,0:13:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三次  -在那么多人面前丢脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Three times. - humiliate yourself in front of all those people.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.23,0:13:49.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直被你摔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You dropped me all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.79,0:13:56.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啦  你就原谅我  忘掉过去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Could you just forgive me and move on?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.63,0:14:01.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以  没错  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course. Yes, yes. Yes, of- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.21,0:14:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是很小气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. This must seem so petty, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.26,0:14:07.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有点傻  但我们都有些小心结  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's a little silly, but we all have our thing, don't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.40,0:14:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴你能释怀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just glad you're getting it out of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.14,0:14:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在举我吗  你真的是想把我举起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you trying to lift me? You are. You're trying to lift me. Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.27,0:14:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持专注  保持冷静  保持怒气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stay focused, stay loose and stay angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.20,0:14:26.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁最强悍  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who's the toughest? - I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.24,0:14:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁最勇敢  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who's the bravest? - I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.53,0:14:31.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁最棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's the baddest?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.69,0:14:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能一口气问完吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you guys ask all the questions now
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.33,0:14:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不用一遍遍举起这面罩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I don't have to keep lifting this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.04,0:14:37.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-上吧  -加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go. - Go get 'em!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.50,0:14:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开始了  准备好了吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There we go. You all set? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.50,0:14:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞  加油  好运哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, go get 'em. Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.01,0:14:44.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请问这有人坐吗  -没有  坐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Excuse me. Is this seat taken? - No. Sit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.30,0:14:45.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.43,0:14:48.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼是你家孩子吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, is Manny yours? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.97,0:14:51.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非常棒  我看过他比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, he's quite good. I saw him earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.31,0:14:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.97,0:14:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是你女儿吗  -卡罗琳吗  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is she your little girl? - Oh, Caroline? No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.14,0:14:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾  她的父母都过世了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sadly, her parents passed away.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.48,0:14:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是她在儿童医院的护士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm her nurse down at the children's hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.90,0:15:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我视所有病人为家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But all of my patients are like family to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.00,0:15:10.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们玩得很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, our boys are enjoying themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.95,0:15:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我可以谈论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. I can talk about
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.06,0:15:15.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整天的天花线和嵌入灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}crown moldings and recessed lighting until the cows come home,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.86,0:15:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有什么能与孩子的笑声相媲美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but nothing compares with that sound right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.78,0:15:23.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟啊  他没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Hey, buddy. Oh, he's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.53,0:15:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脚  我感觉脚扭过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My foot. I think it's backwards.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.39,0:15:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没扭过去  -怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's not backwards. - Wh-What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.51,0:15:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是这破地板  太滑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the stupid floors! They're too slippery.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.09,0:15:32.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橡木家具也被称为自然的枕头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oak. Also known as nature's pillow.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.36,0:15:35.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-像冰一样滑  -好了  别责备地板了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's like ice. - Now, let's not start blaming the floors.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.94,0:15:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不该跑的  -我看到一个鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You shouldn't have been running. - I saw a ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.08,0:15:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼  我是菲尔·邓菲  是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ghosts. Hey, Phil Dunphy. Okay, that's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.29,0:15:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这楼梯就像个天然鞋拔子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's acting like a natural shoehorn.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.55,0:15:48.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  大家最好都脱了鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Probably better all take
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.39,0:15:51.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再上楼参观  跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}our shoes off for this part of the tour. Follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.66,0:15:53.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我们的奇迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's our little miracle.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.24,0:15:56.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是她爸爸没死在阿富汗战场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. I only wish her father had made it back
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.70,0:15:58.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能来看比赛就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from Afghanistan to see this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.09,0:16:01.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的啦啦队来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, there's our cheering section.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.96,0:16:03.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边  朋友们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Over here, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.59,0:16:10.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的神呐  我们必须阻止他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. We have to stop him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.85,0:16:20.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我可以拉响火警警报器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe I can pull the fire alarm.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.96,0:16:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别指望我会手软\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Expect no mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.15,0:16:26.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放马过来吧  小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bring it on, big boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.22,0:16:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴爸爸为曼尼骄傲  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm-I'm glad Dad's proud of Manny. I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:35.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是希望看到他为我们骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just- It would have been nice to see him that proud of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.33,0:16:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我们  其实是指我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By us, I mean me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.21,0:16:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真觉得通过花样滑冰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you sincerely thought that the path to Dad's approval...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.96,0:16:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能得到爸爸的认可吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was going to be through figure skating?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.96,0:16:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我绝对确信爸爸最骄傲的时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, I am fairly confident that Dad's proudest moment...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.09,0:16:50.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你终于脱下那红色火焰紧身衣之时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was when you finally took off the flame-red unitard.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.47,0:16:53.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又没说我的话一定合理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not claiming that any of this is rational.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:59.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不该这么惹人厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm-I'm sorry. I'm sorry for being such a pill, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.73,0:17:04.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我一直为退出而内疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, actually, I always felt very guilty for quitting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.07,0:17:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你非常热爱花样滑冰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know how much you loved figure skating.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.15,0:17:11.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未真正喜爱过滑冰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never really loved skating.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.07,0:17:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.07,0:17:16.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这么说感觉有点娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, all right, this is gonna sound a little gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.83,0:17:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  当我们一起滑冰的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, um, when-when you and I skated together,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.91,0:17:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不再是刻薄的姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you weren't the mean older sister
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.62,0:17:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是缠人的小弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I wasn't the clingy little brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.74,0:17:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是一个团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were- we were a team, and-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:26.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实在的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, let's face it,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.48,0:17:28.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去几年  我们之间渐渐疏远\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we've kind of grown apart in the past few years.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.82,0:17:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为爸妈的离婚  我们又站在对立面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And with Mom and Dad's divorce, we were on opposing sides.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.16,0:17:36.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是怀念你我并肩作战的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I- I just- I miss being on your team.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.46,0:17:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.21,0:17:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是有点娘  -看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- a little gay. - There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.51,0:17:53.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  你要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.74,0:17:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.90,0:17:59.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.27,0:18:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.27,0:18:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really?  -Mm-m
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.03,0:18:08.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我摔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't drop me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.80,0:18:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不拿开  我给你砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Put it away or lose it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.01,0:18:32.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神呐  让这一切停止吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Somebody's got to put a stop to this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.01,0:18:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.36,0:18:51.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能请你们吃冰淇林吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, can we take you and Caroline out for ice cream?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.57,0:18:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  她有糖尿病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can't. She's diabetic.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.37,0:18:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜都猜到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.12,0:18:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌声祝贺我们的冠军  曼尼·迪尔加多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A round of applause for our winner, Manny Delgado.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.83,0:19:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  把这玩意放后备箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's get out of here. Get this thing in the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.04,0:19:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道我是骄傲还是窘迫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't decide if I'm feeling more proud or mortified.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.42,0:19:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How about now?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.02,0:19:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们教育孩子们说  输赢无所谓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We tell our kids it doesn't matter if you win or lose,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.27,0:19:22.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但平心而论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but let's be honest.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.04,0:19:26.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜利的感觉好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Winning feels pretty great.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.06,0:19:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在阳光下的那一刻是无与伦比的美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's nothing like that golden moment in the sun.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.66,0:19:36.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许每位家长都希望孩子能有这样的时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think every parent probably wants that for their child.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.62,0:19:40.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至希望自己也能这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And maybe a little bit for ourselves too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.18,0:19:44.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我们太苛求结果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes we push too hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.71,0:19:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果导致许多怨恨和愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that leads to a lot of resentment and guilt.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.18,0:19:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.84,0:19:53.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么才不算过分呢  我的想法是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, how much is too much? Here's where I come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.55,0:19:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愧疚总会过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guilt fades.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.84,0:19:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奖牌才是硬道理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hardware is forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.52,0:20:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在生气  是吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're mad, aren't you? - I'm not mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.29,0:20:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  你在生气  -我没生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes, you are. - No, I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.73,0:20:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有点嫉妒  -我为你俩感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're a little jealous. - I'm happy for the two of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.53,0:20:17.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们也来一次  站在那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, come on. We'll do one. Stay there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.88,0:20:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真来呀  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- For real?  -Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.79,0:20:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-感觉好点了吗  -是  我来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Feel better? - Yeah. Oh, do me now. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.34,0:20:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么国际玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.67,0:20:36.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.93,0:20:38.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, no.

