[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十八集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.94,0:00:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢的放松方式是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's my favorite way to relax?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.86,0:00:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴上我的无线耳机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Throw on my wireless headphones
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.99,0:00:09.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉浸在自然频道的节目中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and disappear into the Nature Channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.50,0:00:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}年幼的平背海龟在海底搜寻着食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The young flatback turtle searches for food on the ocean floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.87,0:00:16.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}然而这只平背海龟却\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This flatback, however-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.23,0:00:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然的美妙之处在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The fascinating thing about nature...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.54,0:00:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在眨眼之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is how, in the blink of an eye,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以从绝对的宁静美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it can go from a scene of total tranquil beauty...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.71,0:00:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变到原始的暴力场景\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to raw, primal violence.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.90,0:00:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带着这玩意儿真的听不到我说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you seriously not hear me with those things on?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.05,0:00:31.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是消除外界杂音的技术  你来试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's noise-canceling technology. Give it a spin. It's got-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.10,0:00:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  专注  -妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sweetie, focus, now. - Mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.76,0:00:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么对每个人都一惊一乍的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why are you freaking out on everyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.44,0:00:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你表现的很不负责任  你们全都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you are acting very irresponsibly- all of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.83,0:00:37.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.37,0:00:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克有个大型的课题研究要做  明天就得交\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke has a giant project due tomorrow for school
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.49,0:00:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他到现在都没开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that he hasn't even started,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.44,0:00:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而海莉刚通知我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Haley just informed me
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.65,0:00:43.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要为学校的募捐会准备40个纸杯蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she needs 40 cupcakes for her school fund-raiser,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是明天要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}also due tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.34,0:00:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想指出一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd like to point out
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.55,0:00:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我独立按时地完成了全部学校作业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I completed all my assignments on my own and on time.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.05,0:00:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是得瑟的时候  艾丽克斯  -听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Not now, Alex.  -Ok, look,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:53.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来做纸杯蛋糕  你去做课题研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will take the cupcakes. You do the project.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.81,0:00:55.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-主题是文森特·梵高  -成交\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's on Vincent Van Gogh. - Done!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.62,0:00:57.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我需要你好好监督他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ok, I need you to really stay on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.68,0:00:58.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他保持专注\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Keep him focused.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.57,0:01:01.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我打算采用一种不同的教育方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. I'm actually gonna take a different approach, but-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.80,0:01:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我强烈要求你别那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually gonna insist that you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.50,0:01:05.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  我知道你有你的方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, I know you've got your methods,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.23,0:01:06.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也有我的方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but so do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.09,0:01:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  但我不喜欢事必躬亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm sorry, but I'm not a micromanager.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.47,0:01:10.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我可以向卢克提供\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trust me, I can provide Luke
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.51,0:01:12.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他所需的工具和指导\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the tools and guidance he needs...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.59,0:01:15.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时又不会管得太死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without, uh, smothering him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.48,0:01:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我把孩子管得太死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think I smother our child?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.52,0:01:18.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你的错  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not your fault, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.56,0:01:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱管教是母亲的天性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Mother" Is part of the word.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.10,0:01:22.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没听说过父亲的天性是爱管教吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never hear of anyone being "Sfathered" to death.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.83,0:01:24.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道卢克的问题在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know what Luke's problem is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.60,0:01:26.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他患有注意力缺陷过动症\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's got A.D.H.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.09,0:01:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -不  我才没有呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - No, I don't!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.31,0:01:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是什么  -我可以告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What is it? - I'd tell you,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.64,0:01:32.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我肯定话没说完  你就走神了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but you'd wander off before I got to the "H."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.53,0:01:34.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应我你会好好监督他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just promise me that you will stay on him
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.52,0:01:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到他完成任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until this project is done.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.81,0:01:38.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的  但你得对他多点信心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will, but you might have a little more confidence in him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.73,0:01:43.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  哇  大家都听不见我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wah! Wah! No one can hear me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.28,0:01:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,众人皆蠢我独聪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody is stupid except me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.15,0:01:52.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈  哈  我好搞笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ha, ha, ha. I am funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.63,0:02:07.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是我见过的最有爱的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is this the cutest thing I've ever seen?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.97,0:02:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿着你的小望远镜站在路边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You out here on the curb with your little telescope,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.28,0:02:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着你爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}waiting for your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.51,0:02:13.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不叫有爱  那叫科学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not cute. It's-lt's science.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.26,0:02:16.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是壮观的天琴座流星雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tonight is the magnificent Lyrid meteor shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.81,0:02:19.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是"奇客星球"穿过"书呆子路"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's where the planet Geek passes through the Nerdy Way. It-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.71,0:02:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我私心以为很美好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you know I think it's sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每隔几年  米奇尔和他的爸爸就会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every couple years, Mitchell and his father go out
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.45,0:02:24.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去看流星雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and enjoy one of these showers together.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.86,0:02:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我觉得你那样说是不合适的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I- I wouldn't necessarily put it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.44,0:02:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  是的  我和我父亲很喜欢那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, yes, me and my father enjoy it,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.04,0:02:31.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们其实没什么共同兴趣爱好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because we don't share a lot of the same interests.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.78,0:02:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  我从来不跟他一起去看体育比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like, um, I-I never went to sports games with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.66,0:02:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是因为你称之为体育比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Probably because you call 'em "Sports games."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.29,0:02:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-略掉"体育"  -直接说"比赛"就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just lose the "Sports." - Just- Just games.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.88,0:02:44.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  你的沐"雨"伙伴来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, here comes your shower partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.32,0:02:45.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.68,0:02:47.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的  和你爸玩得开心  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding. Have fun with your dad, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.49,0:02:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  晚点见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.67,0:02:51.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别担心我  -我才不担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't worry about me. - I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.34,0:02:53.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是假设你或许会担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just saying, if you were.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.30,0:02:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副驾驶座已占  衰仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shotgun, sucka!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.44,0:03:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保你的座位已经调到你想要的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Make sure your seat is exactly the way you want it,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:06.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以随便按上面这些控制按钮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and feel free to play with any of these controls up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.22,0:03:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也不知道各个功能是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have no idea what they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.66,0:03:10.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我希望我的车就是你的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I want mi car to be su car.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.11,0:03:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  你还好吧  你似乎很紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, are you okay? You seem nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.41,0:03:16.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张  怎么可能  我才不紧张呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, nervous? No. I'm not nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.00,0:03:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实很紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.96,0:03:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  当米奇和他爸计划好出去之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, when Mitchell made plans with his father,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.52,0:03:25.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想  为何不和歌洛莉亚出去玩一晚呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figured, why not spend the evening with Gloria?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.25,0:03:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都想和她做闺蜜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've always wanted to be good friends with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.63,0:03:29.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理论上说  我们注定是好闺蜜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}On paper, we should be good friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.21,0:03:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧我们  一个火辣  身材曲线玲珑的歌后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at us. One spicy, curvy diva-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.01,0:03:34.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.30,0:03:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是  我造成了一点小隔阂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The problem is, I had a little minor setback
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.93,0:03:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是几周前的事了  我们必须得克服才行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that we had to overcome from a couple weeks ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.23,0:03:41.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真受不了和他常青藤的朋友们一起玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I cannot stand hanging out with his lvy League friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.60,0:03:42.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们最差劲了  -他们也没那么差劲啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, they're the worst. - They're not that bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.84,0:03:44.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们是最差劲的  -开什么玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They are the worst! - Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.77,0:03:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要黛比两分钟内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Debbie can't go two minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.66,0:03:47.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不谈哥伦比亚大学都不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without talking about Columbia University.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.69,0:03:49.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那个哈佛毕业的弱视小矮子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the little guy with the lazy eye from Harvard.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.79,0:03:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是布朗大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brown.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.61,0:03:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.21,0:03:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我希望那个骚货可以滚回哥伦比亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honestly, I wish that tart would go back to Columbia...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.70,0:03:55.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她古怪的棕色小朋友也带走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and take her weird little Brown friend with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.07,0:03:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Brown  棕色的  也指布朗大学]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.71,0:04:05.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  你得放松  你已经解释过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, you need to relax. You explained.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.79,0:04:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越解释越糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.84,0:04:10.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道出现尴尬的事情时  我变得多失控\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know how awkward I get when things get awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.67,0:04:11.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我说"棕色的人"[布朗大学学生]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So when I said "Brown people,"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.97,0:04:14.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是在说你们这些棕色皮肤的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wasn't talking about your, uh, brown people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.89,0:04:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在说那些布朗大学的学生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was talking about people who go to a university.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.39,0:04:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你们这种人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, not your people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.22,0:04:23.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说你们这种人不能上大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}N-Not that your people couldn't go to college.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.39,0:04:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我听到我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, now I'm hearing myself
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.66,0:04:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了太多的"你们这种人"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}say "Your people" a lot, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.32,0:04:32.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是很兴奋  因为这是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, just very excited because this is, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.32,0:04:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们第一次一起出去过夜生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, this is our first night out together,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.10,0:04:35.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是我们的小约会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so it's our little date.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.53,0:04:36.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这是要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where are we going?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.14,0:04:39.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先确保你的安全带牢牢系上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Make sure your seat belt is securely fastened...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.26,0:04:41.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及你的小餐桌直立收起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and your tray tables are in the upright position...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.34,0:04:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们要去帕莱索餐厅啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because I got us into Palaiseau!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.00,0:04:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好高级啊  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ah! Fancy! -I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.44,0:04:47.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常要提前4周预约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's normally a four-week wait,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.66,0:04:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那个领班是我在普拉提课上的好基友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but the matre d' is an old Pilates brother of mine,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.98,0:04:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只要打个电话就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so just one phone call.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:52.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.18,0:04:55.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕莱索\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Palaiseau!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.12,0:04:58.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  卡梅隆  其实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, Cameron, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.14,0:05:01.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我好像没心情去那么高档的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know if I'm in the mood for something so fancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.63,0:05:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能去个  比较简单点的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we just go somewhere, like, more simple?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.55,0:05:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  好的  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, uh, yes. Yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.34,0:05:10.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以...你想去哪里啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can- What were- What did you have in mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.70,0:05:12.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.60,0:05:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去我以前常去的一个拉丁小餐馆怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How 'bout a little Latin place that I always used to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.02,0:05:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听上去很棒  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That sounds fantastic. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.02,0:05:21.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想看看你们那种人的饮食文化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would love to see how your people eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.10,0:05:23.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你们那种人"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Your people"?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.44,0:05:25.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是哪根筋搭错了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is wrong with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.32,0:05:26.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好  现在是打鸡蛋时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. It's egg-crackin' time.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.83,0:05:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  妈来传授你一个打鸡蛋的窍门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, I find the key to cracking an egg properly-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.03,0:05:31.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我不是孩子了  我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I'm not a child. I can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.61,0:05:33.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.12,0:05:34.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.12,0:05:35.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈可不傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mom's not dumb.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.36,0:05:38.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能直接开口让她帮你做事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't just ask her to do something for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.16,0:05:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要摆好龙门阵  坐等她上钩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to very carefully put the cheese in the trap.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.79,0:05:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  我弄了一点蛋壳进碗里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Oops. I got a little shell in the bowl.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.88,0:05:49.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生那种事的是时候  我觉得我会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When that happens, I find that I like to...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.13,0:05:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别那样做  -我抓到了  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do not do that. - I got it. It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.01,0:05:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好恶心啊  -好吧  放着  我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, that's- that's really gross. - Okay. I'm gonna- I'll do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.43,0:05:56.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你擦擦手走人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just mop up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.68,0:05:58.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And snap.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.72,0:06:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为她感到悲哀是不是不该啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it bad that I feel sorry for her?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.93,0:06:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我该如何开始呢  -你觉得呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So how do I start? -What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.44,0:06:07.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  通常都是妈妈告诉我怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. Mom usually tells me what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.19,0:06:10.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此  我开玩笑的  我爱你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Join the club. I'm kidding. I love your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.53,0:06:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天换个新的学习方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We are going to try a new approach this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.24,0:06:15.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好  你的目标是要创建一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, your goal is to create a display
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.94,0:06:17.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于梵高的生平和作品的展板  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about the life and art of Van Gogh, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.91,0:06:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -好的  你的展示板在此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Okay. You got your poster board right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.54,0:06:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  就假装你是在叙述他的生平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, pretend you're telling the story of his life...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.58,0:06:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而听众是从未听说过他的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to someone who has never heard of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.07,0:06:30.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会在展板上放些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you put on that board?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.09,0:06:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见你的脑筋在转动  创意的火花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see the wheels spinning. A spark of crea-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.64,0:06:35.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是怎么把铅锌放进铅笔里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do they get the lead in pencils?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.12,0:06:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  别跑题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ok, Let's try to stay on topic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.14,0:06:38.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  杰  瞧瞧谁认为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay. Look who thinks
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.97,0:06:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水星是太阳系中密度最大的行星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mercury is the densest planet in the solar system.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.73,0:06:45.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你嘲笑的语气中  我就知道我说错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I take it from your mocking tone that I am incorrect.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.52,0:06:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密度最大的行星是地球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Densest planet is Earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.97,0:06:50.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就是密度最大的星球上最愚钝的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which makes you the densest guy on the densest planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.24,0:06:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Densest一词多意  密度最大的/愚钝的]
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.40,0:06:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-中枪  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Zing! -Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.41,0:06:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(191,217)\fn方正琥珀简体\fs26}当天早些时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.74,0:06:54.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定米奇尔不建议我跟着去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You sure Mitchell won't mind me tagging along?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.66,0:06:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  他很爱你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding? He loves ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.14,0:06:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在担心什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you worried about?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.24,0:06:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前从来没有过兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've never had a brother before.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.95,0:07:01.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和他一起相处的时间也不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We never really hung out that much.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.91,0:07:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  你想太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kiddo, you are overthinking this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.37,0:07:06.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想说错话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just don't wanna say the wrong thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.21,0:07:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的  那正是有兄弟的好处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't. That's the beauty of having a brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.20,0:07:10.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我弟弟总是相互抨击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me and my brother were zinging each other all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.00,0:07:12.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  "什么情况啊  肥仔"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, like, "What's going on, fat boy?"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.98,0:07:14.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"没什么  蠢蛋'\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Nothing much, jackass."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.59,0:07:15.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那样互相出糗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, things of that nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.88,0:07:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是兄弟间表达爱的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's- It's how brothers express love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.70,0:07:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副驾驶位已占  衰仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shotgun, sucka!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:29.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈  真有你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.52,0:07:32.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去欣赏一下风景\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna see the sights.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.23,0:07:34.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让风景先看到你哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not if they see you first!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.95,0:07:37.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那玩笑没有笑点  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kind of missed with that one, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.57,0:07:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.98,0:07:43.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道的信息都在上面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is all you need to know right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.75,0:07:46.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  铅笔杆一开始是分开的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Apparently, the pencil's in two pieces,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.27,0:07:47.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后才将铅锌放中间粘合到一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they glue 'em together on the lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.87,0:07:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把关于他生平的材料放这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if we put all the stuff about his life on this side...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.79,0:07:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于他画作的材料放那边怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and all the stuff about his paintings on this side?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.38,0:07:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  小老弟  那太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, buddy, that's fantastic!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.54,0:07:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最棒的是  这个主意是你自己想出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the best part is, you came up with that by yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.80,0:08:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需要一点专注就做到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All it took was a little bit of focus and, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.31,0:08:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意儿真松了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This thing is really loose.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.43,0:08:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿把螺丝起子  你继续弄这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna go grab a screwdriver. But you run with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.65,0:08:09.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各就各位  预备开始  小梵高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}On your mark, get set, Van Gogh.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.95,0:08:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  爸  他长得有点像米奇尔舅舅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Dad. He kind of looks like Uncle Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.32,0:08:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果米奇尔舅舅是疯子的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if Uncle Mitchell were insane.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.95,0:08:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被黄鼠狼的臭液喷到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got sprayed by a skunk!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.42,0:08:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你臭死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you stink!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.57,0:08:25.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅是在天文学方面很"臭"  攻击成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And not just at astronomy! Blammo!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.99,0:08:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎么回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.91,0:08:35.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱这地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.17,0:08:37.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点担心  因为这并不是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was a little bit worried because it's not exactly-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.42,0:08:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  爱  这地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I... love... this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.10,0:08:43.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  很  紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I... was... nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.28,0:08:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  菜单上有很多不同的食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, there was a lot of different food on the menu,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.99,0:08:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地上也有  墙上也有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and on the floor, and on the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.03,0:08:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你的话没有任何一点夸张吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are we sure we're not exaggerating just a little bit?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.74,0:08:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当时在现场吗  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Were you there, Mitchell?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.93,0:08:53.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你在  我肯定能认得出当场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I think I would have recognized
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.07,0:08:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除我之外的唯一一个白人或同志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the only other white or gay person.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.83,0:08:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经冒犯过歌洛莉亚一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd already offended Gloria once.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.79,0:08:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再有第二次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not gonna do it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.50,0:09:02.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn经典行楷简\fs22\pos(196,265)}你好  欢迎光临  是歌洛莉亚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.13,0:09:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn经典行楷简\fs22\pos(196,265)}好久没光临过小店啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.69,0:09:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是我朋友卡梅隆  -欢迎光临\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mi amigo Cameron. - Ah, welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.66,0:09:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-照旧点"辣得跳"吧  -你还记得啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So, carnitas diablos. - Ah, you remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.22,0:09:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也给我同样的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I'll just have the same thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.38,0:09:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  你该点鸡肉玉米卷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. You should have the chicken enchiladas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.54,0:09:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我也要"辣得跳"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'll have the carnitas diablos.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.18,0:09:20.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你扛不住的  -你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- These are not for you. - Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.31,0:09:21.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西太辣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're too spicy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.00,0:09:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚小姐是因为已经习惯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Miss Gloria's used to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.05,0:09:23.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, he's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.10,0:09:27.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以辣得让你震惊到趴下  美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can spice you under the table any day there, sweet thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.77,0:09:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要"辣得跳"  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dos carnitas diablos, por favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.27,0:09:32.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.98,0:09:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.93,0:09:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇  止步  -好吧  我妄想什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell! - Of course. What was I thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.60,0:09:43.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我们  能直接回家了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, can we- can we just go home, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.19,0:09:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得先把身上臭气散掉  我才让你进车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've got to air out first before I let you in that car.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.91,0:09:47.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则车里的气味永远消不掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll never get the stink out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.60,0:09:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  杰  那是金星吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay, is that Venus?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.60,0:09:53.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[金星的大气层里有浓硫酸  会下硫酸雨]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.50,0:09:52.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从这儿可以闻到纯硫酸的酸臭气哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause I can smell the clouds of pure sulfuric acid from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.56,0:09:56.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-躺枪  -好吧  我真得回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Slam! - Okay. I-I'd really like to go home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.15,0:09:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会错过流星雨的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll miss the meteor shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.49,0:09:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题出在你的衣服上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The trouble is your clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.91,0:10:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱下吧  车后备箱里有条毛毯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just take them off. I think there's a blanket in the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.99,0:10:02.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You sure, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.79,0:10:04.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不担心我会把毛毯弄臭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not worried I might stink up the blanket?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.37,0:10:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.96,0:10:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们用来铺在车座上的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We just use it to cover up the seat
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.57,0:10:10.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼练完探戈会汗淋淋的要隔一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for when Manny's all sweaty after his tango class.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.12,0:10:12.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你没出汗  就说明你练得不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you don't sweat, you're not doing it right.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.88,0:10:21.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我曾拥有的最佳男友之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was one of the best boyfriends I ever had.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.26,0:10:24.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但他是同性恋  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But he was gay. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.26,0:10:25.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一个月后就察觉出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figured that out after the first month-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.76,0:10:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我跟他继续谈了一年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I stayed for a whole year
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.98,0:10:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他剪的发型超赞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because the haircuts were fantastic!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.06,0:10:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好笑吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's funny, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.25,0:10:34.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  也没那么好笑吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, that one is not that funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.73,0:10:35.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.38,0:10:38.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你确定吗  -我喜欢这地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you sure? - I love this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.55,0:10:41.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你头上汗如雨下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But your head is running water.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.30,0:10:42.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你大概看错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I don't think it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.56,0:10:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说对你太辣了吧  你的衬衫都汗湿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told you it was too spicy for you. Look at your shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.61,0:10:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我得去喝点东西缓解一下  -不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I just need to get a bit of a drink of something. - No, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.17,0:10:52.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  喝水只会辣上加辣  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, the water makes it so worse. No!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.73,0:10:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的对  真是辣上加辣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you're right. That does make it worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.62,0:10:57.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉就像是吞下了火辣的太阳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh- I feel like I ate the sun!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.78,0:11:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是面粉不搅成块状物的秘诀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that is the secret to no lumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.55,0:11:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见了吗  挺有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? It's kind of fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.03,0:11:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-都是你的功劳  妈  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You make it fun, Mom. - Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.65,0:11:06.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听"注意力缺陷过动症"的症状\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen to these symptoms of A.D.H.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.73,0:11:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们敢说卢克不符合吗  -艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And tell me it's not Luke. - Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.67,0:11:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极易因外界无关刺激而分心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Easily distracted by irrelevant stimuli."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.27,0:11:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常冲动地放弃正在干的事  去干别的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Often impulsively abandons one task for another."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.57,0:11:33.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来我是放在那里了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's where I left those.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.57,0:11:37.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在行动前不考虑后果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"A tendency to act without regard to consequences,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.07,0:11:40.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常不考虑个人安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}often at the expense of personal safety."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.56,0:11:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-经常发生事故  -好了  别读了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "Having accidents more often"  -Ok, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.03,0:12:01.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  艾丽克斯  我们懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think that's enough, Alex. We've got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.32,0:12:19.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. No!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.16,0:12:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  菲尔  亲爱的  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil. Phil! Honey, are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.58,0:12:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  记得之前找不到的那个太阳镜吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Remember those sunglasses I couldn't find?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.38,0:12:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bingo!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.71,0:12:34.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就让你做一件事  就是监督卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I asked you to do one thing- stay on top of Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.59,0:12:35.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For your information,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.37,0:12:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子正努力地解读一副梵高的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}your son is hard at work on an awesome Van Gogh-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.68,0:12:39.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得修下楼梯了  杰作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gotta fix that- masterpiece.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.12,0:12:41.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看了就知道了  你会大吃一惊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait'll you see. You're gonna be so surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.00,0:12:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.59,0:12:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就等着他能令我大吃一惊呢  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want nothing more than to be surprised, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.11,0:12:53.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都不惊讶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.41,0:12:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  够了  我再也不想听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's it. I don't want to hear anything
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.78,0:12:58.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所谓的做事的新方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about your new method of doing things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.95,0:13:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对付那些孩子只有一个方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's one thing that works with these kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.47,0:13:02.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是严格监督  严厉管教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that is staying on top of them,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.25,0:13:04.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你  我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which, thanks to you, my friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.21,0:13:06.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得忙活一整晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will now be able to do all night long.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.30,0:13:15.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很不高兴  老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not happy, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.49,0:13:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该在干正经事才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're supposed to be working.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.47,0:13:17.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在干正经事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am working.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.40,0:13:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩土豆娃娃  正经个屁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mr. Potato Head, really?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.08,0:13:20.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道你怎么想的  -不  我不想听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know what you think, but- - No, I don't wanna hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.84,0:13:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要下去清扫车库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm going down to clean up the garage,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.56,0:13:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我会回来  一直监督着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then I'm coming back and I'm gonna stand over you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.06,0:13:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到你最终完成  明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until this thing is done, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.74,0:13:35.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快吸气  -吸气只会让"火"烧得更旺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Breathe. - Breathing only makes the fire spread.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.65,0:13:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就喝了这瓶牛奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Then drink this milk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.41,0:13:41.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  你为什么要点那道辣菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, Cam. Why did you have to order that spicy dish?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.37,0:13:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  我  我是个大白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I'm, um, a big idiot...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.58,0:13:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你我二人能度过一个美好的夜晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I wanted to have this awesome night between the two of us...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.37,0:13:49.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们变成好闺蜜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where we end up best friends,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.16,0:13:51.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起出去吃饭  买鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, having lunch, buying shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.00,0:13:55.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  我们一起去吃饭  买鞋吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay! Let's go have lunch, let's go buy shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.13,0:13:59.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -是啊  你为什么这么惊讶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - Yeah. Why are you so surprised?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.09,0:14:00.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我总觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't know. I guess i just always
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.86,0:14:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把我们之间的关系搞砸了  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}feel like I blow it with you, Gloria
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.22,0:14:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是针对哥伦比亚的那些话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}whether it's the Columbian comment...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.43,0:14:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是选错了餐馆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or picking the wrong restaurant.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.41,0:14:11.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餐馆那事可不是你的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The restaurant had nothing to do with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.15,0:14:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是没心情去那么高级的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just not in the mood to go anywhere that fancy...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.23,0:14:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我今早干了一件蠢事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}after the stupid thing I did this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.45,0:14:18.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.03,0:14:22.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我买了件裙子  -你个女魔头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I bought a dress. - You monster.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:26.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是件超贵的裙子  其实我根本就不需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. It was a very expensive dress that I don't need.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.12,0:14:28.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到家的时候觉得自己好愚蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I felt so stupid that when I got home,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.46,0:14:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不想把它拿回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I couldn't even bring it inside the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.75,0:14:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我放在车里了  -我完全理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I left it in the car. - I totally get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.96,0:14:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有个传奇性的"帽子故事"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a legendary hat story.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.96,0:14:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打赌你穿那件裙子一定美若天仙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll bet you look fabulous in that dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.34,0:14:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但谁穿上那件裙子都会美若天仙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, but anyone would look fabulous in that dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你找到毛毯了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You find that blanket? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.96,0:14:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能找到这件裙子  快闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was all I could find. Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.68,0:14:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是完美展现你的好身材啊  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really shows off your shape. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.00,0:14:51.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转一圈  小美妞  让我们瞧瞧你的美臀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Spin around, cupcake. Let's see the caboose!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.94,0:14:54.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有薯条配你那"奶臀"啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You get fries with that shake?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.13,0:14:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Shake奶昔  此处指摇晃的臀部]
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.15,0:14:57.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是太过分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was that too far?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.06,0:14:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡事都有界限的  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a line, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.03,0:15:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最好过去解释一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I better go mop this up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.32,0:15:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  拜托  怎么找不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on. Where's the-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.66,0:15:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果刚刚有点过分  我向你道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry if things got a little out of hand back there,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.36,0:15:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们想辩解一下  瞧瞧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but in our defense, look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.50,0:15:15.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  闻闻你身上的味儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, smell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.55,0:15:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的道歉可真令人"顺心"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a fantastic apology.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.71,0:15:20.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生那孩子的气  是我教他那么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't be too hard on the kid. I was egging him on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.34,0:15:24.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你要生气  就生我的气好啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be mad, be mad at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.49,0:15:25.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Done!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.69,0:15:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是很高兴看到那孩子露出笑脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just happy to see him laugh a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.10,0:15:29.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他这周过得挺不开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, he's had kind of a tough week.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:31.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被黄鼠狼喷了一身臭屁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got sprayed by a skunk,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.25,0:15:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还穿着一条把我屁股衬托得很翘的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm wearing a dress that makes my hips look huge.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.52,0:15:37.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他不希望我提起这事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know he doesn't want me to talk about it,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.28,0:15:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他没有获邀参加某个盛大的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he didn't get invited to this big party.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.28,0:15:41.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他自以为那些人是他的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some kids he thought were his friends
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.98,0:15:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对方认为他是个怪人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}think he's weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.95,0:15:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你了解我的  我  我不擅长处理这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, you know me on this. I'm no- I'm no good at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.70,0:15:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  总是不知道该如何安慰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I- I never know what to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.85,0:15:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.54,0:15:54.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但或许我养大的儿子知道该怎么安慰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But maybe I raised a kid who would know what to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.21,0:15:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才邀他一起过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the only reason I invited him along-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.25,0:15:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  这种天文观测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, because this astronomy stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.99,0:16:02.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  属于我们父子俩的亲密时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's- that's our thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.01,0:16:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好吧  我去找他谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. No, I'll talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.01,0:16:08.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  你穿这件衣服一点都不可笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you don't look that ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.65,0:16:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的美腿真的可以衬起这件衣服  -老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Now, you actually got the legs for it. - Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.49,0:16:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm just saying,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.17,0:16:14.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-如果你是那种喜欢穿女装的同性恋  -老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- if you were that type of a gay- - Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.23,0:16:16.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能也会混得不错哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'd probably do all right for yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.31,0:16:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.69,0:16:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实一直觉得这片地区很危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I always had a sense it was dangerous down here,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.40,0:16:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实还挺有魅力的  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I guess it's actually kind of charming, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.07,0:16:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  一点都不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's not safe at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.08,0:16:30.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我曾经就住这儿  你知道吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I used to live down here, you know. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.08,0:16:33.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的哦  所以我才过来  瞧那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that's why I come down here. Look there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.96,0:16:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我曾经住过的公寓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was my old apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.96,0:16:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我离开哈维尔后  只能负担得起那样的房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}After I left Javier, that's all I could afford.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.88,0:16:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是我人生经历的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's still part of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.88,0:16:42.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得记住那些过往的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to remember those things,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.74,0:16:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你出身在农场一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like you when you go to your farm.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.68,0:16:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得那个呀  我好像是一年前告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You remember that? I told you that a year ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.01,0:16:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然记得  你是我的朋友  你个大白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course I do. You're my friend, you big idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.46,0:16:54.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  这一地区治安或许很差劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, this part of town might be very rough,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.44,0:16:57.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这里的人  小卡  他们都是最好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but the people here, Cameron- the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.15,0:17:01.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很确定我停车的时候  轮子还在的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm pretty sure I had wheels when I parked here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.48,0:17:03.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶个熊  谁干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ayayay! Who did this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.57,0:17:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  没事的  歌洛莉亚  -是谁干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, it's okay, Gloria. - Who did this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.57,0:17:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个狗娘养的缩头乌龟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You coward son of bitches!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.09,0:17:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  大家伙  我上了保险的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's okay, everybody! I'm- I'm insured!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.45,0:17:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  怎么着  怕了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? What? You scared?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.88,0:17:15.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢出来露脸了吗  怂货娘们儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You scared to show your face, little girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.29,0:17:17.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  没事的大家  -小卡  去车里待着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, it's all right, everybody! - Cameron, wait in the car!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.37,0:17:19.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡梅隆  -歌洛莉亚  我觉得还是可以开的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cameron! - Gloria, I think it's drivable.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.95,0:17:21.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.76,0:17:25.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说  我马上会回到卢克的房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just so you know, I'm going back up to Luke's room,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.81,0:17:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他不弄完我就不走  -谢谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and I'm not leaving until he's finished. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.47,0:17:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉还是有点高估卢克了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm really sorry for not underestimating Luke enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.43,0:17:33.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话让我深感宽慰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that means a lot to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.06,0:17:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最艰难的是  他这些毛病都是跟我学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The hardest part is, he kinda takes after me with all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.29,0:17:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如我做事缺乏专注以及你的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like my lack of focus and your-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.11,0:17:41.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的什么  -我好爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- My what? - I just love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.38,0:17:47.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完成了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.11,0:17:49.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.07,0:17:51.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们喜欢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you like it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.49,0:17:53.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我超爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I- I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.83,0:17:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是你帮忙的吗  -都是他一手做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you do this? -All him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.66,0:17:57.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用上了土豆娃娃的耳朵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I used Mr. Potato Head ears
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.61,0:17:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为梵高曾自割耳朵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because Van Gogh cut his ear off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.33,0:18:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面还贴着钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And there's money
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.28,0:18:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他的画现在卖到天文数字般的价格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because his paintings sell for, like, a bajillion dollars,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.92,0:18:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很可悲  因为他死时身无分文\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is sad because he died broke.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.63,0:18:07.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  那...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. That-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是对的  -不用道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You were right. -Don't apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.22,0:18:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不是在道歉  -接受你的道歉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm not apologizing. -Apology accepted.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.65,0:18:16.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  我真的好为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, I-I really couldn't be more proud of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.44,0:18:18.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉之前看扁你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I am so sorry I didn't give you more credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.84,0:18:21.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -真棒  老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks. - Way to go, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.69,0:18:24.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去把纸杯蛋糕做完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gotta go finish the cupcakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.53,0:18:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. She didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.24,0:18:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的   把那个递给我好吗  -嗯哼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sweetie, can you hand me those? - Uh-huh.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.95,0:18:32.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我可以聊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.58,0:18:34.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.99,0:18:36.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经向你演示怎么做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I showed you how to make 'em,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.52,0:18:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你可以自己做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and now you can do it yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.54,0:18:41.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了大家  都出去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, guys. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.21,0:18:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  因为我真的很想亲自动手呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, good, because I really wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.72,0:18:49.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我把烤箱温度调到700度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I'm setting the oven to 700!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.41,0:18:52.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  接下来把鸡蛋打入碗里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm putting, uh- I'm putting the eggs in the bowl!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.39,0:18:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  我把蛋壳弄进去了  哎呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I got some shells in 'em! Uh-oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.01,0:18:57.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不要这么绝情啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.44,0:19:04.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. - Hey, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.57,0:19:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我知道你永远不会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I know you'd never, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.82,0:19:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你永远不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know you'd never,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.78,0:19:12.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我现在的样子永远也不会相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}never believe this by looking at me right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.20,0:19:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前在学校也被排斥被欺负\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but, um, I used to get picked on at school too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.50,0:19:18.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰告诉你了哈  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So Jay told you? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.21,0:19:20.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会说我是怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, they would, um- they'd call me weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.83,0:19:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确很怪  有趣的那种怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was weird. Uh, fun weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.17,0:19:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是成长的可笑之处就在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I- This is the funny thing about growing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.80,0:19:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在多年的时间中  大家都很害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For years and years, everybody's desperately afraid...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.30,0:19:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,标新立异  异于常人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to be different, you know, in any way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.23,0:19:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  突然间  几乎是一夜之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then, suddenly, almost overnight,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.68,0:19:37.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家又都想异于常人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}everybody wants to be different,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.31,0:19:41.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我们胜利的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that is where we win.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.19,0:19:44.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我期盼着那一天的到来  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm sort of counting on that. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.36,0:19:46.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很抱歉对你太不客气了  -那...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm sorry I was picking on you too much. -Ah, that's-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.86,0:19:48.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰说兄弟间就是那样相处的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay said that's what brothers do.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.36,0:19:51.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以不用听他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we don't have to listen to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.52,0:19:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有时兄弟会合伙反抗老爸的  -姑娘们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Brothers do that too. - Okay, ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.68,0:19:54.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶话会该开完了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Finish up your tea party.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.07,0:19:56.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要错过好戏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're missing the show.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.66,0:19:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不该相信我会和这家伙较劲儿  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can't believe I was fighting over this guy, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.50,0:20:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  快看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Check it out. Check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.25,0:20:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇  -太美了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wow. - Awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.63,0:20:11.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么梵高会创作《星夜》那幅画呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why did he paint The Starry Night?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.43,0:20:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是因为天空很美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe because the sky is beautiful,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.50,0:20:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都喜欢仰望星空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and everybody likes looking at it,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.72,0:20:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那提醒我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it reminds us
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.94,0:20:24.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中有东西在时刻盯着我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that something's up there watching over all of us-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.79,0:20:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是外星人  他们可以瞬间到达地球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}aliens, who could be here in a second...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.55,0:20:30.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们溶解成液体  变成燃料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to liquefy us and use us as fuel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.19,0:20:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒吧  全人类  下一个就是我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So wake up, people. We're next.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.86,0:20:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.86,0:20:36.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好快下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You better get down here!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.29,0:20:43.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.14,0:20:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好美味哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow! Delicious!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.62,0:20:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.00,0:20:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  妈  我把这些都包起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Thanks, Mom. I'm just gonna wrap these up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.97,0:20:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那个  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You know what, sweetie?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.86,0:20:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上学要迟到了  快走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be late for school. Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.17,0:20:53.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会儿给你送过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll bring 'em by later.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.09,0:20:54.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you sure? -Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.06,0:20:56.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快去吧  甜品大师  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Get out of here, Betty Crocker. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.30,0:20:58.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so proud of you!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.30,0:21:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有中毒控制中心的电话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do we still have the number for Poison Control?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.38,0:21:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  克莱尔  至"死"不渝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you, Claire. I'll always love you!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.19,0:21:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的嘴巴麻醉了  像看牙医的时候一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mouth is asleep, like at the dentist.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.64,0:21:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快过来  老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get over here, buddy.

