[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.59,0:02:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.59,0:02:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.59,0:02:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十七集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.58,0:00:04.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  有一部休·格兰特...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, honey, Hugh Grant has a--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.00,0:00:05.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm in.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.12,0:00:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  艾丽克斯11点有大提琴课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, well, Alex has a cello lesson at 11:00...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.37,0:00:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中午要参加象棋课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Junior Congress at noon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.85,0:00:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是还要上一辈子的光棍课吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doesn't she also have no boys at forever?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.46,0:00:14.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是关心一下自己的饮食失调问题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you have an eating disorder you need to attend to?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.92,0:00:18.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  可以看4点或6:20的场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, anyway, uh, we could see the 4:00 or the 6:20.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.80,0:00:19.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  那两场我都去不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, actually, that's no good.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.85,0:00:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和丹妮丝去喝点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm meeting my friend Denise for a drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.47,0:00:22.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮丝  我认识吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Denise? Do I know Denise?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.74,0:00:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  就是我前女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. You know, my old girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.47,0:00:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  想到你和一个女人在一起就恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Gross. I can't even picture you with a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.52,0:00:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -你还有前女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thank you. - You had a girlfriend before Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.15,0:00:31.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是两个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Try two.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.54,0:00:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前一直过得很快活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trust me. I had plenty of fun in my time.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.98,0:00:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到遇见了你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then I met your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.53,0:00:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢"恭维"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.74,0:00:40.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她应该是四处奔波\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I guess she travels
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.09,0:00:42.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为某个化妆品公司做推销\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}around selling makeup for a cosmetics company.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.99,0:00:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会在城里待一周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's in town for a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说  她是个挨家挨户的推销员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean she's like a door-to-door salesman?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.33,0:00:50.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换成是你  就是个呆家呆户的推销员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you were doing it, they'd call it a dork-to-dork salesman.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.08,0:00:53.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一记漂亮的突袭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My boy strikes like a rattlesnake!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.75,0:00:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那  那你就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah? W-Well, you-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.13,0:00:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  电影明天再去看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. All right, well, we can see the movie tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.30,0:01:00.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我走  该去上课了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. It's time for your lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.97,0:01:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第二堂课  她刚刚可是被我教育了一课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean her second lesson, because she just got schooled.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.06,0:01:08.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天是怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's wrong with me today?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.13,0:01:10.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  宝贝  今天你的水平发挥不出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shake it off, champ. It's not your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.85,0:01:16.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好  小家伙  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay, good morning, papi. -Is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.57,0:01:19.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在为试镜结果难过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, you're still sad because of that audition.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.09,0:01:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那角色是我的  我生来就该演特维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That part was mine. I was born to play Tevye.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[电影"屋顶上的小提琴手"主角]
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.07,0:01:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们竟然让罗德·杰克逊来演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Instead they give it to Rod Jackson?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.91,0:01:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他哪里懂什么叫受苦受难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What does he know from suffering?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.91,0:01:27.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-情况如何  -略有起色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are we doing? - A little better.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.31,0:01:29.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这问题得用冰激凌解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we're gonna go and throw ice cream at the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.94,0:01:32.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是冰激凌都没用  就试试这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if that doesn't work, this should do the trick.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.79,0:01:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"大难不死  人自更强"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"What doesn't kill us makes us stronger."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.55,0:01:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个挂在你房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can hang this in your room.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.74,0:01:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早晨看一眼  用心去体会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can see it every morning, start to internalize it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.83,0:01:40.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后什么都打不倒你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pretty soon nothing will keep you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.53,0:01:41.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那话不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.35,0:01:42.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.37,0:01:44.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多大难只会让人更脆弱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lots of stuff that doesn't kill you makes you weaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.49,0:01:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友的爷爷只是患了心脏病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My friend's grandfather had a heart attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.53,0:01:48.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在连喘气都要靠一台机器支撑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now he needs a machine to breathe.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.28,0:01:50.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见过他  就在超市里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've seen him- at the supermarket.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.20,0:01:53.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走到哪都得推着一台\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now he needs to drive one of those little, like-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.29,0:01:54.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你继续悲观教育吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's right. Be negative.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.82,0:01:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那幅画确实不怎么样  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just not a good poster, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.90,0:01:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的打击只会让我变得更坚强\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're only making me stronger.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.05,0:02:15.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂鸭子的面包带了吗  -带了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you pack the bread for the ducks? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.07,0:02:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要全麦的  鸭子不吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not the whole-wheat kind. The ducks don't like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.15,0:02:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  鸭子是不会介意的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're ducks, Mitchell. They don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.56,0:02:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We both believe that
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.50,0:02:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物在莉莉成长过程中是不可或缺的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}animals should play a big part in Lily's life.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.73,0:02:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在农场上长大  接触过很多动物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Having grown up on a farm, I was surrounded by them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.23,0:02:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们更像是我的兄弟姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They were more like brothers
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.47,0:02:27.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不仅仅是牲畜家禽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and sisters than just, you know, livestock.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.57,0:02:30.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多美味的兄弟姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Delicious brothers and sisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.28,0:02:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生在农场  它们深知以后的命运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Life on a farm- they know what they're getting into.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.62,0:02:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Eesh.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.15,0:02:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.19,0:02:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-公司打来的  -别接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, it's the office. -Don't answer it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.15,0:02:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须得接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.75,0:02:41.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周六都来这一套  别接了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like this every Saturday. Just ignore it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.77,0:02:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这次不是呢  喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, maybe it's not that this time. Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.65,0:02:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.24,0:02:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠..小壳  你还好吗  哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Holy- Shel? You all right, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.21,0:03:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.09,0:03:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一共4只小鸭子呢  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, there's four of 'em, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.30,0:03:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们在亲莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're giving her little duck kisses.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.30,0:03:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她笑得很开心  真遗憾你看不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, she's laughing. I can't believe you're missing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.51,0:03:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样  小卡  我错过的还少吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, why not, Cam? I've missed everything else.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.56,0:03:18.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她第一次翻身  我在凤凰城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She rolled over when I was in Phoenix.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.64,0:03:20.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她学会爬行时  我却在法庭上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She started scooting when I was in court.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.69,0:03:24.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他们你不去加班  你做的够多的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, just tell 'em you're not coming in. You do enough for 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.32,0:03:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这一点  你知道  我也知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you know that. I know that. You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.97,0:03:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我那个混蛋老板不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The only one who doesn't know that is my sucky boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.64,0:03:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是有史以来最混蛋的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's the suckiest suck of all time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.43,0:03:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他个可怜的贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a miserable son of a bitch who...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.73,0:03:41.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像听到了我刚才说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}may have heard everything I just said.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.11,0:03:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  亲爱的  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, honey. -Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.88,0:03:51.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候去见你的女性朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When are you getting together with your gal pal?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.59,0:03:52.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我正在等消息呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I was just checking on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.92,0:03:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还没给我发站内信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's supposed to send me a message.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.26,0:03:56.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你加了她的Facebook\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you're Facebook friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.32,0:04:00.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  她只是447个好友之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure am. She's one of my 447 friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.77,0:04:02.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都对我想入"菲菲"呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody wants a slice.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.85,0:04:04.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们恢复联系有多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How long have you two been in touch with each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.85,0:04:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她差不多一年前联系到的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, she tracked me down about a year ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.40,0:04:10.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  你什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? What's- What's that sound?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.03,0:04:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm. Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.78,0:04:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站内信终于来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Here she is right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"七点半  梦境餐厅见"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"How about we meet at Le Reve at 7:30?"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.37,0:04:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的约会真够"单纯"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That sounds innocent enough- I mean-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.41,0:04:25.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和前女友在一家适合幽会的法国餐厅喝酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}drinks with an ex-girlfriend at an intimate French restaurant.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.00,0:04:28.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你说的话正是我期盼从你口中听到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you're doing that thing when you say what I want you to say
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.30,0:04:29.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的语气好刻薄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your tone seems mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.82,0:04:33.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我猜猜啊  丹妮丝还没结婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me guess. Denise isn't married.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.47,0:04:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近才离的  这有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Recently divorced. What's the big deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.85,0:04:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了  菲尔  别太傻太天真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Phil. You can't be that naive.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.56,0:04:41.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  网上那些奔四的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, women in their 30s on the Internet are like-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.35,0:04:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,个个都是忍者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they're like ninjas.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.36,0:04:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换上黑色外套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They get into their little black outfits
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.61,0:04:45.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗地里当第三者插足别人的婚姻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and try and sneak their way into your marriage.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.62,0:04:47.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮丝不是那种人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not Denise.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.20,0:04:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  这都是她给我发的站内信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Read some of her messages.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.12,0:04:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看完就知道你想多了  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're gonna feel silly. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.04,0:04:54.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嗨  菲尔  最近怎么样啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Hey, Phil. How's it going?"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.22,0:04:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别乱加性感的勾引声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't add the sexy voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.13,0:04:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嗨  菲尔  过得怎么样"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Hi, Phil. How's it going?"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.79,0:05:00.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"得知你脖子不疼了  我很高兴"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"So glad to hear your neck is better."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.25,0:05:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真吃醋了  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you seriously jealous? - No,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.09,0:05:03.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都没吃醋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not jealous at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.59,0:05:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是比你更懂女人而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just happen to know women better than you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.99,0:05:07.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女人绝对对你存有非分之想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that woman wants a slice.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.55,0:05:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  为了证明你的想法是错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Just to prove how wrong you are,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.26,0:05:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算邀她来家里喝酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna invite her over here for drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.27,0:05:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无所谓  但愿她不介意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine with me. Just hope it's fine with Denise.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.10,0:05:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"哎呀菲尔  我整颗心都在梦境餐厅"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Gee, Phil, I really had my heart set on Le Reve."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.73,0:05:19.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你故意刻薄的声音可不会让我生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That voice doesn't bother me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.82,0:05:21.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而让我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kind of like it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.31,0:05:23.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有什么反常的举动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Has he been acting weird around you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.93,0:05:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我一上午都躲着他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. I've been avoiding him all morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.93,0:05:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你其实根本不知道他听没听见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you don't even know if he heard you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.17,0:05:29.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以叫你来帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why we're doing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.23,0:05:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到哪了  午餐时间只有半个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And where are you? I only have a half hour for lunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.35,0:05:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  帅哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, handsome.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.89,0:05:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上就是在这里碰见他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So this is where it happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.62,0:05:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关掉手机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just turn off the phone,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.97,0:05:40.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇下车窗  试试能不能听见我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}roll down the window and we'll see if you can hear me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.13,0:05:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请绕行  我们要重现骂人的过程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go around! We're re-creating a faux pas!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.43,0:05:47.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.49,0:05:49.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  能听见我说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Can you hear me now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.69,0:05:50.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以  但听不太清\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but just barely.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.68,0:05:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前骂的时候这么小声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is this how loud you were talking?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.35,0:05:53.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能比这个音量大一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It might have been a little bit louder.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.51,0:05:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时路上都是车  几乎得用喊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There was traffic. I almost had to shout.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.38,0:05:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 几乎得什么  -用喊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You almost had to what? - Shout.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.82,0:05:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-大点声  -用喊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Little bit louder now. - Shout.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.35,0:06:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再大点声  -用喊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Little bit louder now. - Shout!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.14,0:06:04.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了  小卡  我的工作要保不住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really, Cam? My job is at stake here, and-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.10,0:06:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  显然你一开始就听得清\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, who are we kidding? You can obviously hear me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.64,0:06:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我彻底完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so screwed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.44,0:06:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  曼尼  过来一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny? Manny, come here a second, pal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.11,0:06:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么事  -有个坏消息要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Huh? - I got some bad news, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.48,0:06:17.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么坏消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.64,0:06:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很难以启齿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, there's no easy way to say this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.88,0:06:22.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小壳·斯坦龟死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shel Turtlestein is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.31,0:06:25.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  怎么死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? How?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.00,0:06:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我正在看报纸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was down here reading the paper,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.44,0:06:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只听楼上你的房间一阵骚乱的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I heard this commotion up in your room.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.34,0:06:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出  出于本能反应  我跑上楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So- so naturally, I go running up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.93,0:06:34.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见一只脏兮兮的浣熊已经破窗而入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this mangy raccoon had busted through your screen.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.01,0:06:37.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它肯定是跳到了小壳的鱼缸旁边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He must have scampered up to where Shel was.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.39,0:06:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我进去的时候  那个坏家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By the time I walked in, he had-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.06,0:06:43.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正抓着小壳的脖子使劲甩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the little bastard had him by the neck and shaking him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.19,0:06:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎石被甩得到处都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gravel was flying everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.11,0:06:46.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它看见我一点都不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He didn't even flinch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.91,0:06:49.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得意地盯着我看  然后一下子就溜了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just stared at me with that smug look and then bolted.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.52,0:06:52.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真后悔没有早点上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If only I'd have got here earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.49,0:06:56.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看看小壳的尸体吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}May I see the body?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.53,0:06:57.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你真的要看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Baby, are you sure that's a good idea?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.91,0:06:59.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再痛苦我也必须面对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's something I have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.25,0:07:04.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-确实是它  -对不起  哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's him. - Sorry, pal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.54,0:07:05.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是完全说不通呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It just doesn't make any sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.65,0:07:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好龟不长命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yep. Only the good die young.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:09.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师说  浣熊只在夜间行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But in school, we learn raccoons are nocturnal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.53,0:07:10.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白天都在睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They sleep during the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.51,0:07:13.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  这一只可能是半夜起来找零食的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They sure do, and this one must've got up for a midnight snack.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.94,0:07:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们人也有类似的经历嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, we've all done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.05,0:07:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-应该是吧  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I guess so. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.60,0:07:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在都能说得通了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It all adds up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.66,0:07:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在无法待在这个房间  太多回忆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think I can be in here right now. Too many memories.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.68,0:07:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He'll be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.44,0:07:26.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你撒谎  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You lie. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.98,0:07:30.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哥伦比亚  骗局我见一个识破一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm Colombian. I know a fake crime scene when I see one.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.52,0:07:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时想把那幅画钉在墙上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was hanging up the new poster
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.25,0:07:35.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果它掉下来砸在小壳身上  纯属意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it fell on top of him. It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.86,0:07:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去跟他说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.79,0:07:38.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我有经验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I've been through this before.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.70,0:07:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔九岁的时候  他让我照看他的鸟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When Mitchell was nine, I was supposed to take care of his bird.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.78,0:07:43.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果它飞了出去  撞上了一台电扇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It got out and flew into a fan.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.53,0:07:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那场面就像血花四溅的枕头大战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was like a bloody pillow fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.42,0:07:47.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你到底杀过多少只宠物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My God. How many pets have you killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.01,0:07:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这两只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just the two.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.84,0:07:49.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不小心害死了那只鸟  是大错特错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I took the heat on the bird. It was a big mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.88,0:07:51.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到今天  米奇尔看我的眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To this day, Mitchell looks at me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.96,0:07:52.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都好像在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see him thinking,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.79,0:07:54.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"芙莱莎·米奈丽就是被这个人杀死的"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"That's the guy who killed Fliza Minnelli."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.01,0:07:56.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是曼尼发现了  你又要怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And what if he finds out? Then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.05,0:07:59.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候你不仅是宠物杀手  还是个骗子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'll be the guy that killed his pet and lied to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.72,0:08:02.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会发现的  我已经掩盖好自己的"行迹"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not gonna find out because I covered my tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.72,0:08:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.89,0:08:07.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芙莱莎·米奈丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fliza Minnelli?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.19,0:08:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时怎么就没发现他是同性恋呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did I not know that kid was gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.98,0:08:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.69,0:08:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是你的大日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Big day for you, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.95,0:08:15.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.57,0:08:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你终于可以见到你的亲妈了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Because you will get to meet your real mom. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.41,0:08:21.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来大家说好  等你21岁再告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We all made a pact we'd deny it until you turned 21.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.69,0:08:25.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是爸爸的前女友就是为这事来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's the real reason Dad's old girlfriend's coming over.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.75,0:08:26.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才是你亲妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's your mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.91,0:08:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是她喜欢你  你就得跟她生活了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and if she likes you, you'll go live with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.46,0:08:32.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是被领养的  我要去问妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not adopted. I'm asking Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.39,0:08:36.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说邓菲太太吗  她不会跟你说实话的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean Mrs. Dunphy? She's not going to tell you the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.91,0:08:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I'm not-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.90,0:08:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.93,0:08:47.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为他说你是呆家呆户的推销员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just 'cause he called you a dork-to-dork salesman?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.60,0:08:49.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐全力回击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The empire shakes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.63,0:08:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浣熊爪有5个指头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Raccoons have five toes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.89,0:08:53.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.24,0:08:54.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想来烦你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't mean to bother you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.61,0:08:56.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很疑惑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just confusing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.15,0:08:58.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我房间里浣熊的两只脚印都只有4个指头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The footprints in my room only have four toes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.39,0:09:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I bet I know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.91,0:09:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它肯定是在一场打斗中失去了两个指头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll bet he lost those toes in a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.95,0:09:06.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙看起来像是经过了几场打斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that guy looked like he'd been in a brawl or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.50,0:09:08.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-刚好一只爪失去一个指头  -有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- One toe from each foot? - Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.04,0:09:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  只有一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, Manny, I think the only thing...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.63,0:09:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让你不再问这样的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's gonna get you to stop asking all these questions...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.55,0:09:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  一个永久性的告别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is for you to have a little closure.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.55,0:09:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.22,0:09:19.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给小壳举办一场小型追悼会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well,I'd like to throw a little memorial for Shel.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.96,0:09:21.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那对我们大家都好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It'll be good for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.40,0:09:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就可以把悲痛发泄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That way we get our grief out,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.42,0:09:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后谁都不要再提这件事  永远不提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we never have to talk about this ever, ever again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  当心脚下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. Oh, careful. There's a thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.57,0:09:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到你真高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.57,0:09:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -嗨  我是克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi! Oh, my God. - Hi. I'm Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.74,0:09:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是  嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You must be- Oh. Yeah. Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.74,0:09:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-丹妮丝  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Denise. - Well- Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.74,0:09:48.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本人比菲尔上传的照片还要漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're even prettier than the pictures that Phil's always posting.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.04,0:09:50.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-只有几张  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just a couple. - Oh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.04,0:09:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞎说  每周都有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up. Every week.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.27,0:09:53.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢炫耀你的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He loves showing you off.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.46,0:09:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我男友喜欢你在阿卡普尔科照的那几张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And my boyfriend likes your Acapulco pictures,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.54,0:09:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢得我都有点吃醋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}probably a little too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.41,0:09:59.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我谢谢你男友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, thank your boyfriend for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.47,0:10:00.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快请进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on in, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.01,0:10:05.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带来一瓶祛皱紧致霜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I brought you, um, some lifting intensifier.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.10,0:10:07.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你用不上  不过这是限量版\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not that you need it. It's a limited edition,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.51,0:10:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  谢谢  -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thank you. Thank you. - Never mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.98,0:10:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮丝  给你介绍我的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Denise, I think you might know these people.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.35,0:10:12.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是海莉  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, that's Haley - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.90,0:10:15.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾丽克斯和  -卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Alex and- - Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.73,0:10:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的卷发和我小时候的一模一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had curly hair just like that when I was little.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.03,0:10:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样  说明不了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So? That doesn't mean anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.99,0:10:28.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都过来  请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't we, uh, come on in, have a seat. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.54,0:10:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸上高中时候是什么样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what was my dad like in high school?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.62,0:10:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的霹雳舞无人超越\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Only the most amazing break-dancer ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.46,0:10:36.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不可能  -别刺激我  你看  你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No way. - Oh, don't fire it up. What? What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.17,0:10:40.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他柜子里有一个大匣子和一块硬纸板\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He had a boom box and a piece of cardboard in his locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.63,0:10:42.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你那个舞叫什么名字  -O型区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And what was your dance name? - O-Zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.72,0:10:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开车送他去搜星节目试镜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I drove him to his Star Search audition.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.72,0:10:46.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便提一下  试镜就是走个形式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which is totally political, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.18,0:10:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,O型区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}O-Zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.60,0:10:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太搞笑了  我以后就叫你这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is dead-ass funny. I'm so calling you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.63,0:10:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.33,0:10:53.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太走运了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. You really lucked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.77,0:10:56.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美丽娇妻  豪华住房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have a beautiful wife, a gorgeous house.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.32,0:10:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一群孩子  我都想把卢克带回家去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And those kids- I could take Luke home with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.19,0:11:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用跟我客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, be my guest.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.19,0:11:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  赶紧把他带走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, you go right ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.66,0:11:06.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我喜欢这个家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! I like it here!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.33,0:11:11.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  宝贝  看看你弟弟怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, honey, will you go find out what's wrong with your brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.91,0:11:13.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.92,0:11:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话  我想去一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, um, if it's okay, I think I'm just gonna use the, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.59,0:11:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以  走廊尽头就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. Of course. Down the hall.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.59,0:11:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就在左手边  很容易找到  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Left-hand side. You can't miss it. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.93,0:11:26.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我承认她人很棒  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, she's fantastic. -Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.01,0:11:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我好愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. I feel awful.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.91,0:11:31.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候起  我变得这么刻薄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When did I become this horribly cynical person...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.17,0:11:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把别人都往坏处想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who assumes the worst about people?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.93,0:11:35.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实7年前我就发现...你才不是那种人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I first noticed it seven years- You're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.48,0:11:38.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太笨了  请问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Such an idiot. Is it-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.48,0:11:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我带你过去  没关系的  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, I'll show you. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Okay. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.70,0:11:46.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So how are we gonna do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.41,0:11:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为只要给你指一下门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought I'd just point at the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.62,0:11:51.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以我只想着  -我也是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So I was thinking - I was thinking too.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.58,0:11:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  是我酒店的房卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here... is my hotel room key.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.46,0:11:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时欢迎你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can come by whenever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.18,0:12:10.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上挺有意思的  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was funny this morning, huh-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.26,0:12:12.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红灯的时候我刚好停在你的车旁边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I pulled up next to you at that stoplight?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.44,0:12:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Funny?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.08,0:12:15.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  当时我正在和我老公打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Because I was on the phone with my partner...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.35,0:12:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈论他的上司多讨厌  他的上司\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}talking about how horrible his boss was- his.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.22,0:12:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你刚好停下  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then you pull up. So-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.36,0:12:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  很高兴路上碰见你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I'm glad I ran into you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.05,0:12:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心他们要把开庭日期提前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm getting worried they're gonna move up our court date.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.00,0:12:26.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你要全力做好准备\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need you to bust ass preparing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.15,0:12:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一旦周一叫我们去开庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause if they call us on Monday-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.95,0:12:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要现在看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, you need to get that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.74,0:12:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  没关系  只是一张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It's fine. It's just a...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.58,0:12:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿第一次站起来的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}picture of my daughter standing for the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.58,0:12:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以理解  确实值得庆祝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, they do that. It's a big day.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.34,0:12:38.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何  明天你还要来加班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I need you here tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.08,0:12:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道明天是周日  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it's a Sunday, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.60,0:12:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定会准时到的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, you think you can be on time, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.34,0:12:46.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  明天我有事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, um, I have plans tomorrow,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.80,0:12:48.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, so I won't be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.93,0:12:51.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算明天待在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I have plans to stay at home
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.70,0:12:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和家人一起  什么都不做  就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with my family and do absolutely nothing. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.98,0:12:57.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过周一我还是会来上班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I will see you on Monday.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.44,0:12:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是  这事你说了算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you're in charge now, is that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.52,0:13:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才意识到  既然我女儿都能站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just figure if my daughter can stand up,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.64,0:13:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也应该起身反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then so can I.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.57,0:13:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  最近大家加班都很辛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, look. We've all been working hard lately, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.24,0:13:08.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是工作性质决定的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.32,0:13:11.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天不来  你就永远不用来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So either come in tomorrow or don't bother coming back again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.04,0:13:15.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.84,0:13:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得用一下证件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Need the, uh, I.D. to
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.43,0:13:31.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘电梯下楼  奔向自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}make the elevator go down to freedom...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.60,0:13:34.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有咖啡  配合我的行头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and this to complete my set.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.27,0:13:43.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌龟  爬行动物  宠物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turtle, reptile, pet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.52,0:13:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小壳·斯坦龟不仅仅是一只乌龟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shel Turtlestein was many things.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.57,0:13:49.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说下去我就要哭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think I can do this without crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.57,0:13:51.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们直接跳到吃冷盘的环节吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe we should just get to the cold cuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.62,0:13:53.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想听完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we wanna hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.62,0:13:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  要不你去念吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, why don't you read it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.24,0:13:59.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你"送它上路"的  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were with him at the end. Remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.80,0:14:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"小壳·斯坦龟不仅仅是一只乌龟"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Shel Turtlestein was many things,"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.62,0:14:09.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"最重要的是  它是我的朋友"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"but above all, he was my friend."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.42,0:14:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"当菲奥娜·冈德森拒绝我的约会请求"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"When I didn't get a date with Fiona Gunderson,"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.75,0:14:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"有小壳的见证"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Shel was there."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.43,0:14:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"当我落选特维的角色"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"When I didn't get to play the part of Tevye,"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.51,0:14:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"有小壳的见证"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Shel was there."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.10,0:14:19.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"而当一只浣熊闯入我的房间"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"And when a raccoon broke into my room,"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.15,0:14:21.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不幸的是  小壳也在"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"unfortunately, Shel was there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.65,0:14:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"跟这位朋友  我说过很多话"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I said a lot of things to my friend,"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.65,0:14:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"但最终却来不及跟它说一句再见"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"but the one thing I never got to say was good-bye."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.19,0:14:29.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  我知道它是怎么死的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop. I know what really happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.86,0:14:32.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -我床边上有一包薯条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You do? - I left a bag of chips near my bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.20,0:14:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浣熊肯定是闻到味了  是我害死了小壳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The raccoon must have smelled it. It's my fault he's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.62,0:14:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  小壳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, Shel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.12,0:14:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  有什么话要跟曼尼说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you don't have anything to say to Manny?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.04,0:14:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.84,0:14:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.04,0:14:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小壳不会怪你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shel forgives you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.14,0:14:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.35,0:15:01.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Denise.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.85,0:15:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些照片太棒了  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These pictures are amazing. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.22,0:15:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你还是卷发呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, that perm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.11,0:15:09.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确切地说是杰里卷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Technically, that's a Jheri curl.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.40,0:15:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特喜欢照相  今天还给自己照了一张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just love to take pictures. I took this one of myself today.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.62,0:15:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  我去开一瓶红酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I'm gonna open a bottle of wine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.37,0:15:20.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  千万不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No. That's the worst idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.79,0:15:23.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开  我没那个心情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. I'm not in the mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.37,0:15:25.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是怎么了  像个狼孩一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What am I, raised by a pack of wolves?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.50,0:15:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Come on now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.25,0:15:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.34,0:15:31.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对丹妮丝的判断也不是一点道理没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You weren't completely wrong about Denise.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.59,0:15:33.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么这么说  -她想要我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How's that? - She wants me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.22,0:15:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干什么  -那个  干她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- To do what? - It. Her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.34,0:15:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说Facebook上的女人不正经\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Oh, this is because of the thing I said about Facebook...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.68,0:15:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在上面约炮  所以你失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and everybody's hooking up, and now you're disappointed.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.93,0:15:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  她对着我大口咬空气  像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. She bit the air right in front of me. Like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.48,0:15:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你看她塞给我一个什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then look what she tried to give me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.52,0:15:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-需要我帮忙吗  -不用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Anything I can help with? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.57,0:15:51.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到开瓶器了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just- I can't find my corkscrew.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.36,0:15:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-摸我  -好了  丹妮丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Touch me. - Okay. Denise,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.62,0:15:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是有什么地方让你误会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think somewhere along the line you got the wrong idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.32,0:15:59.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脑袋里充满想入"菲菲"的误会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My head is full of wrong ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.28,0:16:03.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的品味真不赖  克莱尔  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You have such great taste, Claire. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.20,0:16:06.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔当年也是很有品"味"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I remember Phil used to have really good taste too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.21,0:16:08.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我用点洗手液  -找到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let me get a little of this. - Oh, here it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.21,0:16:09.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  拿几个杯子过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, would you mind grabbing us a couple glasses?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.80,0:16:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You betcha.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.26,0:16:12.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要我帮忙"抓"什么吗  -不用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Need me to grab anything? - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.63,0:16:15.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这样太离谱了  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, this is so wrong. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.30,0:16:17.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有她在更刺激不是吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's way more exciting when she's in the room, isn't it? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.51,0:16:19.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还留着拉拉队队长的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I still have my cheerleader outfit.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.28,0:16:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.92,0:16:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是不能这样  那个怎么碎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But this still can't happen. When did that break?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.98,0:16:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么退却了  -我根本没想乱来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why are you wussing out? - I never wussed in.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.52,0:16:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你在Facebook上写那些是为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What about all those things you wrote on Facebook?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.61,0:16:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你还好吗  我脖子好疼"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"How was your day? My neck is so sore."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.02,0:16:33.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么大家都要把留言说的那么下流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do people keep adding voices to these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.01,0:16:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没别的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't mean anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.99,0:16:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说  我在这段关系上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you telling me that I wasted a year
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.75,0:16:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪费了一年时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of my life on this relationship?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.32,0:16:38.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What relationship?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.58,0:16:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有多少女人被你勾引了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How many other women have you led on?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.34,0:16:41.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  我怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.51,0:16:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.58,0:16:47.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.92,0:16:50.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记不记得  我们第一次约会的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you remember when you broke your arm
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.57,0:16:52.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胳膊受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when we were first dating?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.09,0:16:54.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得  我在冰上摔倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, uh, when I slipped on the ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.09,0:16:56.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  奇怪了  这张照片里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right. That's so weird. Because in this picture,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.34,0:16:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带着受伤的胳膊坐在丹妮丝旁边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're sitting with Denise and you have a broken arm, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.30,0:17:01.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是挺奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that's- that's weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.39,0:17:04.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你和我约会的时候和她还没断呢  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So you were still dating her when you started dating me? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.52,0:17:06.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  -可能是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil? - Yeah. Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.31,0:17:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有段时间  我横跨两条船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There was a time, a little overlap...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.29,0:17:10.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时  我打算和丹妮丝分手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when, uh, I was trying to break things off with Denise.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.76,0:17:12.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你还带我去圣达菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You took me to Santa Fe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.40,0:17:16.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣达菲  你当时说是带你爸爸去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Santa Fe? Phil, you told me that was your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.11,0:17:19.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们很"新疼"  但其实都是旧伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I know the pain is fresh, but the lie is really old.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.45,0:17:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来就是个错误  我走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, this was a mistake. I'm gonna leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.62,0:17:25.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  我要是你  就把他踢出家门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, if I were you, I would kick him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.41,0:17:26.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他会更加感激你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe he'd appreciate you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.63,0:17:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他尝到孤身一人在酒店过夜的滋味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}more after he spent a lonely night in a hotel.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.96,0:17:31.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在机场旁的雷迪森酒店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At the Radisson, by the airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.84,0:17:36.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你辞职了  -感觉太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You quit? - It was amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.30,0:17:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你眼前的是一个全新的我  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. This is the new me, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.01,0:17:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不会让别人主宰我的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not letting people run my life anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.72,0:17:43.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该紧张才对  但我反而为你激动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should be nervous, but I'm not. I'm excited for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.26,0:17:45.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  这太令人激动了  太激动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes! It's exciting! It's exciting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听从了自己内心的想法  值得庆祝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you followed your heart, and that is worth celebrating.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.69,0:17:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  我觉得自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, I just feel-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.65,0:17:53.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻底解放了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so liberated.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.12,0:17:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会去捡起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm not picking it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.61,0:17:58.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我喜欢你这样  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I like this guy. - I do too.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.86,0:18:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我们以后要节俭一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, we'll have to cut back a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.16,0:18:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这值得  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But isn't it worth it if you feel
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.40,0:18:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次为自己而活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like you're living your life for the first time?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.33,0:18:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太值得了  -那我们还等什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Totally. - What were we even waiting for?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.29,0:18:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你重操旧业  当音乐老师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You will go back to teaching music,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我休息几个月  再找一份工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then I'll just find something in a... few months.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.92,0:18:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前  我们只管坐下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And until then, all we need to do is just sit back...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.50,0:18:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我们的小千金快乐成长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and watch this little miracle here dazzle us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.59,0:18:19.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我好激动  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm tingling. - I am too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.09,0:18:22.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心似乎从没这么充实过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like my heart is full for the first time in forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.18,0:18:23.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  心跳得好快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God, it's really pounding.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.14,0:18:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能感受到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like I feel the weight of
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.94,0:18:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的胸口充满了一切可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}endless possibilities just sitting on my chest-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.39,0:18:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她什么表现都没有  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She is not doing anything, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.62,0:18:30.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是慌乱了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not panicking, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.79,0:18:32.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我当然慌乱了  -你别慌乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Of course I am panicking. - No. Don't panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.39,0:18:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一乱  我也乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you panic, I panic!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.30,0:18:35.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚辞职了  小卡  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just quit my job. Cam! My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.17,0:18:37.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我过惯了好日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, I am used to nice things.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.34,0:18:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后要怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.59,0:18:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别慌  镇定下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. No, no. Just calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.01,0:18:40.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来规划一下该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.76,0:18:43.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要  我要用我的看家本领\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am going to- I'm gonna do what I'm trained to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.25,0:18:44.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为达目的不惜说谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am going to lie, grovel, debase myself
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.84,0:18:46.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卑躬屈膝  自我贬低\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until I get what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.43,0:18:47.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是律师  妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am a lawyer, damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.73,0:18:48.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.29,0:18:51.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.40,0:18:52.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提醒的好  忘了打领带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, you're right. The tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.98,0:18:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我们一定能找到更合适你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. We'll find something better for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.11,0:18:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且对大家都好的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}something that works for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.11,0:18:59.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有备用方案的  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's no Plan "B" here, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.36,0:19:03.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要还房贷  还要养个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have a mortgage. We have- We have a child to support.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.66,0:19:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, it's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.79,0:19:07.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们肯定有办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.96,0:19:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望你开心  你一定会开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just want you to be happy, and you will be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.67,0:19:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是值得庆祝的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that is something worth toasting.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.59,0:19:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝那个便宜的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's just drink the cheap stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.09,0:19:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那瓶贵的我们转手卖掉吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause we might have to sell that bottle.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.95,0:19:26.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说谎太多容易失眠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's hard to sleep in a bed of lies.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.18,0:19:28.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不对  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Isn't it, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.13,0:19:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩记性很差\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids get over these things pretty quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.63,0:19:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准他现在像婴儿一样熟睡呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's probably sleeping like a baby right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.81,0:19:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定是清醒着的  满心愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure he's wide awake, full of guilt.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.02,0:19:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我要睡觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm going to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.41,0:19:48.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.92,0:19:54.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.96,0:19:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么不睡  -我在等待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What are you doing up? - Waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.96,0:19:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Waiting for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.23,0:20:02.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等真相  浣熊不是凶手  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The truth. It wasn't a raccoon, was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.09,0:20:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  被你发现了  是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, all right. You got me. I killed Shel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.31,0:20:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了吧  对不起  我不是故意的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right? I'm sorry. It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.68,0:20:09.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当时为什么不说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why didn't you just tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.14,0:20:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想惹你生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I didn't want you to be upset with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.56,0:20:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一开始关系很僵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You and I got off to a rocky start.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.15,0:20:15.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近  好不容易相处融洽了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lately, it's been pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.58,0:20:17.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕毁了这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was afraid I'd mess all that up
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.99,0:20:19.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不想让你知道是我杀死了你的宠物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if you knew that I was the one that killed your pet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.97,0:20:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你现在不仅杀了我的宠物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now you're the guy who killed my pet
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.47,0:20:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还编了个愚蠢的谎言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and made a stupid lie about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.87,0:20:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不觉得那是个愚蠢的谎言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't think it was stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.87,0:20:25.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为挺聪明的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought it was pretty clever.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.65,0:20:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想重蹈覆辙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just trying to avoid past mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.77,0:20:31.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.61,0:20:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我现在无法弥补对你造成的伤害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I can't make things all better right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.44,0:20:36.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我相信以后会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but maybe over time.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.14,0:20:37.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.17,0:20:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好睡吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get some rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.95,0:20:42.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你已经坦白了  我也该坦白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Since we're confessing things,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.41,0:20:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得你车上的抓痕吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know that scratch on your car?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.46,0:20:46.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一直擦不掉的那个  记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The one that can't be buffed out? Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.34,0:20:48.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该猜得到是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should probably know how it happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.21,0:20:49.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know how it happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.59,0:20:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是浣熊干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Raccoon did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.14,0:20:56.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-晚安  杰  -晚安  小家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Good night, Jay. -Good night, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.43,0:21:00.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最大的成就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Best thing I ever did
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.70,0:21:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是辞了份烂工作  自己创业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was quit a miserable job and start my own business.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.03,0:21:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢老爸  -不过自己创业也不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks, Dad. - No, it's not gonna be easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.98,0:21:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我和歌洛莉亚来送你个东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why Gloria and I wanna give you a little something
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.35,0:21:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你渡过难关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to help you through it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.64,0:21:10.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  我不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Dad, I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.19,0:21:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要给你  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I want to, Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.82,0:21:15.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辞职之后  我特别想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, but, I mean, as soon as I'm back on my feet, I really want to-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.32,0:21:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  不要  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Oh, Dad. No. You-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.53,0:21:21.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20年前我的宠物蛇死了  你就想给我这个的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You tried to give me this 20 years ago when my pet snake died.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.54,0:21:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I did? -Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.37,0:21:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-叫扎扎·戈波娃  -这名字真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Zsa Zsa Gaboa? - Oh, that's adorable.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.90,0:21:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当时真不知道他是同性恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you really didn't know that he was gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.71,0:21:30.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该知道的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I must've, right?

