[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.54,0:01:36.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.54,0:01:36.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.54,0:01:36.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第九集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.90,0:00:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有消息了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do we know anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.28,0:00:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  医生正在里面诊断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. They're in there now with the doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.59,0:00:08.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过已经是万幸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're lucky though.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.36,0:00:10.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急救员说完全有可能比现在的情况严重的多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The paramedics said it could have been a lot worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.57,0:00:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  怎么会发生这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My God, how did this even happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.10,0:00:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b0\pos(186,234)}几   天   前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.74,0:00:17.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子来了  大日子快到了哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There he is. Big day's coming up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.82,0:00:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生日想要什么样的礼物  小狗娃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you want for your birthday, big dog?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.02,0:00:20.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  我不想要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's okay. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.54,0:00:23.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来嘛  除了上天什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Sky's the limit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.33,0:00:25.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狮子大开口吧  儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dream big, my boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.42,0:00:28.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得送我一条皮带挺好的  -皮带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, I guess I could use a belt. - A belt?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.08,0:00:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你说的对  我根本不需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, you're right. I don't need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.46,0:00:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天线延长线用着也挺顺手的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Extension cord works pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.47,0:00:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年卢克的生日都在感恩节附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every year, Luke's birthday falls right around Thanksgiving,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.96,0:00:39.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以大家都忙着准备过节了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and so it gets lost in the holiday shuffle.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.06,0:00:41.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一年我们彻底忘到九霄云外了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One year we forgot completely,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:43.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只好用火鸡填料临时做了个蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we had to improvise a cake of stuffing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.28,0:00:44.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说一下  他一点都不介意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which, by the way, he was fine with.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.65,0:00:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是那种古怪孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's one of those kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.25,0:00:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你送他一份礼物  他却只想着玩盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you get him a gift and all he wants to do is play with the box.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.59,0:00:49.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  有一年我们直接送他一个盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, one year we actually just got him a box,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.78,0:00:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个非常漂亮的盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a really nice box.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.21,0:00:54.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们犯了个错  将之放进了礼品袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we made the mistake of putting it in a gift bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.28,0:00:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他就玩起了礼品袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So he played with the gift bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:00:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们怎么都做不对  -做不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We can't get it right. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.02,0:01:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得很愧疚  我们得做点什么  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I feel terrible. We gotta do something. - Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.73,0:01:04.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  家人们准备趁感恩节来个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, the family is gonna be together for Thanksgiving...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.41,0:01:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大团圆聚会  我不知道会持续多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for the first time in I don't even know how long.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.41,0:01:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太同意你了  我们应该取消聚会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so with you. We should blow this out...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.86,0:01:10.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给卢克办一个有史以来最棒的生日派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and throw Luke the best birthday party of all time.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.08,0:01:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  对  我们可以订购许多匹萨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Yes. And we'll order a whole bunch of pizzas...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.46,0:01:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设立一个手工艺品桌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and set up an arts and crafts table.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.46,0:01:16.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -手工艺品桌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- A what? - A crafts table.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.15,0:01:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  大家都围在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, where everybody gathers around
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.94,0:01:19.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作一些小工艺品  然后  砰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they make stuff, and then bam!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.80,0:01:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就发现了自己最爱的派对项目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They got their own party favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.12,0:01:22.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry. I fell asleep
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.13,0:01:24.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的简直是史上最无聊的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}while you were describing the most boring party ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.70,0:01:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-几小时后再见了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- See you in a few hours. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.35,0:01:43.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次谢谢你们借我卡拉OK唱机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks again for the karaoke machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.87,0:01:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派对办完后  我会立刻送过来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll get it back to you right after the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.29,0:01:46.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再好不过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That'd be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.60,0:01:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万不要  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please don't. I beg you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.09,0:01:49.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-千万别送回来  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't bring it back. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.56,0:01:52.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  菲尔  你今天的派对有请小丑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Phil. Are, uh, you getting a clown for today?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.08,0:01:56.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  卢克不怎么喜欢小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. Luke's not much of a clown fan.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.80,0:01:58.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -是啊  他从来不喜欢小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - Yeah. He never liked 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.51,0:02:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有见过出色的小丑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Has he ever seen a good one?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.44,0:02:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁  见过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Has- Has anyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.98,0:02:04.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  总之  谢谢你们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really. So anyway, thanks again.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.74,0:02:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  一会儿见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.81,0:02:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要小丑  不要小丑吗  -算了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No clown? No- No clown? - Let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.81,0:02:12.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁家开派对不请小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who throws a party without a clown?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.02,0:02:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从上世纪30年代开始  大部分人都不请了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Since the late '30s, I'd say most people.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.23,0:02:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  我们还没给卢克准备生日礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? We haven't gotten Luke a present yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.82,0:02:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许扮小丑可以当生日礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe a clown could be our present.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:20.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron. Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.28,0:02:22.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果菲尔和克莱尔想给卢克请个小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If Phil and Claire wanted to get Luke a clown,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.24,0:02:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯定已经请了  那不是我们的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they would've. This is not our party.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.11,0:02:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但  -那不是我们家开派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But- - this is not our party.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.33,0:02:28.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我刚刚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.28,0:02:29.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.48,0:02:31.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说我们送他什么礼物好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What would you suggest we get him then, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.70,0:02:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送他一张礼物卡就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get him a gift card.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.92,0:02:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就礼物卡打发他吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- A gift card? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.42,0:02:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被谁摧残过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who hurt you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.79,0:02:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Gloria,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.61,0:02:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道怎么包装这玩意儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you got any idea how to wrap one of these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.80,0:02:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是个十字弓吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is that a crossbow? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.48,0:02:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是堪称世上最好的外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I the greatest grandpa in the world or what?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.72,0:02:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能送十字弓给卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can't give Luke a crossbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.72,0:02:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他每次用吸管都能戳到眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He pokes himself in the eye every time he uses a straw.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.85,0:02:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  我像他那么大的时候就有一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding? I had one when I was his age.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.94,0:02:58.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每射杀一只乌鸦  我爸就会给我25美分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad used to give me a quarter for every crow I bagged.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.23,0:02:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经还有大砍刀呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I used to have a machete.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.88,0:03:01.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但时代已经变了  -他会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But times have changed. - He'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.79,0:03:03.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会教他怎么用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll teach him how to use it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.78,0:03:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老弟  过得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, pal, how's it going?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.25,0:03:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有魅力吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I charming?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.14,0:03:08.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-靠  -你当然有魅力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, boy. - Of course you're charming.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.16,0:03:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁说你没魅力了  -没人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who said you were not charming? - No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.29,0:03:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校里有个妹子挺好  我想让她喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But there's a girl in my school, and I want her to like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.83,0:03:15.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我需要你的建议  杰  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I need your advice, Jay. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.54,0:03:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会去参加卢克的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's gonna be at Luke's party.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.56,0:03:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是  有点受宠若惊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm a little thrown.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.30,0:03:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  你一般不会向我征询建议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, you don't usually come to me for advice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.52,0:03:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在泡美妞这方面  您老可算个中高手啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, this is one area in which you've done pretty well.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说的很对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He has a point.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.01,0:03:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过用各种方法吸引她的注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've tried everything to get her attention-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为她开门  在餐厅为她递上一杯牛奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}opening doors, having a milk sent over in the cafeteria.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.18,0:03:35.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-全都不奏效  -事实上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing's worked. - Here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.18,0:03:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子不吃浪漫那一套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Girls don't go for all that romantic stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.48,0:03:39.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们喜欢有权势的或成功的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They go for power and success.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.48,0:03:41.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这两样你都不沾边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And since you don't have either one of those things,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.73,0:03:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就得做个风趣幽默的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're gonna be the funny guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.53,0:03:48.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  我想要你养的最危险的爬虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. I want the most dangerous reptile you've got.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.24,0:03:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一只吃蟋蟀的鼠鳞蜥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have an iguana that eats crickets.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.49,0:03:53.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是给蟋蟀办生日派对  那才算吓人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That'd be scary if it was a birthday party for crickets.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.58,0:03:55.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  丛林女郎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, Jungle Tanya,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.34,0:03:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你升级一下恐怖程度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need you step it up a notch.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.87,0:03:58.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有什么东西能把你自己吓个半死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there anything that scares the cocoa out of you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.04,0:04:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真没有  不过我有条"胡须龙"[一种蜥蜴]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, not really. I do have a bearded dragon.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.30,0:04:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  它会..  -不  它不会喷火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ooh. Does it- - No, it does not breathe fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.21,0:04:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说来说去又说回去了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then we're back to square one, aren't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.68,0:04:12.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脑子里一直想着卢克的生日会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I couldn't get Luke out of my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.60,0:04:14.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我向米奇尔保证过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I made a promise to Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.97,0:04:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有些东西比"保证"二字要重要的多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but some things are bigger than promises.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.35,0:04:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲茨宝一定要在派对上华丽登场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fizbo would be at that party.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.01,0:04:28.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  老朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, old friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.87,0:04:35.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都发生在眨眼之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It all happened so fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.42,0:04:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I keep thinking
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.04,0:04:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时做点什么阻止这一切就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}there was something I could've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.16,0:04:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不要自责\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, don't blame yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.83,0:04:40.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能想到会发生这种事呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who could've possibly seen it coming?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.63,0:04:43.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  那是道攀岩墙  那安全吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, that's a rock wall. Is that even safe?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.63,0:04:43.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b0\pos(186,234)}当天早些时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.84,0:04:45.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老天啊  -亲爱的  放心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God. - Honey, relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.01,0:04:48.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  有人因为这东西受过伤吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, has anyone ever gotten hurt on one of these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.88,0:04:50.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道  今天是我第一天上班  -瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't know, man. It's my first day. - See?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.89,0:04:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯让新人操作肯定说明没有...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They wouldn't let the new guy do it if it-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.80,0:04:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那只会让我更加担心  -别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That did not make me feel better. - Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.72,0:04:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我签了一堆的责任声明书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I signed, like, a hundred releases.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.81,0:05:00.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们什么时候决定弄这些的  太过了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When did we decide all this? I think it's too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.27,0:05:01.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  我就知道你会这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, I knew you'd say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.52,0:05:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就没告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why I didn't tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.56,0:05:04.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就放轻松  去吃个冰霜卷吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So just relax. Grab a snow cone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.57,0:05:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你弄来了冰霜卷机器吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There's a snow cone machine? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.86,0:05:09.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  记住  迪兰不能吃蛋黄酱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, just so you know, Dylan cannot have mayonnaise.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.69,0:05:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没头没脑来这么一句  你干嘛告诉我这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's random. Why are you telling me that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.82,0:05:14.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为他要来参加派对  -有那个必要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 'Cause he's coming to the party. - Is that absolutely necessary?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.58,0:05:15.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  因为她忍受不了10分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, because she can't go 10
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.69,0:05:17.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有她男友的舌头在她嘴里搅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}minutes without her boyfriend's tongue in her mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.87,0:05:19.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像他在喂幼鸟一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like he's feeding a baby bird.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.85,0:05:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别羡慕嫉妒恨了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't be so jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.25,0:05:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确定你在计算机夏令营会遇到超级大帅哥的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure you'll meet someone super hot at computer camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:25.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-姑娘们  -嘿  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Girls. - Hey. Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.92,0:05:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手上拿的什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what you got there?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.11,0:05:28.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是手工艺品桌需要的一些原材料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These are supplies for the crafts table.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.67,0:05:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于想到我们要做什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I finally figured out what we're gonna be making.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.68,0:05:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让孩子们无聊吗  -我开玩笑的  玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Kids bored? - I'm teasing. I'm teasing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.76,0:05:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去挺不错  是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It looks good. What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.03,0:05:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梳套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Comb sheaths.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.86,0:05:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.10,0:05:40.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是11岁的时候做的这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we made them when I was 11 years old
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.60,0:05:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在唐娜·瑞格比的生日派对上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at Donna Rigby's birthday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.19,0:05:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始我们也觉得那很傻帽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At first we thought it was really stupid,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.49,0:05:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们觉得那是很愉快的经历\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we had a blast, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.35,0:05:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能不愉快呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could you not?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.00,0:05:48.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把孩子们最爱的两样东西结合到了一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You combined the two things that kids love the most-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.69,0:05:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梳子和套子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}combs and sheaths.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.90,0:05:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.45,0:05:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的梳子哪儿去了  噢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's my comb? Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.45,0:05:59.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来在我超级方便的绣珠梳套里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here it is in my incredibly convenient beaded comb sheath...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.12,0:06:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是我在卢克超棒的生日派对上做的哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I made at Luke's awesome birthday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.75,0:06:03.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一举夺魁  邓菲太太\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hole in one, Mrs. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.79,0:06:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一举夺魁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hole in one.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.17,0:06:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm home.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.09,0:06:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给卢克买了一套游戏盘  但是关于数学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got Luke a video game, but it's about math.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.63,0:06:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我们估计是那种督促人学习的讨厌舅舅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I guess we're those kind of uncles.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.93,0:06:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.22,0:06:21.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't be mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.69,0:06:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢   小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Cam. Uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.48,0:06:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立志想当小丑是从\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've known I wanted to be a clown...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.92,0:06:29.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现小丑不过是人化妆扮成的开始的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}since I found out clowns were just people with makeup.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.48,0:06:32.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  当我成长为小少年的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, as a matter of fact, by the time I was a teenager,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.28,0:06:35.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我不是在上学或钓鱼  就是在扮小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I wasn't in school or fishin', I was clownin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.45,0:06:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总共有4种类型的小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There are four types of clowns
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.96,0:06:38.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乞丐小丑  彩面小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a tramp, an Auguste,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.76,0:06:40.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白脸小丑  和角色小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a whiteface and a character.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.50,0:06:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个接受过传统训练的彩面小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am a classically trained Auguste clown
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.26,0:06:43.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名叫菲茨宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}named Fizbo.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.00,0:06:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? N-Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.13,0:06:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又要扮小丑又要钓鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Between the clownin' and the fishin',
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.13,0:06:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真奇怪你竟然还有时间上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm surprised you had time for the schoolin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.80,0:06:54.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有第5种类型的  悲伤小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aw, and there's the fifth type- the sad clown.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.09,0:06:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲伤小丑也属于乞丐小丑  所以仍然只有4种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sad clown is a tramp. So there's still only four types.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.02,0:07:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  我觉得我们已经说过这事儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, I thought we discussed this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.02,0:07:06.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但我后来一想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We did. But I- I started thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.19,0:07:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事的重点不在你我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this isn't about you or me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.80,0:07:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是一个小男孩  该享受快乐一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is about a little boy who deserves some happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.73,0:07:13.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能从他古怪的同性恋舅夫那儿得到快乐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he's gonna get that from his weird gay clown uncle?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.03,0:07:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲茨宝才不是同性恋  他是无性的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fizbo is not gay. He's asexual.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.96,0:07:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个纯情大男孩  唯一的目标\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's an innocent whose only drive...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.87,0:07:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是给人们带去喜庆  欢笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is to bring people joy and laughter
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.13,0:07:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和气球扎成的动物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and balloon animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.04,0:07:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他  他是地球上最与性无关的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's- He's the least sexual being on earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.85,0:07:26.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  至少我们都认为你这装扮让人性趣全无\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, okay. Well, at least we agree on something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.63,0:07:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果未来有人发现这盘带子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If this tape is found in the future,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.34,0:07:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这就是我们人类庆祝生日的方式  -老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- this is how we humans celebrated birthdays. - Hey, Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.19,0:07:43.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  那是我的乖儿子  高空滑索\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, there's my boy. Zip-line extreme-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.89,0:07:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  我没事  我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm okay. I'm good. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.48,0:07:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃一撞长一智  千万别站在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lesson learned. Don't stand- Don't stand there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.23,0:07:52.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这一块儿用绳子圈起来禁止入内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go ahead and rope this area off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.13,0:07:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  谢谢你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excellent. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.46,0:07:56.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小老弟  玩得开心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy, you having fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.95,0:07:58.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  而且我爱我的新皮带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. And I love my new belt.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.45,0:08:00.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  卢克  瞧啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Luke. Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.80,0:08:02.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做个梳套吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you wanna make a comb sheath?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.54,0:08:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A what?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.22,0:08:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一个皮质小套  可以放梳子进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a cool leather holder for your comb.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.75,0:08:06.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以装饰一下它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you can decorate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.86,0:08:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边有小珠子  小亮片等各种东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've got beads and glitter and all kinds of stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.75,0:08:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想试试吗  -不  我去玩攀岩墙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you want to? - Nah. I'm gonna do the rock wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.42,0:08:17.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧宝贝  你的生日你做主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, honey. It's your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.55,0:08:19.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  如果你材料不够了  记得通知我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, let me know if you get low on supplies.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.55,0:08:22.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会迅速穿越到1950年代帮你买回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll make a quick run back to the 1950s for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.39,0:08:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  又撞我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Again?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.97,0:08:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  负责滑索的人  用绳子圈一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, zip-line guys, use some ropes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.50,0:08:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得把白色衣服放进烘干机了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you remember to switch the whites to the dryer?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.44,0:08:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  我忘了  -到时肯定一股霉味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no. I forgot. - They're gonna smell musty.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.90,0:08:36.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  我很抱歉  -我来加油吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know. I'm sorry. - I'll pump.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.15,0:08:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  我来吧  你坐在车里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. I'll do it. You stay right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.74,0:08:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放轻松  -哦  我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Relax. - Oh. I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.74,0:08:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你担心别人看见我  -毫无疑问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're worried about people seeing me. - Without question.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.95,0:08:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们会盯着我们看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, people are gonna stare.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.40,0:08:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们很少见一个小丑在车里的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're not used to seeing one clown in a car.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.33,0:08:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是她  比安卡·道格拉斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's her- Bianca Douglas.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.42,0:08:53.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好可爱哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's so cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.83,0:08:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她写得一手好字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She has good handwriting.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.63,0:08:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个完美女神  祝我好运吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's a complete package. Wish me luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.13,0:08:59.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要运气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't need luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.26,0:09:02.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要记住我传授给你的那些笑话就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just remember those jokes I told you, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.31,0:09:07.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能再这么见面了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have to stop meeting like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.39,0:09:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我们是同学啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - We go to school together.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.77,0:09:11.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-噢是哦  -你喜欢笑话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, yeah. - Do you like jokes?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.98,0:09:13.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然  -很好  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sure. - Great. Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.98,0:09:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只叫加里的蚂蚱进了一家酒吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So a grasshopper named Gary walks into a bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.37,0:09:17.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aw. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.65,0:09:19.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不该一开始就把名字说出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not supposed to know his name.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.03,0:09:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我换一个讲吧  可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me try another one, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.24,0:09:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-敲敲门  -你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.24,0:09:28.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[曼尼本该在女孩说Who前先说Moo\N笑点是Who和Moo的英文发音相似]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.41,0:09:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-捣蛋牛  -捣蛋牛谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Interrupting cow. - Interrupting cow who?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.49,0:09:27.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哞  糟糕说晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Moo. Oh, crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.30,0:09:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-搞什么  -搞你个大头鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Um, hey. - Hey yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.49,0:09:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让开  -你刚开车碰到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Move. - You kind of just bumped me with your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.30,0:09:43.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.35,0:09:45.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你确实碰到了  因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, you did, because, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.18,0:09:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  我的裤子上沾了油迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, yeah, I got grease on my pants
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.96,0:09:49.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-而且我明显感觉被碰到  -叫救护车吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and then also I felt it. - Call an ambulance.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.43,0:09:51.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我只是觉得你可能有心知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I just thought you might wanna know...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.35,0:09:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你还想当个懂礼貌的人  道个歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in case you wanted to be a decent human being and apologize, but-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.96,0:09:56.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想吗  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.86,0:09:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.74,0:10:01.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.54,0:10:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just forget about it, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.41,0:10:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听着  红毛鬼  我没碰到你  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Listen, carrottop. I didn't touch you. - Um, I-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.37,0:10:10.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你给我放聪明点  闭上你的臭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So do the smart thing. Shut your hole,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.39,0:10:12.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚上车  开远点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}get in your car and drive away.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.12,0:10:13.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there a problem here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.48,0:10:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么鬼东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.50,0:10:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个惩恶扬善的小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm the ass-kicking clown...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.81,0:10:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把你拧成像气球动物那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that'll twist you like a balloon animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.80,0:10:20.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以拿你的脑袋猛撞保险杠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will beat your head against this bumper
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.46,0:10:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到气囊弹开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until the air bags deploy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.09,0:10:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻  向我男友  道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So apologize to my boyfriend right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.68,0:10:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-道歉  男友  -道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Apologize? Boyfriend? - Apologize!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.10,0:10:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.94,0:10:31.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.25,0:10:37.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  要迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go. We're gonna be late.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.91,0:10:50.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介意我也进来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mind if I come in?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.12,0:10:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.91,0:10:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.92,0:10:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么蹦得那么不开心  -我说尽了笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why you bounce so sad? - I told all my jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.25,0:11:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实证明我不是搞笑男\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It turns out I'm not the funny guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.93,0:11:05.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时候到了  真命天女自然会降临\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The right girl will find you when it's time,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.20,0:11:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管把你交给另外一个女人会让我很失落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}even though I'm gonna hate losing you to another woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.10,0:11:09.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会娶了媳妇忘了娘的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'll never lose me, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.91,0:11:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会永远爱你的  无论发生任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll always love you, no matter what.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.81,0:11:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀真乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, chiquitn.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.27,0:11:16.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  刚刚说的多好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You see? Right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.32,0:11:18.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不需要什么泡妞技巧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You need no tricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.11,0:11:21.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要表现出贴心可爱的  真实的你就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just be the sweet, wonderful little boy that you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.28,0:11:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的小男孩  懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweet little boy. Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.07,0:11:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她会被我迷得神魂颠倒的  -加油加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She won't know what hit her. - Vaya para all!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.32,0:11:30.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  曼尼  想做过可爱的梳套吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Manny, wanna make a sweet comb sheath?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.99,0:11:33.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在真不是时候  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could not be a worse time, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.96,0:11:38.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  这边真是安静又冷清啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. It's so peaceful and quiet over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.67,0:11:40.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈  哈  如果你是来幸灾乐祸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ha-ha. If you came over here to gloat,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.59,0:11:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经知道这很无聊了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I already know it's a dud.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.00,0:11:44.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  我是来给你送这个的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I came to give you this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.95,0:11:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你最喜欢的口味  蓝色冰恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's your favorite flavor- blue.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.59,0:11:49.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.60,0:11:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的头发看上去真的好美  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And your hair looks really nice. Hmm. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.28,0:11:54.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经梳了一天了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been combing it all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.64,0:11:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  大家都掌声鼓励一下卢克的勇敢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, let's all give Luke a big hand for being so brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.36,0:12:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好怪哦  它以什么为食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This feels so weird. What does it eat?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它专吃小男孩的大脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, just little boy brains.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.90,0:12:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克本来就没大脑  没什么好担心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, at least Luke's got nothing to worry about.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.28,0:12:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-里面有蛋黄酱吗  -没有  放心吃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is there mayo in this? - No. You're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.37,0:12:14.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想  或许我们可以悄悄溜走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I was thinking that maybe we could go slip away-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.29,0:12:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人想摸摸鼠鳞蜥吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, does anyone wanna pet the iguana?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.05,0:12:18.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然了  天啊 -这边  我  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hells, yeah. Oh, man. - Over here! Me! Me!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.10,0:12:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我超爱蜥蜴的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love lizards.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.63,0:12:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}["Lizzy-蜥蜥"取自"Lizard-蜥蜴"]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.68,0:12:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他叫什么名字  -她名叫蜥蜥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's his name? - Her name is Lizzy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.51,0:12:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  我完全懂其含义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. I totally get that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.13,0:12:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该面临如此下场的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't deserve this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.14,0:12:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -性感的爬虫女郎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Hot reptile chick.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.68,0:12:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她或许有自己的公寓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, probably has her own apartment,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.93,0:12:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很显然不介意摸些"恶心的东西"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}obviously okay touching gross stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.69,0:12:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们不过是聊聊天罢了  -你说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They're just talking. - You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.85,0:12:42.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰品味那么"高"  肯定不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan's far too sophisticated to get sucked in...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.31,0:12:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被一个浑身刻满纹身的女人吸引的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by a single lady with tons of cool tattoos.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.28,0:12:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我觉得它尿在我手上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. I think it peed on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.03,0:12:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -别啊  大自然的小精灵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no. - No way, Mother Nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.16,0:12:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不敢相信他会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe he does that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.96,0:12:56.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我错过什么了  伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, what am I missing, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.50,0:12:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aw, geez, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.50,0:13:01.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  看啊  我跳得好高  看啊看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, look! I go high! Look! Look!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.97,0:13:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  该滚蛋了  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, hit the road. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.64,0:13:05.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都是有家室的男人  快  散开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're family men. Come on. Scat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.01,0:13:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒啊  小老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great job, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.72,0:13:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有趣的部分到啦  快滑下来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now comes the fun part. Rappel down.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.01,0:13:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really high.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.05,0:13:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用畏惧任何事  只需面对畏惧本身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have nothing to fear but fear itself...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.62,0:13:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及水泥地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the concrete.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.65,0:13:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但老爸在这儿呢  小老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm right here, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.75,0:13:20.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  要接住我哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, just catch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.35,0:13:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很勇敢  过山车  爱死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am brave. Roller coasters? Love 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.02,0:13:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖电影?  《捉鬼敢死队》我都看7遍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scary movies? I've seen Ghostbusters, like, seven times.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.59,0:13:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经常驾车穿过那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I regularly drive through neighborhoods...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.24,0:13:30.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚装修过的街区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that have only recently been gentrified.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.32,0:13:32.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以基本上我是无所畏惧的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So yeah, I'm pretty much not afraid of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.70,0:13:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿嘿  大家伙儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.70,0:13:37.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快别闹腾逗乐了  那是我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Quit your clownin' around. That's my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.91,0:13:41.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Except clowns.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.50,0:13:43.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未告诉过家人们这一点  所以  嘘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Never shared that with the fam, so... shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.04,0:13:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥得维护自己的良好形象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do have an image to maintain.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.09,0:13:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我的恐惧源自何处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not really sure where the fear comes from.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.35,0:13:50.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈说是因为我小的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mother says it's because when I was a kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.26,0:13:53.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾在森林中发现过一具小丑尸体  谁知道呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I found a dead clown in the woods, but who knows?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.05,0:13:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你一定就是小寿星了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Oh. Well, you must be the birthday boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.56,0:13:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你吗  小卡舅夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that you, Uncle Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.92,0:14:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是小丑菲茨宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I'm Fizbo the clown.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.52,0:14:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道小卡舅夫是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know who this Uncle Cam is,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.21,0:14:05.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但听上去他似乎很帅  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he sure sounds handsome, doesn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.27,0:14:08.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁喜欢气球拧的动物  -我  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, who likes balloon animals? - I do! I do!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.61,0:14:11.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是小卡  只是小卡而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just Cam. It's just Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.33,0:14:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吧  -什么  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You all right? - What? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.69,0:14:17.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是对小丑有种复杂的情节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just have kind of a complicated relationship with clowns.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.99,0:14:20.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, join the club.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.08,0:14:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我之前太刻意勉强自己装成搞笑的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I came on strong with that whole funny guy bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.13,0:14:31.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在在你面前的是真实的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is me just being myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.09,0:14:33.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你知道那边那个男生是谁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Hey, do you know who that boy is over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.05,0:14:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是迪兰  海莉的男朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. That's Dylan. He's Haley's boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.18,0:14:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是又高又帅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's so cute and tall.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.48,0:14:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在发育呢  别老挑我的短处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm still growing. Give me a break.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.40,0:14:48.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  小姐  这只小狗需要一个新家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pardon me, miss, but this little doggy needs a new home.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.36,0:14:50.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.40,0:14:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的装扮真是很夺人眼球啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's quite an impressive getup you got there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.36,0:14:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  杰  噢  对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you, Jay. Oh, by the way,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.00,0:14:57.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的肩膀上有点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you have something on your shoulder.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.64,0:15:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.71,0:15:03.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  什么都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Never mind. It was nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.78,0:15:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,适可而止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把这些动物都关在动物园还是哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, do you keep these at a zoo or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.52,0:15:19.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  都放在我家里  -真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. I just keep 'em at my place. - That's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.49,0:15:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家只有一只猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I only have a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.73,0:15:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我曾经也有过一只猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah? I used to have a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.69,0:15:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前是想故意惹你生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just messing with you before,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.52,0:15:29.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他现在竟然还在跟她说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but seriously, he's still talking to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.61,0:15:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇  好凉啊  -姐这就出马\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wow. Cool. - On it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.40,0:15:35.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-其实  这是...  -我感觉像布兰妮一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know, this is one of- - I feel like Britney Spears.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.62,0:15:37.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好搞笑哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're so funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.00,0:15:39.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这确实很像布兰妮MV中的造型\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You kind of do look like Britney Spears.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.87,0:15:41.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - I'm just kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.44,0:15:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正  这只大概是我的最爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, this is probably my favorite.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.61,0:15:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  丛林女郎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, jungle lady?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.58,0:15:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎  你的一只爬虫跑出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think- I think one of your bugs got out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.96,0:15:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  这只吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? This one?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.71,0:15:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这只盒子里的  盒子歪倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This box thing here- It's on its side.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.88,0:15:54.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老天啊  跑哪儿去了  -没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God. Where did it go? - Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.21,0:15:57.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我丢了一只毒蝎子  我得找到它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I lost a poisonous scorpion, and I need to find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.26,0:16:00.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了孩子们  都把裤腿扎进袜子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, kids, let's all tuck our pants into our socks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.06,0:16:02.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要去阴暗潮湿的角落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Avoid shady, moist places,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.71,0:16:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来玩个游戏  叫做"当心脚下"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and let's make a game of looking where we step.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.80,0:16:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他没事吧  -我们现在能探望他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is he okay? - Can we see him?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.44,0:16:16.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生正在给他诊治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's in with the doctor right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.61,0:16:19.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事就是常发生的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These things happen, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.14,0:16:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你多么的小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No matter how careful you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.74,0:16:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  瞧瞧外公送了我什么  十字弓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, look what Grandpa gave me- a crossbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.74,0:16:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b0\pos(186,234)}一小时前
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.87,0:16:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-宝贝  那东西看着不安全啊  -别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sweetie, that does not look safe. - Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.60,0:16:27.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会教我怎么用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna show me how to use it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.00,0:16:29.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正是  我担心的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what... I'm afraid of.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.29,0:16:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快过来  准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.00,0:16:35.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  老天  你不会是在做梳套吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. You are not making comb sheaths.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.59,0:16:37.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是的  我知道的  又老套又无趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am, and I know. It's really lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.40,0:16:38.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都讨厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody hates it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.26,0:16:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  就像是当年唐娜·瑞格比的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It's just like, uh, Donna Rigby's party.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.39,0:16:43.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊  太对了  我这边小珠子什么的都有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Exactly! Yes! And I have the beads and everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.60,0:16:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  真是太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Amazing. This is awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.73,0:16:48.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  小卡是个小丑哈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So... Cam's a clown.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.76,0:16:50.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.90,0:16:54.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我绝对射到你了  -那是我家那位小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I totally got you. - And there's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.07,0:16:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有觉得很怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think it's weird
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.83,0:16:57.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们姐弟俩找的对象都  -自由不羁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- that we both chose people who were so- uninhibited?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.20,0:16:59.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想说令人尴尬的  不过你说的也对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was gonna say "Embarrassing," But yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.74,0:17:03.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧他们  派对因他们而充满活力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at them now. They're the life of the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.24,0:17:06.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须承认  尽管他很疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, you know, I gotta say, for all his craziness,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.25,0:17:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我爱我家那位小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love my clown.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.21,0:17:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐也是  有他们在真的很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me too. They're good for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.79,0:17:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我  肯定把派对气氛给毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would've totally tanked this party.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.96,0:17:15.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我则会在加油站被人暴揍一顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I would've gotten my butt kicked at a gas station.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.48,0:17:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -菲茨宝可是个不好惹的大坏蛋哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sorry? - Turns out Fizbo is a real bad-ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.26,0:17:22.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝎子  有蝎子  有蝎子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scorpion! Scorpion! Scorpion!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.80,0:17:23.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有蝎子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scorpion!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.10,0:17:30.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  靠得太近  离我太近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. Too close. Too close. Too close.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.98,0:17:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞毛啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.33,0:17:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.77,0:17:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-冷静  -发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Calm down. - What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.39,0:17:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发射了十字弓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We fired the crossbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.32,0:17:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我知道的  天啊  射中蹦床了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I know. Oh, my God. It's right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.95,0:17:46.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比安卡  我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bianca, I'm coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.95,0:17:51.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有谁在里面  -快出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who else is in there? - Get out!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.96,0:17:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实证明我不是甜心帅哥  也不是幽默达人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It turns out I'm not the sweet guy or the funny guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.76,0:18:00.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  曼尼  别进去  千万不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Manny, don't go in! Por favor!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.22,0:18:02.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I must!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.31,0:18:07.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.85,0:18:10.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼·迪尔加多是个用行动说话的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny Delgado is a man of action.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.19,0:18:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我的狗狗还在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. My dog is still in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.65,0:18:21.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.54,0:18:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  我的胳膊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! My arm!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.71,0:18:34.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小宝贝  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie? Luke?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.71,0:18:36.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  小老弟  -出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What happened, buddy? - What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.18,0:18:37.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.10,0:18:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  嘿  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.63,0:18:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我踩在这些小珠子上滑倒了  -糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I slipped on these stupid beads. - Oops.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.05,0:18:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  先起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.26,0:18:46.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.85,0:18:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他会没事的  -老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, he's gonna be fine. - Ay, Dios mio.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.64,0:18:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小宝贝  你怎么样啊  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, honey. How are you, kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.56,0:18:53.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他出来了  -小可怜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, there he is. - Pobrecito.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.65,0:18:56.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个可怜的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You poor thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.56,0:18:58.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  大家都来了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. Everybody's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.36,0:19:00.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当然得来了  你的小翅膀怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course we are. How's that busted flipper?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.48,0:19:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事  -今天的事真遗憾  小老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - Sorry about today, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.43,0:19:03.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明年再给你办个完美的生日派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll try again next year, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.95,0:19:06.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说笑吗  这是有史以来最棒的生日了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding? This was the best birthday ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.53,0:19:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我打了个石膏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - I got a cast.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.24,0:19:11.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你喜欢打石膏吗  -我一直想要一个的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You like a cast? - I've always wanted one.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.00,0:19:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-几周后  里面就会发臭  -恶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- After a few weeks, they start to smell. -Ew!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.87,0:19:16.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个怪胎  你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are so weird, you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.88,0:19:18.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可以在上面签名吗  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I sign it? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.50,0:19:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  我先来  -这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. Me first. - Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.67,0:19:22.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你在派对举办之前问我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you'd asked me before the party...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.34,0:19:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否希望发生一系列灾难的连锁反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I wanted there to be a chain reaction of disasters...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.90,0:19:28.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致卢克摔伤了胳膊  我很可能会说不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that led to Luke breaking his arm, I probably would've said no.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.72,0:19:31.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可能吗  -可...绝对  绝对不希望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Probably? - Prob- Definite- Definitely not.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不希望发生那种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would not want that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.13,0:19:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  不管怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, one way or another,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.69,0:19:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克在他生日这天是众人关心的焦点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke was the center of attention on his birthday,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.59,0:19:40.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且全家人都聚在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the whole family was together...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.36,0:19:44.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正是家庭生日会该有的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just the way it should be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.53,0:19:47.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲茨宝快递  我带蛋糕来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fizbo delivery! I brought the cake!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.78,0:19:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bravo!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.53,0:19:52.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心理承受不住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.70,0:19:54.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我得出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. I'm out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.13,0:20:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.26,0:20:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快吹蜡烛  快吹蜡烛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Blow the candles. Blow the candles.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.80,0:20:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比安卡·道格拉斯今晚给我打了3个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bianca Douglas called me three times tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.77,0:20:15.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不打算说假话骗你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna lie to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.39,0:20:17.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉快被那姑娘缠死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm starting to feel smothered.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.89,0:20:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很喜欢我的石膏  但里面开始痒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really like my cast, but it's starting to itch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.36,0:20:24.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好有我妈特制的挠痒神器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good thing my mom made me this personal scratcher.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.61,0:20:27.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好东西用了才知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's good stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.61,0:20:30.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有别的女人想勾搭你的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If another woman is messing with your man,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.32,0:20:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要先发制人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you have to get proactive.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:33.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管她有多漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't care how pretty she is
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.89,0:20:36.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者她有多少只恶心的爬虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or how many stupid reptiles she has.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.66,0:20:39.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要她想抢我的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She tries to take what's mine,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.42,0:20:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不择手段坑死你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}girlfriend's gonna get stung.

