[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第五集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.17,0:00:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, I'm home.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.21,0:00:09.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼打电话回来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did Manny call?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.69,0:00:10.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  因为他啥事也没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, because he's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.01,0:00:13.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是去睡衣派对  又不是黑帮火拼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was a slumber party, not a gang fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.64,0:00:16.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想他融入集体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just want him to fit in.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.35,0:00:18.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去冲个澡  你要一起来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna take a shower. Do you care to join me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.97,0:00:21.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  车库的小提箱里有一杆枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, honey, there's a gun in the footlocker in the garage.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.94,0:00:23.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我哪天脑袋发昏拒绝和你共浴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I ever say no to that question,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.93,0:00:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你直接一枪打死我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you to use it on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.86,0:00:28.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛丽·马克小姐  马克马克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Miss Mary Mack, Mack, Mack.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.69,0:00:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-穿成黑色  黑色黑色  -嘘  别出声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All dressed in black, black, black. - Shh, shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.28,0:00:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -银色扣子  扣子扣子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's wrong? - With silver buttons, buttons, buttons.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.53,0:00:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她背上  背上背上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All down her back, back, back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.03,0:00:38.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么不打架了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why aren't they trying to hurt each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.62,0:00:40.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道  我震惊得都不敢动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know, but I'm afraid to move.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.91,0:00:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你玩得真好  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're really good at this. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.08,0:00:45.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  这是怎么一回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is happening, Claire?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.78,0:00:48.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.67,0:00:50.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对正宗的松饼啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, that is a scone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.67,0:00:52.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零黄油  无脂肪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No butter. Nonfat.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.05,0:00:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得瑟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.30,0:00:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去看看莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna go check on Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.77,0:01:04.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-惊喜哦  -妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Surprise! - Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.73,0:01:07.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.69,0:01:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来像是有鸟撞上玻璃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sounds like a bird hit the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.65,0:01:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  这是个凶兆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. That's a bad sign.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.77,0:01:15.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很痛啊  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! That hurt, jerk!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.40,0:01:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了你  你个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! I'm gonna kill you, stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剧情峰回路转吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.09,0:01:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我郁闷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I'm sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.87,0:01:25.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  宝贝  -你好  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, honey. Mmm! - Hi. I, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.29,0:01:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你要来  你之前没给我打电话啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I didn't know you were in town. You didn't call.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.71,0:01:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等不及要见我的小孙女了  她在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I couldn't wait to see your new baby. Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.80,0:01:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  是谁啊  -是我妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell, who was that? - It's my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.09,0:01:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就使劲儿忽悠吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah, right,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.15,0:01:36.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上回她来的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause the last time she was here,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.63,0:01:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰箱门上的磁铁被摆成了五边...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the refrigerator magnets rearranged themselves into a penta...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.42,0:01:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是奶奶啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Grandma!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.09,0:01:59.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你拽着她的脚干嘛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom. Mom, what are you doing to her legs?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.28,0:02:01.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打太极  我在塞多纳时每天都打\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tai chi. I did it every day in Sedona.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.89,0:02:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  你也该试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, you should try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.06,0:02:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔的妈妈对我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell's mother has a problem...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.10,0:02:09.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有成见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.44,0:02:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如去年圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Last Christmas, for example,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.94,0:02:15.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她送了我一台健身器材和生菜烘干机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she gave me a piece of exercise equipment and a lettuce dryer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.20,0:02:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题的重点是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, to recap,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.22,0:02:19.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我送给她的是一副华丽的钻石耳环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gave her a gorgeous pair of diamond earrings,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.30,0:02:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她送的礼物却暗示我很肥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she gave me a hint.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.76,0:02:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在塞多纳让我改变了许多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And living in Sedona has been transformational.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.19,0:02:29.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天早上起床后  去参加冥想集会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I get up every morning, and I go to a Vortex meditation site...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.94,0:02:31.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在高僧的指导下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and work with a shaman to
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.78,0:02:35.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于参透精神世界的奥秘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}finally understand how to live my spirituality.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.02,0:02:37.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.18,0:02:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我领悟到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I've learned that
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.91,0:02:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我的修行更上一层楼的唯一方法...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the only way I can move to the next level of my awakening...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.68,0:02:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要想办法...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is if we all can somehow...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克服...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}get past...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.50,0:02:49.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事的阴影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.14,0:02:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.61,0:02:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"那件事"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.39,0:02:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不堪回首啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.28,0:02:58.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想恭喜杰和可爱的歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would like to congratulate Jay and the lovely Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.87,0:02:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(232,194)}杰&歌洛莉亚的婚礼现场
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.87,0:02:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(276,217)}去年二月
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.63,0:03:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为他们感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm very happy for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.85,0:03:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和杰举办一次盛大的婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanted a big, beautiful wedding with Jay...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.18,0:03:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我和我前夫的婚礼是在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because my ex-husband and I got married...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.35,0:03:08.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥伦比亚一间很小的法官办公室里举办的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a tiny little office of a judge in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.36,0:03:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈想去参加婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mother wanted to go to the wedding
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.12,0:03:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以显示自己对前夫再婚一事十分大度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to show everyone how okay she was with all of it,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.69,0:03:16.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我说服我爸和歌洛莉亚邀请她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I convinced Dad and Gloria to invite her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.34,0:03:19.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时是谁警告你  那是史上最烂的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who warned you that that was the worst idea ever?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.84,0:03:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.26,0:03:22.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.96,0:03:25.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我已经开始新生活了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course, I've-I've moved on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.47,0:03:28.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来要带男朋友来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was supposed to come with a date,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.09,0:03:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他闪到腰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he just hurt his back,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.93,0:03:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有点讽刺啊  因为他可是又年轻又健康\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is very ironic because he's young and-and healthy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.31,0:03:35.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈在婚宴上...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mom started drinking...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.81,0:03:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狂饮一种叫做"哥伦比亚淫棍"的鸡尾酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}these cocktails called "Horny Colombians"...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:41.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和歌洛莉亚的叔叔们大拼酒量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with some of Gloria's uncles,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.71,0:03:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那酒名显然说的就是那帮家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}whom apparently the drink was named after.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.59,0:03:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  他们很好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on. They were funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.39,0:03:49.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们一直摸我屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They kept patting my butt.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.96,0:03:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人自恋了哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Somebody's full of herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.77,0:03:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说  那是哥伦比亚婚礼的传统习俗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a- It's a Colombian wedding tradition, they said.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.90,0:03:59.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来祝个酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would like to make a toast.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.13,0:04:02.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  外婆醉得不行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Nanna got totally wasted.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.64,0:04:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, it was really funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.11,0:04:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就乌七八糟的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then it was gross.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.39,0:04:11.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬新娘  以及新郎  也就是我的前夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To the bride and the groom- my ex.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.51,0:04:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起生活了35年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thirty-five years we were together,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.05,0:04:15.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他见到小骚货10分钟不到就跟着跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he couldn't wait 10 minutes to run off with Charo.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.84,0:04:18.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.28,0:04:23.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  我知道他们是天生一对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, I knew they were perfect for each other...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.22,0:04:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为新郎"财大"气粗  而新娘"胸大"乳挺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I saw his wallet and her boobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.05,0:04:29.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的脏手拿开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take your hands off me!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.23,0:04:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈  妈  -米奇尔  放松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mom. Mom. - Oh, relax, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.32,0:04:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你今天也变得跟克莱尔一样了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, did you take your Claire pill?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.63,0:04:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别别  -我们去呼吸一下新鲜空气  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, no. - Let's just go get a little fresh air, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.19,0:04:38.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就变得诡异了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then it got weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.11,0:04:40.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是歌洛莉亚  我是歌洛莉亚  -我抓住她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm Gloria! I'm Gloria! - I got her.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.93,0:04:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吻我吧  吻我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kiss me! Oh, hey, kiss me!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.87,0:04:45.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Oh, geez.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.30,0:04:49.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外婆力大如金刚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nanna is really strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.68,0:04:53.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呦  哎呀哟  啊嘶嘚啊嘶哆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ayayayayay! Ooh! Ayayayayay!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.25,0:04:56.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我对前夫说出婚誓时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}During my vows to my first husband,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.97,0:04:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几个毒贩子冲了进来  暗杀了法官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}drug dealers burst in and assassinated the judge.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.23,0:05:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到二婚的情形更可怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was way worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.46,0:05:03.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么好呢  我就是能让女人如痴如"狂"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What can I say? I drive women crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.87,0:05:07.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有点太快了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's too soon, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.73,0:05:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  所有人都会去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody is going to be there, Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.10,0:05:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.92,0:05:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸和我都不会允许你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your father and I are not about to let you
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.34,0:05:15.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开两小时的车去看一个演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}drive two hours to go to a concert...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.34,0:05:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后跟一帮男孩子混一晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then spend the night with a bunch of boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.09,0:05:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是和你那个17岁的性冲动男友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}especially that 17-year-old hormone you're dating.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.70,0:05:21.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全程都有人监护的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's totally supervised.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.28,0:05:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  谁监护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, really? By whom?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.63,0:05:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞·潘丁的叔叔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By Spencer Patine's uncle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.07,0:05:25.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞·潘丁是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's Spencer Patine?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.42,0:05:27.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认得斯宾塞的  就是手里带家伙的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know Spencer- the guy with the arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.51,0:05:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会儿  抄什么"家伙"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. What kind of arm?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.26,0:05:29.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的"家伙"是什么意思啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is that even mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.53,0:05:30.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叔叔就是托比叔叔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His uncle is Uncle Toby.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.81,0:05:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托比叔叔啊  我会把他加入"安珀警报"名单的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Uncle Toby. I'll be sure to include that in my Amber Alert.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.89,0:05:36.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[安珀警报  出现儿童丢失或绑架案时\N通过媒体向社会发布的警报]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.79,0:05:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天啊  -我能插句话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God! - Okay. Can I step in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.30,0:05:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我能帮上忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I can help.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.42,0:05:39.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  你妈妈担心的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, what your mom is worried about...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.21,0:05:40.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的心会被伤透\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is you getting your heart broken
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.72,0:05:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为迪兰明年就要上大学去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when Dylan goes off to college next year.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.61,0:05:43.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他不上大学  -我担心的不是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's not going to college. - That's not what I'm-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.93,0:05:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不上大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not going to college?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.76,0:05:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是混乐队的好吧  他们要去巡演呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's in a band, okay? They're going on tour.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.22,0:05:49.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情发展的真是越来越"好"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, this just gets better and better.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.78,0:05:52.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们每件事都要替我做主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you always on me about everything?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.78,0:05:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为你必须明白  -好啦  大家冷静一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Because you need to understand... - Okay. Everybody, calm down!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.86,0:05:56.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从头来说一说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's start from the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.31,0:05:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞手里带什么家伙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's wrong with Spencer's arm?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I'm home!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.97,0:06:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  睡衣派对好玩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, baby! Did you have fun at the slumber party?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.12,0:06:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定累坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You must be exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.70,0:06:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我一点儿也不累\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm not tired at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.23,0:06:15.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是第一个睡着的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was the first one to fall asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.24,0:06:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸上是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's on your face?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.45,0:06:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是与朋友欢聚后的幸福笑容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A smile from having such a good time with my friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.05,0:06:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.16,0:06:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.96,0:06:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来他们是笑这个啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why they were laughing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.72,0:06:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是我对时事的评论很逗呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought it was my funny take on current events.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.96,0:06:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么要干这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would they do something like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.66,0:06:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好担心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.85,0:06:37.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子们成天就搞这种恶作剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys pull pranks like that all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.74,0:06:39.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也捉弄他们一下呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just gotta prank 'em back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.40,0:06:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要让他们知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just gotta show 'em
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.18,0:06:41.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是会以牙还牙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're willing to give as good as you get.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.43,0:06:45.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.40,0:06:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报仇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Revenge.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.47,0:06:51.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还挺喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.66,0:06:58.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  也许我们不该旧事重提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Mom, instead of dredging up the whole incident,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:07:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就直接全部忘掉好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe we should just try and repress it,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.46,0:07:01.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像一般家庭那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like a- like a normal family.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.75,0:07:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行  我得来个了断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't. I need closure.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.21,0:07:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生即将开始新的旅程了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm about to embark on a new journey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:09.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识了个男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I met a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.67,0:07:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫查斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His name is Chas,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.27,0:07:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他让我搬到国外和他双宿双飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he's asked me to come live with him in his foreign land.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.94,0:07:16.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.02,0:07:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.06,0:07:18.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要搬到加拿大去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're moving to-to Canada?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.96,0:07:20.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大法语区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}French Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.91,0:07:23.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.60,0:07:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It is wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.07,0:07:27.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我一想到自己对歌洛莉亚和杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just that when I think of all the awful things...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.49,0:07:31.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及对你和克莱尔说过的那些恶言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I said to Gloria and Jay and you and Claire,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.12,0:07:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就有罪恶感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel such guilt.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.83,0:07:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[班夫公园:加拿大著名景点]
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.83,0:07:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往事随风去吧  班夫公园再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give it time, and see Banff.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.10,0:07:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.49,0:07:42.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是没法对他以身相许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just can't give myself to him sexually.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.12,0:07:44.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别说这  妈  -没想到你突然说如此劲爆的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Mom. - Did not see that coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.35,0:07:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Coming另意为高潮  整句偏意为  没有高潮]
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.04,0:07:45.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  别误会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, oh. Don't get me wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.49,0:07:47.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们"下半身"非常性福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We satisfy each other down there-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.60,0:07:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-受不了了  -听不下去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh! Can't.. - Don't wanna-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.04,0:07:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我需要大家原谅我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why I need everyone's forgiveness.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.67,0:07:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我需要你帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need your help, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.29,0:07:54.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  你听见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you hear that, Mitchell?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.08,0:07:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈需要你的帮助  才能跟她的新男友查斯做爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mom needs your help to make love to her new man, Chas.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.25,0:07:59.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全"不"奇怪啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not weird at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.41,0:08:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.79,0:08:03.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是很明白你到底想我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just not really sure what you're asking me to do, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.12,0:08:06.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都生我的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, everyone's mad at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.51,0:08:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你能帮我安排一下  我好道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe you could pave the way so that I can apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.98,0:08:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, um, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我们今晚要搞周日聚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we are actually all supposed to have Sunday dinner tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.95,0:08:17.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以或许我可以问问大家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so maybe I could go around and ask everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.71,0:08:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你能不能也来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if it's okay for you to join us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.95,0:08:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你靠谱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! I knew I could count on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.20,0:08:24.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的帅小伙儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my beautiful boy. Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.19,0:08:25.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱死你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.86,0:08:27.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上有一种鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a fish in nature
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.65,0:08:30.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会一直把小鱼含在嘴里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that swims around with its babies in its mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.58,0:08:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这种鱼看见米奇尔和他母亲的关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That fish would look at Mitchell's relationship with his mother...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.85,0:08:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准会说  "乱得不堪入目啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and say, "that's messed up."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.97,0:08:45.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boy-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.23,0:08:48.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你妈妈闹僵了对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Things with your mom got pretty intense down there, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.81,0:08:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好比是水火不容  你明白我的意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All like East Coast-West Coast. You feelin' me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.98,0:08:54.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲般的威严  朋友般的关爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Act like a parent, talk like a peer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.44,0:08:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我称之为"友父"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I call it "Peerenting."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.49,0:08:58.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从我老爸那儿学来的  当年他走进我房里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I learned it from my own dad, who used to walk into my room...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.89,0:09:00.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会说  "怎么了  小老弟"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and say, "what's up, sweathog?"
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.95,0:09:06.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  我很愿意让你去看演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I would love to let you go to the concert.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  演唱会多劲爆啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me? I think concerts are rad.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.25,0:09:10.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当年可是个"霍粉"呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello? I was a Hall-Raiser.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.00,0:09:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A what?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.81,0:09:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一年夏天我追着霍尔&奥兹走遍了全国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I followed Hall & Oates around the country one summer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.57,0:09:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《千金小姐》唱出了我的心声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Rich Girl" Just spoke to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.71,0:09:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[《千金小姐》为Hall & Oates名曲之一]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.77,0:09:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当年正和一个千金小姐恋爱  也不算恋爱啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was dating this girl. Not- Not dating.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.52,0:09:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜自己也只是在追着她而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I was following her too, kind of-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.92,0:09:23.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈就是不相信我  这不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Mom just doesn't trust me, and it's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.77,0:09:27.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她相信你  只是演唱会很容易就让人乱来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She trusts you. It's just that weird stuff happens at concerts.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.14,0:09:29.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-男生们会一柱擎天  -真恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Boys get urges. - Ew.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.48,0:09:31.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你进来有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, is there something you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.52,0:09:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  就这个事  来跟你这妹子沟通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, there is- to connect with this girl right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.75,0:09:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  假装我不是你爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, come on. Pretend I'm not your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.39,0:09:38.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是两个好朋友在果汁吧闲聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're just a couple of friends kickin' it in a juice bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.85,0:09:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果汁吧是什么东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's a juice bar?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.87,0:09:41.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就茶餐厅吧  随便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, a malt shop. Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.52,0:09:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  我不...  -别  谁是你爸啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad, I don't... - No. Who's Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.39,0:09:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是你爸啊  我是生物系的马库斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's Dad? I'm- I'm Marcus from Biology.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.83,0:09:49.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉你好  你和迪兰发展得如何啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Haley. How's it going with you and Dylan?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.36,0:09:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有没对你图谋不轨啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Has he tried anything inappropriate with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.26,0:09:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.33,0:09:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.10,0:09:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在干嘛呢  -不知道  没啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What are you doing? - I don't know. Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.48,0:09:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在和茶餐厅里碰到的一个傻子聊天呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just talking to some dork I met in a malt shop.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.69,0:10:05.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  米奇尔  有事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mitchell. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.07,0:10:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  恰好路过而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey! Just in the hood.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.20,0:10:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得当年妈妈放弃工作来照顾我们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you- Do you remember how Mom gave up a career to raise us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.21,0:10:12.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大有前途的工作呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Promising career.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.96,0:10:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.43,0:10:15.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.68,0:10:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.91,0:10:19.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why so long?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.76,0:10:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道这么长时间没说话很怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, I know. It's weird when we haven't talked for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.82,0:10:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说你的头发长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean your hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.42,0:10:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我不指出你的形象问题  谁会啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if I can't tell you, who will?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.80,0:10:29.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈想你知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Mom wants you to know
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.77,0:10:32.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对那件事非常抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that she's very sorry about the incident,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.41,0:10:35.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她希望我们能原谅她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and she wants us to forgive her.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.44,0:10:37.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过你来道歉  她还真有诚意啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How very nice of her to say that through you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.50,0:10:39.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you see?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.82,0:10:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的讽刺太伤人了  像抽了我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The sarcasm is so hurtful, like a whip.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.79,0:10:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吧  在成长中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know how growing up,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.89,0:10:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们脑子里总有一个声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we all have that voice inside our head...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.49,0:10:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时刻提醒我们自己的不足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that tells us we're not good enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.72,0:10:51.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而提醒我的声音来自脑外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, mine was outside my head,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.00,0:10:52.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天开车送我上学的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}driving me to school.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.57,0:10:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, so- so anyway,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.95,0:10:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈希望化解跟爸爸和歌洛莉亚的矛盾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom really wants to smooth everything over with Dad and Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.64,0:10:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我在想  你看这样行不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I was thinking, uh, would it be okay
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.00,0:11:01.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今晚和我们一起吃饭如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if she maybe joined us for dinner tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.53,0:11:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这也许是你们最后一次见我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it may be the last time you ever see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.16,0:11:06.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这个嘛  -好吧  妈  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well... - Okay. Wait, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.70,0:11:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.82,0:11:10.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  我要去...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm- I'm moving...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.50,0:11:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个遥远危险的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to a far and dangerous place.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.61,0:11:16.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加拿大  不过啊  她认识了个叫查斯的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Canada. But, uh, she met a man named Chas.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.99,0:11:18.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -他是个记录员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - He's a logger.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.90,0:11:21.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Logger有"记录员"和"伐木工"两种意思]
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.90,0:11:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个伐木工吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, like a lumberjack?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.25,0:11:24.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他是给一个胆固醇研究记录血液样本的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, he logs blood samples into a cholesterol study.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正  在我走出那次婚礼的阴影之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, until I'm past this whole wedding debacle,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.02,0:11:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没法和他亲热\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't be intimate with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.66,0:11:32.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们互相取悦对方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We do things to each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.11,0:11:34.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是用手来做的  -老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We use our hands. - Oh, my Lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.72,0:11:36.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  外婆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Nanna.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.17,0:11:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小心肝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my little comet!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.78,0:11:40.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你  都长成大人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, look at you. You're all grown up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.86,0:11:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话你跟妈妈说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hmm. Tell Mom that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.61,0:11:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她甚至还不让我去看演唱会呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She won't even let me go to a concert.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.63,0:11:46.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要跟男朋友过夜的好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Overnight, with her boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.05,0:11:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you laughing at?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.28,0:11:54.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啥  我在笑因果报应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, karma's a funny thing, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.85,0:11:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还记得瑞奇吗  -天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Remember Ricky? - Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.85,0:11:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是瑞奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh. Who's Ricky?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.22,0:12:00.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁也不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.59,0:12:02.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞奇是你妈妈当年的男朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ricky was your mother's boyfriend,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.82,0:12:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他长得跟邪教杀人狂查尔斯·曼森一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he looked like Charles Manson.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.13,0:12:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一晚  她直到凌晨4点才回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And one night, she didn't come home until 4:00 in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.83,0:12:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4点啊  妈  你当年跟瑞奇干嘛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}4:00. Wow. Wow. Mom, what were you and Ricky doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.86,0:12:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我们什么事也没干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing. We were doing nothing,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.59,0:12:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个很贴心的小伙儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he was a very sweet boy,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.83,0:12:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你当年愿意了解一下的话  就会明白这点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which you might have known if you bothered to get to know him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.75,0:12:19.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰也很贴心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan's a sweet boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.57,0:12:23.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  迪兰怎能和瑞奇比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan. Dylan isn't Ricky.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.02,0:12:24.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞奇是个诗人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ricky- Ricky was a poet.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.97,0:12:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰还是歌手呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan writes songs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌写得可棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome songs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.63,0:12:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可能会明白这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And maybe you would know that
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.73,0:12:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是"你愿意了解一下的话"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"If you bothered to get to know him."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.95,0:12:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  首先  我不是我妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know? First of all, I am not my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.09,0:12:40.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在了解一个人之前  我不会先做出评判\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't judge people before I get a chance to know them.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.89,0:12:44.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你请迪兰今晚来吃晚饭吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you invite Dylan over to dinner tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.14,0:12:47.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他像你说的那样贴心善良\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and if he's as sweet and as kind as you say he is,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.46,0:12:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就一百个放心地让你们去演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then I have no problem considering letting you go to the concert,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.18,0:12:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还得查查托比叔叔的底细\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}after I do a background check on Uncle Toby.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.98,0:12:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢  谢谢妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.97,0:12:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就给他打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna go call him!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.50,0:13:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是心胸"开阔"教女有方啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's very revealing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.18,0:13:04.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我为人之母的风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's my parenting style.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.01,0:13:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我是说你胸部外露了  -妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, I meant your blouse. - Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.64,0:13:09.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, wait. Come...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.61,0:13:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您这是帮倒忙呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not making this easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.20,0:13:14.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔拜托  别这样  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, come on. Stop, stop, stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.00,0:13:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让她来吃晚饭吧  向爸爸和歌洛莉亚道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just let her come to dinner, apologize to Dad and Gloria,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.59,0:13:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后她就能和查斯幸福到永远了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she and Chas can live happily ever after.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.58,0:13:22.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在加拿大  -在加拿大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- In Canada. - In Canada.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.09,0:13:25.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会  你为啥不让她自己解决呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. Why don't you make her fix this,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.06,0:13:27.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她每次都找你帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}instead of you doing it as usual?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.06,0:13:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这话什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa. What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.22,0:13:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次老妈一闯祸  就让米奇尔来收拾残局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom makes a mess, and there's Mitchell to clean it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.64,0:13:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is so not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.06,0:13:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要细究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.29,0:13:36.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是因为你跟妈咪的关系太僵了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're the one with the screwed-up relationship with Mommy-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.63,0:13:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟妈妈  -哇塞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- With Mom. - Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.73,0:13:39.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"妈咪"  -没  我没这么叫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "Mommy"! - No, I didn't say it-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.26,0:13:42.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我擦  -好吧好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Damn it. - Ooh. Fine. Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.28,0:13:44.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让她来吧  但她得亲自跟爹地说  -"爹地"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She can come, but she's gotta clear it with Daddy. - "Daddy"?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.71,0:13:46.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没叫"爹地"  -你叫了"爹地"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I did not say "Daddy." - You said "Daddy."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.21,0:13:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.05,0:13:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  你来这儿干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.15,0:13:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, I'm sorry to bother you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:13:58.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能跟你和歌洛莉亚说几句吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I talk to you and Gloria for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.15,0:14:00.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她出去解决曼尼的事儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's out dealing with a Manny situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.54,0:14:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把一个小孩的单车给烧了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He set a kid's bike on fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.18,0:14:05.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫他去报复别的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I might have told him to get even with some kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.74,0:14:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他就做了回"铁血真汉子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he went all Rambo with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.39,0:14:11.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我这个当爹的教育失误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not my best parenting moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.77,0:14:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是最糟的一回啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not your worst.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.85,0:14:13.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.99,0:14:16.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那个  妈妈回来了  -你妈妈?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, well, you know, uh, Mom's in town. - Your mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.94,0:14:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是你妈妈  她从坟墓里爬出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, your mom. She's back from the grave.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.88,0:14:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是我妈啦  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Yes, my mom, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.17,0:14:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈诈尸也没她可怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mom would be less scary.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.10,0:14:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  是她毁了那次婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, she's a wreck about what happened at the wedding,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.48,0:14:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她想今晚一起去吃饭  向大家道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she wants to come to dinner tonight to apologize to everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.42,0:14:29.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是她的狗腿子啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still her little errand boy, I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.39,0:14:31.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  为什么大家都这么说啊  才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No- Why does everybody keep saying- No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.72,0:14:34.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想让这个家重归于好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I'm just trying to piece this family back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.15,0:14:38.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会跟歌洛莉亚说  妈要一起去吃晚饭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you'll talk to Gloria about Mom coming to dinner?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.08,0:14:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚打死都不会同意的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Gloria would never go for that in a million years.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.86,0:14:41.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还在生你妈妈的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's still furious with your mother,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.80,0:14:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我没有在和你谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is why I'm not talking to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.94,0:14:45.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么得罪你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.28,0:14:46.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次谈话压根就不存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This conversation never took place.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.60,0:14:47.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可有点不近人情啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not very nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.64,0:14:48.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大老远跑来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I drove all the way here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.53,0:14:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你从来就没来过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you didn't. You were never here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.58,0:14:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连电话都没打过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never even called.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:51.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来是要打的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would've called,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.54,0:14:53.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得面谈比较好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I thought it would be better-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.21,0:14:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么一回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's happening here?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.01,0:14:59.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我也想给这事来个了断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, I would love to get this thing behind us,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.98,0:15:01.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我瞒着歌洛莉亚请你妈来的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but Gloria would never forgive me
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.58,0:15:02.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是绝不会原谅我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I pulled a fast one on her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.07,0:15:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  要由你瞒着她去请你妈来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why you're going to pull a fast one on her,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.17,0:15:07.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我则假装对此极力反对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm not going to like it one bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.92,0:15:08.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's just great.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.93,0:15:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  好极了  看来又是我背黑锅了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, that's great. So, it's all up to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.45,0:15:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听不见你  因为你在家里  而我在打瞌睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't hear you because you're back home, and I'm taking a nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.81,0:15:21.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小迪迪  你可算来啦  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- D-Money! There he is. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.18,0:15:23.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快进来  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on in. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.48,0:15:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi. - How you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.96,0:15:25.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.99,0:15:27.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um- Uh, hey, everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.69,0:15:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这位是迪兰  -你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is Dylan. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.71,0:15:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好迪兰  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, Dylan. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子心地非常善良\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He has a very gentle soul.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.54,0:15:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一句"你好"你就看出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got that from "Hey"?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.09,0:15:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  我看你带了乐器啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Dylan, see you brought the ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.54,0:15:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  我刚排练回来  -真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, yeah. I just came from practice. - Sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.19,0:15:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真怀念当年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Miss those days.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.38,0:15:44.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前也在乐队混吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you were in a band?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.71,0:15:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来可以的  但是在高中时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could have been, but in high school
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.82,0:15:48.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一心痴迷于魔术  所以嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was really all about my magic, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.07,0:15:49.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  别吹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Over.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.67,0:15:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是爸爸和歌洛莉亚来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's gonna be Dad and Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.46,0:15:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.91,0:15:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这很傻  但我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it's silly, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.89,0:15:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真有点儿紧张了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a little nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.48,0:15:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不傻  紧张是正常的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. That's not silly. You should be.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.43,0:16:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好呀  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hola. Hola. - How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.66,0:16:05.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Manny? - Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.15,0:16:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-胡子真帅  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nice mustache. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.83,0:16:08.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逗他  小心他把你家给烧了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't make fun. He may burn your house down.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.97,0:16:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.05,0:16:13.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dede.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.70,0:16:15.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  歌洛莉亚  你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Jay, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.87,0:16:16.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在这儿干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is she doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.54,0:16:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那话什么意思  她不知道我要来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What does she mean, "What is she doing here?"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.61,0:16:21.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔跟你说了我会来  -瞎说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell told you I'd be here. - Lies!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.78,0:16:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能跟她说  否则她就不来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I couldn't tell her, because she wouldn't come.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.87,0:16:26.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  我妈妈想为之前的事道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, uh, my mom wants to apologize for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.91,0:16:28.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就给歌洛莉亚来个突然袭击吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you just spring it on Gloria like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.71,0:16:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  你有病是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, what the hell is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.53,0:16:31.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听她道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want her apologies.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.70,0:16:33.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  不能怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who could blame you, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.03,0:16:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以都怪你出的馊主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which is why this is a terrible idea by you!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.09,0:16:37.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  曼尼  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay. Manny. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.78,0:16:39.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, wait, wait, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.69,0:16:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I just want to tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.30,0:16:44.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对大闹婚礼的事非常抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how sorry I am for ruining your wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.98,0:16:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时孤独一人  日子很不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was struggling with being alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.82,0:16:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时  杰那么快就有了新恋情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Meanwhile, Jay moves on so easily,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.72,0:16:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他找的不是一般的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and not with just anyone-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.45,0:16:57.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是一位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with a...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.13,0:16:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}young...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.48,0:17:00.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明  而且美丽的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and smart and beautiful woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.73,0:17:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不指望你原谅我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't expect you to forgive me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.85,0:17:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是你  我只想抽我自己丫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I were you, I'd want to punch me right in the mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.27,0:17:19.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们家今天报仇也报够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think we've had enough revenge in this family for one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.16,0:17:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊  你们看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah. Okay. Y- You see?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.33,0:17:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家即将翻开新的一页  多亏了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, we're all gonna move past this, and because of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.76,0:17:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是妈妈的小乖乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who's not a mama's boy, but is
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.49,0:17:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是个通情达理  善于察言观色的智者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a caring person with wisdom and emotional insight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.25,0:17:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都给我记着吧  衰货们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So make a note, bitches.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.00,0:17:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真心不适合王婆自夸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not a good color on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.62,0:17:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原谅你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I forgive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.37,0:17:41.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没料到会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not prepared for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.38,0:17:43.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.48,0:17:44.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I wanna
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.80,0:17:46.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-扭断你的脖子  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- rip your head off! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.30,0:17:49.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞毛啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.12,0:17:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你毁了我的婚礼  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You ruined my wedding! - Oh, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.47,0:17:53.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我按住歌洛莉亚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! I got Gloria!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.75,0:17:55.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我按住歌洛莉亚了  -妈  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got Gloria! - Mom, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.17,0:17:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腿别乱蹬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Unbend your legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.95,0:18:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我按住歌洛莉亚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.03,0:18:03.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站好  都是大人了  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stand up like a big girl. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.28,0:18:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  别闹了  别闹了  都别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it, the two of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.82,0:18:09.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让你见笑了  很抱歉  -没事没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I am so sorry about this. - No, it's cool. It's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.81,0:18:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太荒唐了  歌洛莉亚不是小三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is ridiculous. Gloria didn't steal me,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.52,0:18:13.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪迪  你是知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dede, and you know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.10,0:18:15.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们夫妻不和已经多年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We grew apart for years,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.47,0:18:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你离开家去寻找自我  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you left to find yourself, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.43,0:18:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为自己能处理好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought I could handle this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.64,0:18:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.54,0:18:23.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要听你丫说抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't say sorry anymore!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.12,0:18:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的抱歉都是放屁  -我拉住歌洛莉亚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That word means nothing in your mouth! - I got Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.39,0:18:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what just happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.59,0:18:31.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.84,0:18:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  在我看来这事很简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, it seems pretty simple to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.36,0:18:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都极力想护住些美好的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're reaching out, trying to hold on to something awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.05,0:18:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  或许你不该...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, maybe- maybe you shouldn't...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.36,0:18:44.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事  我不习惯这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, look, look. I'm not used to this-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.86,0:18:46.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种大家族的家事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the whole big family thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.47,0:18:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我家  我们甚至互相不说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In my house, we don't even talk to each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.41,0:18:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的是  当我第一眼见到海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, it's funny- the first time I saw Haley,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.00,0:18:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道我喜欢她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew I liked her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.38,0:18:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很美丽动人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, she's beautiful and everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.95,0:18:57.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不只如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's-it's not just that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.46,0:19:00.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还有一种令人折服的自信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's that she's got this killer confidence-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.69,0:19:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种  那种自信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, the kind of confidence
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.90,0:19:06.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自于像你们这样的大家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you get from having a family like this...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.07,0:19:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种充满激情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's passionate...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.29,0:19:11.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对异国美女的包容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and accepting of hot foreigners...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.63,0:19:15.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对基佬和疯婆子的包容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and gay dudes and nutty people.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.65,0:19:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.03,0:19:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正相亲相爱的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a family that actually loves each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.95,0:19:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法相信自己会说出这话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.19,0:19:26.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许我们应该让她跟他去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but maybe we should let her go with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.59,0:19:27.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个好小伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.01,0:19:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  海莉说迪兰是个音乐家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody, Haley says that Dylan is a musician,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.72,0:19:35.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他写歌写得非常好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he writes some great songs.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -老弟  来演奏一曲吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Play something, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.53,0:19:40.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们真想听的话当然可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I guess so, if you want me to.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.23,0:19:42.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给大家来一首好歌吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We could all use a nice tune right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.48,0:19:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这首歌嘛  其实是我写给海莉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is, uh, actually a song I wrote for Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.08,0:19:47.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌名叫《月下》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's called "In the Moonlight."
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.77,0:19:49.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-歌名真有爱  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Lovely title, Dylan. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.14,0:19:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*星星从天边划过*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*The stars are falling from the sky*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.56,0:20:02.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*它们都是被你吸引而坠落*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*And you're the reason why*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.91,0:20:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*月光洒在你脸庞*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*The moon is shining on your face*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.20,0:20:13.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*因为它终于感到*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Cause it finally feels*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.10,0:20:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*它找到了归属*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*It's found its place*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.76,0:20:18.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*因为宝贝  宝贝*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Cause baby, baby*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.68,0:20:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我就是想要干你  干你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*I just wanna do you do you*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.88,0:20:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*你想不想干我  干我*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Do you wanna do me, do me*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.91,0:20:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*就在这月下  月下*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Underneath the moonlight the moonlight*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.77,0:20:30.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*宝贝  宝贝*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Baby, baby*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.97,0:20:34.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*也许我会偷你  偷你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Maybe I will steal you Uh, steal you*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.00,0:20:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*这样我就能摸你  摸你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Just so I can feel you feel you*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.96,0:20:39.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*也许这能安抚你  安抚你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Maybe that would heal you heal you*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.53,0:20:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*从你身体里*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*On the inside*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.67,0:20:45.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不能跟他去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's so not going.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.21,0:20:46.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打死也不准去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not a chance in hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.85,0:20:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*它们似乎不在乎*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*They don't seem to mind*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.62,0:20:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*月光洒在你脸庞*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*The moon is shining on your fa-a-ace*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.36,0:21:02.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*而它终于感到*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*And it finally feels it's*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.99,0:21:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*找到了它的归属*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Found its place 'cause*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.20,0:21:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*宝贝  宝贝*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Baby, baby*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.40,0:21:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我就是想要干你  干你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*I just wanna do you, do you*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.70,0:21:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*宝贝  你也可以干我  干我*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Baby, you can do me, do me*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.74,0:21:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*而我则会干你  干你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*And I will do you, do you*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.80,0:21:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*也许这能安抚你  安抚你*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Maybe it would heal you heal you*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.91,0:21:23.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*从你身体里*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*From the inside*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.31,0:21:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*-从你身体里  -从你身体里*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*- From the inside  - From the inside*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.44,0:21:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*-从你身体里  -身体里*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*- From the inside  - Inside*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.13,0:21:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是唱不好和声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Never good at harmonizing.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.63,0:21:31.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唱得挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was good.

