[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.59,0:03:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.59,0:03:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.59,0:03:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第二十一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.06,0:00:07.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝儿  找我什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honeydew! What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.40,0:00:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜谁来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess who's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.81,0:00:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.95,0:00:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从可可海滩一路开着房车过来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He drove his R.V. all the way up from Cocoa Beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.38,0:00:16.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子啊  在努力工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Son, working hard?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.36,0:00:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会说  工作个屁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna say "Hardly working."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.45,0:00:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本是打算告诉你他出发的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I meant to tell you he was driving out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.45,0:00:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他说了吗  -说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did he say it? - Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.29,0:00:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.28,0:00:27.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他本该过几天才到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He wasn't supposed to show up for a few more days.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.10,0:00:29.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜他给我们带了什么来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, guess what he brought us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.50,0:00:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只狗  给我们养的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A dog... to keep.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.17,0:00:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes! Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.42,0:00:37.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我早该把狗的事告诉克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I should have told Claire about the dog,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.12,0:00:38.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来准备说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I was going to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.72,0:00:41.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想等她心情好时再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I was just waiting for her to be in the right mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.35,0:00:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  几天前的某晚她心情就挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I did get one right mood a couple nights ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.56,0:00:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我用那晚"干"了其他的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I cashed that in for something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.15,0:00:53.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是不是有大麻烦了  -非常非常大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Am I in trouble? - Oh, really, really big.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.98,0:00:55.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吓到我了  到底有多糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I'm a little scared. How bad is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.81,0:01:00.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家立了新规矩  不许进卧室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well we have a new rule- no sleeping in the bedroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.13,0:01:01.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(191,66)\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs28\c&HBFAD90&\3c&HFFFFFF&}{\shad0}牙科诊所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.12,0:01:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普里契特先生  我是本  本·杜根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mr. Pritchett. Uh, Ben- Ben Dugan.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.37,0:01:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是米奇的高中同学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I went to high school with Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.66,0:01:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起参加过戏剧社\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were in the drama club together.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:12.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想起来了  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's right. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.71,0:01:14.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你卸了老头子妆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, I didn't recognize you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.24,0:01:15.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都认不出你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without that old-guy makeup on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.30,0:01:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和米奇演的《阳光小子》火爆全场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you and Mitch knocked The Sunshine Boys out of the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.01,0:01:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇演得很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitch was really great in that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.55,0:01:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直觉得他是当演员的料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I always thought he should be an actor.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.01,0:01:22.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在找了份真正的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, he's got a real job now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.11,0:01:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他做了律师  你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a lawyer. How about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.87,0:01:26.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我还在演戏  -那敢情好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Still acting. - Fantastic.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.33,0:01:28.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实挺过瘾的  我演了部新电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, it's exciting. I'm in a new movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.19,0:01:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《枫叶大道》  刚上映的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maple Drive. Just came out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.70,0:01:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  哇  我认识名人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're kidding me. Look at me. I know somebody famous.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.33,0:01:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, anyway, I got to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.75,0:01:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-见到你真高兴  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Great to see you. - Good to see you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.46,0:01:39.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子成电影明星了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kid's a movie star.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.00,0:01:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-医生怎么说  -没有蛀牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, how'd it go in there? - No cavities.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.01,0:01:43.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还得了把免费牙刷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I got a free toothbrush.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.40,0:01:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你想去看电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you want to go to the movies?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.01,0:01:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚听说一部好片子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just heard about a good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.28,0:01:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我该去上学了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm supposed to be in school.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.64,0:01:48.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还应该用牙线呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you're supposed to floss too,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:49.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也躲过了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but you got away with that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.01,0:01:51.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.06,0:01:53.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我生命中最美好的几个日子之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One of the greatest days of my life...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.06,0:01:55.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我老爹带我逃课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was when my old man sprung me from school
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.73,0:01:57.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后带我去坐卡车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and took me to the track.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.90,0:02:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让曼尼有同样的体验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanted to do the same type of thing for Manny,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.19,0:02:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说如果歌洛莉亚听到这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}plus I figured when Gloria heard about it,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.11,0:02:03.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会在卧室好好犒赏我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe it pays off in the bedroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.10,0:02:07.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爹当年莫非也是为了这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wonder if that's why my old man did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.14,0:02:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.62,0:02:13.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你婆婆非要养这只狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mother-in-law just had to have the dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.24,0:02:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果发现原来她对狗过敏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turns out she's allergic.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.95,0:02:17.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宠物店就没个宽限期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the pet store didn't have a grace period
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.33,0:02:19.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者包退换之类的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or a return policy or anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.35,0:02:21.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是从宠物收留所领回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got him from the pound.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堪萨斯州刮龙卷风了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was there a twister in Kansas?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.98,0:02:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然怎么把房子刮到我家车道上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause there's a house in my driveway.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.09,0:02:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家  邓菲先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Welcome home, Mr. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.43,0:02:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你  邓菲先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, always a pleasure, Mr. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.53,0:02:33.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  邓菲先生  请把它放在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Indeed it is, Mr. Dunphy. Place it there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.28,0:02:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的好的  -真怀念啊  来抱一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, I shall. I shall. - I miss this. Get in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.50,0:02:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸超级棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad is awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.04,0:02:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他特别好  永远积极向上  笑口常开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's awesome. He's always up. He's always happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.38,0:02:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟我是好哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, he and I are best buds.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.46,0:02:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就像一个模子刻出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're like two peas in a pod.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.71,0:02:48.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是连体双胞胎  或者双头蛇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or Siamese twins. Or a snake with two heads.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:50.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们在万圣节扮过以上所有角色  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They've actually been all those things for Halloween. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.34,0:02:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟  这一定是斯科特吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oy. This must be Scout, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.04,0:02:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得警告你  他会脱毛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should warn you. He sheds.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.62,0:02:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一路上让他上床和我一起睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made the mistake of letting him sleep with me on the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.93,0:02:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那床单就跟被俩野人滚过一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now my sheets look like two bigfoots did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.89,0:03:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我的粗俗用语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pardon the language.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.90,0:03:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我妈好吗  -说到那个"大脚野人"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How's Mom? - Speaking of big feet, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.34,0:03:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和她的闺蜜们乘游轮旅游去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's on a cruise with her girlfriends,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.63,0:03:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多都是恐龙  也有几个尚有几分姿色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}some of which are not totally unattractive.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.68,0:03:11.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒提醒了我  她给孩子们带了礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that reminds me. She sent some gifts for the kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.93,0:03:13.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I will be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.93,0:03:16.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们仨先套套近乎  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You three get better acquainted. - Will do!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.98,0:03:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-慢走  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye! - Will do!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.56,0:03:21.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你没和我商量就领来了只狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I cannot believe you got a dog without consulting me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.31,0:03:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此事需要全家共同商议才行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was a major family decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.48,0:03:24.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我错了  -知道就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It was wrong. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.07,0:03:25.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.96,0:03:28.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我们早就讨论过养狗的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we have talked about getting a dog for years,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.40,0:03:30.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家只有你不同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you're the only one who wasn't into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.16,0:03:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道照顾它都会是我的活儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I knew that I would be the one taking care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.58,0:03:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.16,0:03:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都会帮忙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we will all help.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.02,0:03:39.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是教导孩子责任感的大好机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a great chance to teach the kids responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.67,0:03:42.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当年你让卢克送报纸时也是这么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is exactly what you said about Luke's paper route.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.04,0:04:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.03,0:04:07.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}里面有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is anyone in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.60,0:04:21.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}你真适合红色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Red's a good color on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.80,0:04:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是电影罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just a movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.04,0:04:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-它好可爱啊  -瞧它那小脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, he's so cute. - Look at his little face.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.10,0:04:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想养狗来着  谢谢爷爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I always wanted a dog. Thanks, Grandpa.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.41,0:04:37.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要记得  养狗可是个大责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, but remember, having a dog is a major responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.71,0:04:39.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里每个人都得负责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everyone in the family has to pitch in.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.96,0:04:42.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没问题  邓太太  -没包括你  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can do, Mrs. D. - Not you, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.05,0:04:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松了一口气  我最近正好忙着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, phew. 'Cause I got a lot on my plate right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.21,0:04:47.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看谁来了  小卡舅夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, look who's here. Uncle Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.55,0:04:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我们听说来了新成员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, we heard about the new addition
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.46,0:04:50.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一定得来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we had to come right over.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.93,0:04:53.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  又见到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, so good to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.78,0:04:55.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这衬衣真好看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now that is a shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.69,0:04:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  弗兰克  我网购的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well, thank you, Frank. I get 'em online.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.31,0:04:58.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头发给你链{\c&H16F5F3&}接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\b0}{\fs14}{\3c&H202020&}{\shad1\c&HFFFFFF&}I'll send you a link.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.36,0:04:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我自家熏制了香肠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well, at home, I smoke sausages.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.98,0:05:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头也给你发一{\c&H16F5F3&}节\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\b0}{\fs14}{\3c&H202020&}{\shad1\c&HFFFFFF&}I'll send you a link.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.92,0:05:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真经典\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Classic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:05.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这就是莉莉吧  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And this must be Lily. - Oh, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.60,0:05:07.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她等不及要来看新狗狗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She just couldn't wait to meet the new doggy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.48,0:05:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看她待在这里挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think she's good right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:11.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快让我来和狗狗亲热亲热\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me get in there and get some of that doggyness.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.53,0:05:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-宝贝儿啊  -海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, there it is. - Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.03,0:05:15.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-乖乖啊  -我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There it is. - I gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.70,0:05:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -是布莱恩  他要退出乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's wrong? - That was Brian. He just quit the band.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.82,0:05:20.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  为什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.12,0:05:21.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要搬去波特兰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's moving to Portland.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.79,0:05:23.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他父母复合了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His parents got back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.16,0:05:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真可恶  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, that sucks. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.16,0:05:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明天的演出得取消了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now we're gonna have to cancel the gig tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.54,0:05:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好你能找到其他的鼓手呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe you can find another drummer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.54,0:05:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想现在已经来不及找了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I think it's too late for that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.84,0:05:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会打鼓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I play drums.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.59,0:05:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然自从有了莉莉以后  我许久没练了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I mean, I haven't played in a while, since Lily's come along,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.34,0:05:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过如果你紧缺人手  我就是你的人手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but if you're in a jam, I can jam.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.74,0:05:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴  可我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I totally would, but I'm not sure
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.22,0:05:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们玩的是同一卦的音乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we like the same sorts of music, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.19,0:05:46.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛  我是基佬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, because I'm gay,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.13,0:05:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只会演奏舞台剧的音乐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just gonna want to play show tunes?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.72,0:05:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  因为你年纪比较大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, because you're old.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.06,0:05:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这话更伤人  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. That hurt more, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.10,0:05:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他试试吧  总比取消好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give him a chance. It's better than canceling.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.73,0:05:56.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我不想白白浪费\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're right. I don't want to lose
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.91,0:05:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造雾机的押金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the deposit on that fog machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.86,0:06:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们试一试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Let's do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.90,0:06:03.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前是音乐老师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I used to be a music teacher,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.11,0:06:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有了莉莉后我就放弃了事业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I gave that up as soon as Lily came along.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.42,0:06:07.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们觉得必须有一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Well, we just felt that it was really important...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.50,0:06:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在家里照顾她  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that one of us stayed hometo raise her, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.12,0:06:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说别人的选择不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and that's not a judgmenton other people's choices.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.67,0:06:14.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我们的家庭观念非常传统而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just that we happen to be a very traditional family.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.75,0:06:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  那个帮莉莉房间祈福的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, that's what the disabled lesbian shaman
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.04,0:06:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残疾拉拉神婆也这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who blessed Lily's room said too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.62,0:06:26.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How you doin', buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.66,0:06:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.98,0:06:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, geez.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.03,0:06:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说  菲尔  你爸真哭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am telling you, Phil, the man was crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.03,0:06:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.92,0:06:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爹是全世界最乐天的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad is the happiest guy on earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.80,0:06:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是听起来像哭吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It probably just sounded like he was crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.24,0:07:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听过他从椅子上起身的声响吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Have you heard the noise he makes when he gets out of a chair?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.05,0:07:02.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我听得清清楚楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I know what I heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.97,0:07:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想大概是和你妈有关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think this has something to do with your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.80,0:07:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -想想看  他是一个人来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Yeah, he came here alone. Think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.89,0:07:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她坐游轮玩去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's on a cruise.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.79,0:07:11.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从没分开旅行过  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and they never take separate vacations, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.76,0:07:14.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不可能  如果真有事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, if something was wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.89,0:07:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸会告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my dad would tell me about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.14,0:07:16.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  菲尔  他不会说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Phil, he wouldn't,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.94,0:07:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们从来就没认真聊过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you guys never actually talk about anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.97,0:07:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们常聊呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We talk all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.07,0:07:22.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上班时他一周打三次骚扰电话来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He crank calls me at work, like, three times a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.10,0:07:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-骚扰电话不算数  -但是算有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Crank calls don't count. - Counts for fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.10,0:07:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  我想你应该\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, honestly, I think that you should
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.95,0:07:27.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞清楚你爸到底怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}find out what's going on with your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.07,0:07:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸什么事都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's going to be nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.93,0:07:32.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他又不像你爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad isn't like your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.11,0:07:34.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没那些城府  心机之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's nothing deep and dark inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.28,0:07:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他甜美外表下隐藏的是更多的甜美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His hard candy shell is just hiding more candy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.76,0:07:41.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该是想出去  好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think he wants to go out. Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.86,0:07:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-聪明的狗狗  -不想扫你的兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Smart dog. - I hate to break it to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.59,0:07:46.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这招所有狗都会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I think all dogs can do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.38,0:07:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要出去玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna play outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.06,0:07:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.51,0:07:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.89,0:07:57.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是先露一小手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Should I just play a little something?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.06,0:08:00.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  不过如果打不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. But, you know, if it doesn't work out,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.43,0:08:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也别难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}don't feel bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿打鼓就像骑自行车一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, hopefully this is- this is like riding a bicycle,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.92,0:08:08.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学了就永远忘不掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it'll all come back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.47,0:08:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是重音鼓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the loud one.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.18,0:08:14.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So... here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.49,0:08:32.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  我真傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, silly me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.24,0:08:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把鼓槌给拿反了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had the sticks in the wrong hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.92,0:08:58.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  你该给鼓槌贴好左右标签\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dude, you should label those sticks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.06,0:09:07.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是警报吗  我们家被入侵了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that the alarm? Has our perimeter been breached?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.16,0:09:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是警报  是门铃停不下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not the alarm. The doorbell won't stop ringing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.92,0:09:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许是魔鬼在按门铃  -才没有魔鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Maybe a demon is ringing it. - Not a demon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.80,0:09:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁老是在按门铃啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who keeps ringing the doorbell?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.13,0:09:17.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-肯定是魔鬼在按  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We're pretty sure it's a demon. - Oh, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.97,0:09:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.72,0:09:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是魔鬼  它就会继续响了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If it were a demon, it would keep on ringing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.76,0:09:24.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他已经进屋了  我要去武装起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not if he's already inside. I'm getting a weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.36,0:09:27.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脑子里想什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What were you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:29.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带这么小的孩子去看恐怖片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who takes a little boy to a horror movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.09,0:09:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你疯了吗  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's loco, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.48,0:09:32.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么大不了的  你知道什么才恐怖吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is no big deal. You want scary?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.65,0:09:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像他这么大时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I was his age,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.69,0:09:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是经历过古巴导弹危机的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&} I lived through the Cuban Missile Crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡觉时都藏把黄油刀在枕头下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I slept with a butter knife under my pillow...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.07,0:09:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防要和苏联上校搏斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in case I had to fight some Soviet colonel.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.70,0:09:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏联上校抓你个小屁孩干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would they send a Soviet colonel to get a little boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.91,0:09:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我能认出苏共的每一架飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I could identify every commie plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.58,0:09:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这是在说什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are we talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.90,0:09:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是  恐惧也是成长的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, all I'm saying, being scared is part of growing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.56,0:09:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼会没事的  那有助于培养个性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny will get over this. It builds character.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.43,0:09:56.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我站第一班岗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll take the first watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.80,0:09:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩最好先去睡一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You two might as well get some rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.30,0:10:00.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长夜漫漫啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna be a long night.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.77,0:10:05.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个性吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Character.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.00,0:10:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.95,0:10:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧  门没锁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on in! It's open!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.37,0:10:13.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说你是上隔壁借白糖来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't tell me. You need a cup of sugar.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.54,0:10:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nah. Just, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.43,0:10:18.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得  那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just wondering, I don't know, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.40,0:10:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您脑子里没在烦恼什么事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anything on the old noodle?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.46,0:10:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了这顶烂假发吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Other than a bad toupee?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.36,0:10:25.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的  这可是真头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding, of course. This is my real hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.89,0:10:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, okay. - Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.67,0:10:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事问你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.27,0:10:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把狗带来是不是让你为难了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I putting you in a bad position with this whole dog thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.65,0:10:34.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔看起来不太高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire seemed a little put out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.61,0:10:37.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别理她  克莱尔一开始还不喜欢我呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't worry about it. Claire didn't like me at first either.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.98,0:10:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也不怪她  解散\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't blame her. Dismissed!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.15,0:10:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你知道吗  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Dad, um, you know what? I, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.45,0:10:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔撞见了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire saw something,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.65,0:10:49.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我不问你  她非灭了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she'd kill me if I- if I didn't ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.25,0:10:50.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.58,0:10:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吃早饭时就不能穿条裤子吗  真叫人"哭"笑不得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you wear pants to breakfast, for crying out loud?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.50,0:11:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-又被你骗到了  正中弱点  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You got me again. Right in the funny bone. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.46,0:11:03.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  斯科特  松口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Scout. Let go of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.59,0:11:04.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.84,0:11:07.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏狗狗  你看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dog. Look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.05,0:11:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么会有你的胸罩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did he get ahold of your bra?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.39,0:11:11.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, uh, we were out on a date,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.98,0:11:13.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有辆特别好的车  于是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he has a really nice car, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.56,0:11:15.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为呢  当然是从洗衣篮里找到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you think? He got it out of the laundry basket.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.02,0:11:18.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这狗一秒钟也不能大意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can't take my eyes off that dog for a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.68,0:11:20.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛不把它关笼子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you just keep him in the crate?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.20,0:11:22.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我关了  他自己会开笼子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I tried that. He figured out how to get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.42,0:11:24.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是去找你爸谈话了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you were dealing with your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.39,0:11:26.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我们谈了  他没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah, I did. He's fine, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.43,0:11:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们才谈两分钟就谈好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got that from a two-minute conversation?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.90,0:11:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直接问他还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I... asked him point-blank if he was okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.78,0:11:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说很好  所以我就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He said he was. So I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.03,0:11:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果你们扯了几个笑话  就谈完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just swapped some jokes and moved on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.32,0:11:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你得更深入地问他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, the man needs more of a push than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.78,0:11:44.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他想谈  他会主动说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, if he wants to talk to me about it, he will.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.87,0:11:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人的内裤搅成一团了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, someone's panties are in a bunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.87,0:11:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[有大惊小怪之意]
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.87,0:11:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只想表示一下关心  -不  你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I thought I was showing concern and- - No. Right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.67,0:11:51.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  这该死的狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! That damn dog!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.33,0:11:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二位  帮帮忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, little help?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.14,0:11:59.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要上厕所了  我可不想尿裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have to go to the bathroom, and I'm not gonna do it in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.68,0:12:11.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我买了中餐外卖  -太好了  正饿着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, I got Chinese. - Sweet! I'm starving.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.39,0:12:12.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有客人呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we have guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.73,0:12:15.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正合奏呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. We're just having a little jam session.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.56,0:12:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰你认识的  那边是克雷格和尼尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know Dylan. This is Craig. This is Neil.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.60,0:12:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会记得他是抱着我女儿的陌生人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll always remember him as the stranger holding my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.02,0:12:23.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能到厨房来一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I talk to you in the kitchen for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.57,0:12:26.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  各位  我们休息一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Hey, guys, let's, uh- let's just take five.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.25,0:12:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这支龙虎少年队怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up with 21 Jump Street?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.38,0:12:30.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的鼓手退团了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well, their drummer quit
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.77,0:12:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明晚帮他们顶替一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm gonna fill in for him tomorrow night.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.51,0:12:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  明天我们得去胡娇家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. We have Pepper's
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.96,0:12:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑雪风情奶酪火锅派对  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}apres-ski fondue party tomorrow night, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.72,0:12:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.38,0:12:39.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得通知乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you'll just have to tell your band
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.00,0:12:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另请高明了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that they're gonna have to find someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:42.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不能失信于他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? No. I'm not gonna let these fellas down.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.14,0:12:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made a commitment.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.47,0:12:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也答应了胡娇  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You made two commitments, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.51,0:12:46.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你又知道胡娇那脾气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you know how Pepper is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.57,0:12:47.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡事必须完美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything has to be perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.73,0:12:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不穿厚毛衣他都能跟你急\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He gets mad if you don't wear a big sweater.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.98,0:12:51.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得  去年我热得要命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I remember. I got so hot last year,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.08,0:12:53.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点晕死在奶酪上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I almost went face down in the gruyere.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.23,0:12:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是想让我一个人去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I'm going by myself, is that what you're saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.63,0:12:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真心需要参加这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just feel like I kind of need this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.23,0:13:01.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了丰富你大学申请书吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To round out your college applications?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.44,0:13:04.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是呆在家里守着莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just that because I'm always home with Lily...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.15,0:13:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我闷得有点发疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just feel like I'm going a little bit stir-crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.96,0:13:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看那书房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at the den.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.96,0:13:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我翻来覆去地粉刷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every time I finish painting it, I start all over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.88,0:13:11.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快赶上金门大桥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like the Golden Gate Bridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.88,0:13:11.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[金门大桥易生锈  必须反复油漆]
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.80,0:13:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去练习了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna go back to jamming.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.47,0:13:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得  我们必须解决这事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, we gotta fix this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.00,0:13:35.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿厚毛衣来听演唱会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, what's with the big sweater at a concert?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.81,0:13:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是基友们的穿衣风格吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that a gay thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.85,0:13:40.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是为了胡娇的滑雪风格风奶酪火锅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Dad. It's for my friend Pepper's apres-ski fondue-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.52,0:13:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  的确是基友们的风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yeah, it's a gay thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.98,0:13:43.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好赶紧开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hope they start soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.92,0:13:46.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特不喜欢独守空屋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think Scout likes to be left alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.91,0:13:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挺喜欢那狗的嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You love the dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.74,0:13:51.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是喜欢它  我是心疼我的沙发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I don't love the dog. I love my couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.03,0:13:54.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那狗看沙发的眼神就跟那是巨型香肠一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the dog was looking at it like it was a giant sausage.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.08,0:13:57.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  好消息  你的车道要腾空了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good news, you two. You're getting your driveway back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.37,0:13:59.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-明天一早我就上路  -这么快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm hitting the open road in the morning. - Oh, already?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.04,0:14:01.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -迫不急待想回家看妈了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Anxious to get home and see Mom, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.00,0:14:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我打算要随风游荡一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm just gonna drive wherever the wind blows me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.00,0:14:05.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般也就是飘到隔壁的车道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is usually into the next lane.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.80,0:14:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去喝苏打汽水好吗  爷爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we get some sodas, Grandpa?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.38,0:14:10.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀  不过只能一杯  我还得开车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, but just one. I'm driving. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.43,0:14:14.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他居然不回家  他从没离开我妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not going home? He's never been away from my mom
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.76,0:14:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超过看医生的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for longer than a doctor's appointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.39,0:14:18.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我知道  我就说嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I know. I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.39,0:14:19.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很同情那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I always felt bad for people
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.45,0:14:20.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和父亲关系疏远的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with emotionally distant fathers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.73,0:14:22.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我也是其中之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It turns out I'm one of 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.09,0:14:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没沦落成脱衣舞男真是奇迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a miracle I didn't end up a stripper.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.65,0:14:27.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢各位来观看演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, everybody, for coming out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.65,0:14:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面是我们写的几首歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These are some songs we wrote.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.70,0:14:32.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二  一二三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One, two. One, two, three.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.73,0:14:37.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*宝贝别走  我只想让你知道*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Baby, don't leave me I just want you to know *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.18,0:14:39.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我只想让你知道*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* I want you to know *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.96,0:14:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*有些热情我自己也控制不了*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* There's something inside me that I cannot control *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.92,0:14:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我控制不了*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* I cannot control *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.92,0:14:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我俩的男朋友都帅呆了  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Our boyfriends totally rock! - I know, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.76,0:14:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*听到你高喊我的名字  我就彻底疯狂*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* I heard you screamin' my name I'm goin' insane *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.80,0:14:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, the plan was...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.59,0:14:53.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看十分钟的演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to watch him for 10 minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.80,0:14:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就溜去胡娇的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then run out to Pepper's party.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.60,0:14:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*奔腾在我的血管中*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Coursing through my veins *
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.43,0:15:01.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他在台上太亮眼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But he was so great up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.52,0:15:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么舍得离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How-How could I leave?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.19,0:15:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*别害怕*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* But don't be afraid *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.65,0:15:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我就是你的吸血鬼*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* I'll be your vampire *
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.82,0:15:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他的光辉时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was his moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.70,0:15:15.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时刻持续了很久很久的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And his moment went on for a really, really long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.65,0:15:50.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久到我可以溜去参加派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turns out I could have run to the party
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.50,0:15:54.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再回来听他的最后一敲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and made it back for the end of his moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.58,0:16:00.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  去刷牙准备上床睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, go brush your teeth and get ready for bed, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.70,0:16:04.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-上你的床  -我能看电视吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Your bed. - Can I watch TV?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.12,0:16:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-只能看十分钟哦  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mmm, only 10 minutes. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.55,0:16:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  杰  我是本·杜根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay, it's Ben Dugan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.78,0:16:18.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到你的留言了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got your message.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.10,0:16:20.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很乐意帮忙  我晚上来拜访\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, yes, I'm happy to help out. I'll swing by tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.89,0:16:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁啊  -是本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's that? - That's Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:23.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演电影的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the guy who was in the movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.02,0:16:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想如果曼尼看到他真人很善良\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figure when Manny sees him, sees how nice he is,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.77,0:16:28.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会发现电影都是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he'll realize it's all pretend.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.58,0:16:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你觉得会有效吗  -那家伙人可好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You think that will work? - Guy's a sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.46,0:16:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼和他聊一聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's gonna spend two minutes with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.21,0:16:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听他解释电影拍摄过程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He'll explain how the movie's made.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.67,0:16:42.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还带了他的道具刀来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's even bringing his fake machete.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.23,0:16:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橡胶做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thing's made of rubber.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.68,0:16:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是曼尼吧  我是来找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, are you Manny? I'm here for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.72,0:16:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧我带了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look what I got.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.85,0:17:01.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, he's here!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.19,0:17:02.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦  怎么啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Que paso? Que paso? Que paso?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.03,0:17:09.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得换张大床了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna need a bigger bed!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.99,0:17:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, geez.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.41,0:17:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  真的是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! I think that's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.42,0:17:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没溜走啊  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You stayed. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.33,0:17:22.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是乐队家属\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you know, I'm-I'm with the band.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.34,0:17:24.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得演出某些地方还需改进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought the gig was a little sloppy in spots,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.55,0:17:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过等我学会了所有的歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I think once I learn all the songs-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.84,0:17:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你只参加这一次呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought- I thought this was a one-time thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.12,0:17:32.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑吧  我们秒杀了全场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding? We destroyed in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.55,0:17:34.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没听到有个妹子大喊我的名字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you hear that one lady screaming my name?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.74,0:17:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是菲尔喊的  他喝了罐红牛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was Phil. He had a Red Bull.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.21,0:17:40.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  表现得不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, guys. Good gig, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.10,0:17:42.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  棒极了  -震撼的演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. Totally awesome, man. - Heck of a gig.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.76,0:17:44.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙儿好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.14,0:17:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你不是去波特兰了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. I thought you were in Portland.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.83,0:17:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  我爸妈又闹崩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. My parents broke up again.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.07,0:17:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不搬走了  我可以继续参加乐队了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not moving. I can stay in the band.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.32,0:17:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下可尴尬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, this is awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.36,0:17:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.81,0:18:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是我尴尬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, awkward for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.80,0:18:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[林戈·斯塔尔  披头士的第二任鼓手]
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.39,0:18:10.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油赶超我吧  林戈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good luck following that, Ringo.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.01,0:18:15.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你们的电线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I believe this belongs to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.18,0:18:17.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想拖着一房子在后面跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to drag the house along with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.93,0:18:19.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猴子们  都过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come here, you little monkeys.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.73,0:18:21.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  爷爷  我们会想你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye, Grandpa. We'll miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.31,0:18:22.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望能把你们一起带走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wish I could take you with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.85,0:18:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-路上小心  爷爷  -我尽量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Drive safe, Grandpa. - Oh, I'll try.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.31,0:18:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不留下吃早餐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You sure you don't want to stay for breakfast?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.61,0:18:30.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我该上路了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I ought to be hitting the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.45,0:18:32.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, adios.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.11,0:18:34.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.70,0:18:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能和你谈谈吗  -好呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I talk to you for a second? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.66,0:18:39.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝们  我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.03,0:18:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你没跟我说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think you're being honest with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.16,0:18:46.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你有什么事在心上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I know something is going on with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.21,0:18:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.71,0:18:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心上  我的内裤倒是提得太上面了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Something up? Well, my boxers are, uh, riding a little high.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.72,0:18:55.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没在没心气跟你开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not in the mood for jokes right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.25,0:18:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-虽然刚才那句逗死了  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- although you nailed that. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.73,0:18:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说得真好  -谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&} - Great stuff. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.56,0:19:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没事  -没事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's nothing. - Oh, it's nothing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.31,0:19:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是跟妈有关吧  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing to do with Mom? - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.10,0:19:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  其实有关  我坠入爱河了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, yeah. I've fallen in love.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.23,0:19:15.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.37,0:19:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她是谁  -是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who is she? - He!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.33,0:19:19.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.98,0:19:22.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那边的小家伙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's that little guy right over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.72,0:19:25.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快过来  过来  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on over here. Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.32,0:19:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子  瞧瞧他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you go. Ah, look at him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.62,0:19:29.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在驾车穿越全国的路上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Driving across country,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.58,0:19:31.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个小崽子成功地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this little bastard nuzzled his way
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.08,0:19:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺走了我的心  对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}right into my heart, didn't ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.51,0:19:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就是不想送掉这狗罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So this is just about you not wanting to leave the dog?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.77,0:19:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该和妈说清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you should tell Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.43,0:19:39.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和它在路上的这三天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those three days on the road with him
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.29,0:19:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我人生最快乐的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}were the happiest of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.43,0:19:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话你就别对她说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should leave that part out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.07,0:19:45.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想因为留下斯科特而让爷爷难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to keep Scout if it makes Grandpa sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.15,0:19:48.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  宝贝 可是奶奶会过敏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I know, sweetie. But Grandma has allergies,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.34,0:19:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以斯科特必须留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so Scout has to stay with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.12,0:19:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可以打抗过敏针嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she could always just get some allergy shots.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.04,0:19:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你不会愿意让她遭那罪的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you don't want to put her through that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.54,0:19:58.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  当年我还为她做了结扎手术呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hell, back in the day, I got a vasectomy for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.41,0:20:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  爸  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad. Dad. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.77,0:20:03.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特是你的狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scout's- Scout's your dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.38,0:20:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该跟着你走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He should go with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.34,0:20:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧  这可是你逼我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you twisted my arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.64,0:20:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  儿子  多谢你看穿了我的伪装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, Son. Thanks for poking through the armor.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.76,0:20:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-您下面也快穿出来了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're poking through the armor down there. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.56,0:20:18.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Made you look.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.50,0:20:21.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是块奇才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are a treasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.52,0:20:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  斯科特  我们走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Scout. Let's mosey.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.69,0:20:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, oh, oh! Oh, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.07,0:20:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他喜欢这个  -那是肯定的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He loves that, yeah. - Oh, I bet he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.40,0:20:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  斯科特  这次轮到我开车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Scout. This time I drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:35.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You still got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.21,0:20:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信我会这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe I'm saying this,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.56,0:20:40.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我好像和我爸更加亲近了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I think I might have actually gotten even closer with my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.11,0:20:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信他把我的狗带走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe he took my dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.95,0:20:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  -爷爷再见  爱你哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye-bye. - Bye, Grandpa! Love you!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.91,0:20:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.49,0:20:51.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爷爷再见  我爱你  -卢克  停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye, Grandpa! I love you! - Luke, stay!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.12,0:20:54.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  停下  -下次再来  再见啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Luke, stay! - Come back soon! I'll see you later!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.12,0:20:55.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, stay!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.33,0:20:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  -停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke! - Stay!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.17,0:21:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗兰克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Frank.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.24,0:21:04.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  真高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay. Good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.29,0:21:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  没想到你会在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great to see you. Didn't expect to find you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.96,0:21:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我孙女男友的乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, listen, when my granddaughter's boyfriend's band
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.63,0:21:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我儿媳妇弟弟的男友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}plays an under-21 club with my daughter-in-law's
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.33,0:21:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在少年俱乐部一起演出  我不会错过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}brother's gay partner, I show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.71,0:21:16.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是礼节问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's just how I was raised.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.67,0:21:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还没见过我太太吧  歌洛莉亚  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't think you met my wife, Gloria. - Hola.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.51,0:21:22.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你  你真是漂亮啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, it's a pleasure. You are a lovely woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.93,0:21:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你一定是弗兰克吧  -哎呀呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You must be Frank.  - Okay, then,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.96,0:21:29.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Frank意译为坦白的  说实话\N于是弗兰克(Frank)就很直白地夸赞歌洛莉亚]
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.05,0:21:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比国庆节时的拉斯维加斯街头还要火热啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you are hotter than a Las Vegas sidewalk on the Fourth of July.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.02,0:21:32.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我太过火了吗  -不  没事  弗兰克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did I go too far? - Not you, Frank. No.

