[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.09,0:02:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.09,0:02:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.09,0:02:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第二十四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.52,0:00:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  好好享受比赛哦  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, hey, honey. Have a great time at the game. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.38,0:00:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么在响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Why are you crunching?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.86,0:00:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常  我是守规矩的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ordinarily, I'm a rule follower,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.52,0:00:13.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果有人不准我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but when someone tells me I can't bring
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.84,0:00:15.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自带零食进体育馆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my own snacks into their stadium,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.38,0:00:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要生气[坚果]了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's when I get a little nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.81,0:00:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个自由的国家不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a free country, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.81,0:00:24.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说吧  让我不爽[薯片]的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's just say it ruffles me...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.03,0:00:25.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某些蠢货[花生]叫我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when some goobers tell me...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.90,0:00:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在发薪日[糖]花上半天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have to spend half my payday...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.39,0:00:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他们的热狗上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}on their hot dogs.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.68,0:00:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得回来照全家福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please, just remember the family portrait.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.78,0:00:37.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-摄影师只有一个小时时间  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We only have the photographer for an hour. Okay? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.10,0:00:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  要不要去试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, sweetie, did you have a chance to
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.03,0:00:40.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放在你衣橱里面的白裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}try on the white pants I put in your closet?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.57,0:00:42.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  长什么样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, what do they look like?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.93,0:00:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白裤子还能长什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there really a more clear way to describe white pants?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.37,0:00:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  如果不合适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, if they don't fit you,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.75,0:00:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是全家唯一没穿白裤子的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're going to be the only one not wearing white,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.68,0:00:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你就像"沃尔多在哪里"一样明显扎眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then you're gonna stand out like "Where's Waldo?"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.68,0:00:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[美国儿童杂志上的一款游戏\N读者要在一群人当中找出沃尔多]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.23,0:00:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  沃尔多在哪里不会明显扎眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, "Where's Waldo?" doesn't stand out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.23,0:00:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很难找到他  那正是游戏乐趣所在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's super hard to find. That's the challenge.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.92,0:00:57.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次全家福对我来说很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This portrait is incredibly important to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.35,0:00:58.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  他就叫沃尔多  没有"在哪里"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Also, his name is just "Waldo."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.90,0:01:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我花了好几周时间才选到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I spent weeks trying to find
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.79,0:01:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个每个人都有空的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a time that works for everybody...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.96,0:01:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有合适的摄影师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and finding the right photographer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.31,0:01:07.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我保证会乖乖合作  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So if you could just promise me that you'll cooperate, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.17,0:01:08.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我保证  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I promise. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.66,0:01:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想得真周到  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is amazing that you're doing this. - Mmm, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.62,0:01:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你太棒了  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're wonderful. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.24,0:01:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get in here
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.40,0:01:16.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哎呀使不得  -哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no can do. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.09,0:01:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你  -拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I love you. - Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.13,0:01:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的好内裤哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's my good underwear?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.56,0:01:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题应该是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The question is,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.81,0:01:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你还有烂内裤  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why isn't all your underwear good, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.34,0:01:28.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赚钱那么多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You make a nice living.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.41,0:01:31.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新来的佣人老是把我的内裤和曼尼的弄混\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The new maid keeps mixing up my underwear with Manny's.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.21,0:01:32.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次我随便抓了一条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Put on the first thing I grabbed.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.34,0:01:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧得跟止血带一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was like a crotch tourniquet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.01,0:01:35.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你得跟她说啊  -为什么让我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You gotta talk to her. - Why me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.83,0:01:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你们说一样的语言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hola. You both speak the same language.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.50,0:01:41.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是葡萄牙人  你知不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's Portuguese. Do you know how offensive it is...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.57,0:01:44.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们混为一类人是很不礼貌的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you put all of us in the same mixing pot?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.12,0:01:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  请代我给她道个歉  还告诉她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry. Please apologize to her when you tell her not to
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.40,0:01:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要把我的内裤  -我们语言不通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- put my underwear- - I can't talk to her!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.38,0:01:54.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克呢  -我代替他去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where's Luke? - I'm going instead.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.10,0:01:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克有个家庭作业明天就要交了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke suddenly remembered a school project due tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.52,0:01:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  太不幸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.39,0:01:58.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这对他可能是不错的一课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it's a good lesson for the kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.74,0:02:00.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你作了承诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you make a commitment,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.10,0:02:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你得要兑现  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- you gotta follow through. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.65,0:02:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么作业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is the project?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.90,0:02:05.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要采访一个曾经生活在60年代的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He has to interview somebody who lived through the 1960s.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.71,0:02:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:10.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.72,0:02:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.58,0:02:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我记得我承诺过什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sure. I remember what I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.99,0:02:17.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来吧  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, come on over. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.86,0:02:19.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  你得带曼尼去看比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, you're gonna have to take Manny to the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.72,0:02:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶  曼尼  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yay. Manny, vamos!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.17,0:02:23.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在穿衣服呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm still getting dressed.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.71,0:02:26.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我觉得我减肥有效果了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mom, I think my diet's working.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.47,0:02:28.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我内裤都松了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My underwear won't stay up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.05,0:02:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃  来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, so delicious. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.86,0:02:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不和你去没关系吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you're okay with me not going with you today, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.50,0:02:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人请我周末去婚礼献唱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have been hired to sing at a wedding this weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.10,0:02:56.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在一次精彩的卡拉OK\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was plucked from obscurity
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.99,0:03:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出后被别人选中了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}after a particularly stirring karaoke performance.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.07,0:03:03.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说呢  我也算是专业歌手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I guess you could say I'm a professional singer now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.50,0:03:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是以花代钱付给你的  所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, they're paying you in flowers, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.20,0:03:08.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正就算他们给钱  我也会拿去买花的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I would've blown the money on flowers anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.93,0:03:09.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们倒是省了我的麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're saving me a step.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.97,0:03:12.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说所有的歌后都有人献花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Plus all the great divas are rewarded in flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.49,0:03:15.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后还有支票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're also given paychecks.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.76,0:03:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不大擅长闲聊  所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm really bad at small talk, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.39,0:03:20.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了  没什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I get it. It's not a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.03,0:03:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我看你一早上没说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you sure? 'Cause you've been quiet all morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.46,0:03:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我得酝酿一下我的嗓子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's because I'm resting my instrument.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.50,0:03:26.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.09,0:03:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看他是压力巨大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel tension.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.22,0:03:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科比  科比  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kobe! Kobe, over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.93,0:03:38.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科比  科比  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kobe! Kobe! Over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.68,0:03:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要帮忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What can I do for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.92,0:03:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢当篮球运动员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you like being a basketball player?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.77,0:03:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.02,0:03:48.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我紧张了  我没想到你会往这边看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I choked. I didn't think you'd look up here at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.21,0:03:49.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那下次准备下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Little preparation next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.86,0:03:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用用脑子好好想哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a mental game.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.37,0:03:52.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Duly noted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.41,0:03:54.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  -湖人队入场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. - Your Los Angeles Lakers!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.92,0:04:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -楼梯坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's wrong? - That broken step.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.71,0:04:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家福会因此被毁的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna ruin our whole family portrait.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.29,0:04:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这样想的  我兴奋得不得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, here's my idea. I'm really excited about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.72,0:04:13.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家人都穿白色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The whole extended family, all dressed in white,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.21,0:04:15.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一字从上到下排开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a single-file line down the staircase.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.81,0:04:17.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像高速公路的汽车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, like a line on the highway.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.49,0:04:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.66,0:04:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那跳台滑雪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or, uh, a ski jump.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.77,0:04:21.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.64,0:04:23.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞跳台滑雪干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why- Why would I want a ski jump?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.38,0:04:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.96,0:04:26.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想一家人在一张大床上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My idea was to have the whole family in a giant bed,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.00,0:04:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像威利·旺卡一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like in Willy Wonka.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.00,0:04:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[威利·旺卡  《查理与巧克力工厂》人物]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.19,0:04:29.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简直太"可笑"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but that's ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.72,0:04:31.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是"可口"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Ridiculicious."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.15,0:04:35.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没看到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't see anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.67,0:04:36.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以是我疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I'm crazy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.70,0:04:38.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你  没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You're... not.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.88,0:04:42.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸早该把这个楼梯修好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your father was supposed to fix that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.83,0:04:45.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你对这些小细节太挑剔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, you're obsessing over the tiniest little thing-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.98,0:04:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说你也看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you do see it, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.92,0:04:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就照张相嘛  有什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is the big deal about this one picture?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.13,0:04:51.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you know what,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.10,0:04:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不指望你能理解  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't expect you to understand, but-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.33,0:04:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  等你以后当妈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, when you're a mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.30,0:04:58.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会感到时光如白驹过隙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}everything goes by so quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.57,0:05:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不了多久  卢克就开始刮胡子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In a minute, Luke's gonna be shaving,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:04.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯去上大学  你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Alex is gonna be off at college, and you're gonna be-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.49,0:05:08.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会做一些了不起的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you'll be doing something great.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.83,0:05:13.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想时间定格在这一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just wanna freeze this moment as it is right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.17,0:05:15.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-能理解吧  -能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know? - I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.38,0:05:16.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我平时松松垮垮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I don't show it,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.63,0:05:19.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这个家庭对我来说很重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but this family's still the most important thing-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.00,0:05:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管它呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Screw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.59,0:05:22.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亲自来修\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna fix the bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.04,0:05:24.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒要看看有多难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, seriously, how hard can it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.08,0:05:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老爸能行  那我也能行  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If your father can do it, I can do it. Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.59,0:05:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.83,0:05:29.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just need to...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.09,0:05:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抬起来-\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}lift-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.22,0:05:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我看见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, now I see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.82,0:05:44.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的位置真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These seats are amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.29,0:05:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你口袋里怎么有糖漏出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why you have candy coming out of your pocket?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.06,0:05:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.87,0:05:50.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我自己带了零食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Huh? - I brought my own snacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.72,0:05:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我小气  这是原则问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not because I'm cheap. It's a matter of principle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.13,0:05:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说冒着被人发现的危险其实挺刺激的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Plus I get a little rush from the danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.80,0:05:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定  装酷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Be cool. Be cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.78,0:05:58.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -淡定  看前面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Be cool. Just look straight ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.57,0:06:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉好极了  哦吼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never felt more alive. Whoo!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.54,0:06:08.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我越搞越糟糕  但我没有惊惶失措\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I just made it worse. I'm not freaking out though.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.06,0:06:10.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打电话给你爸  问他怎么修\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna call your dad, and he's gonna tell me how to fix this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.07,0:06:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  是老爸  -哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God! It's Dad. - Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.77,0:06:14.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里  科比的后面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right there, behind Kobe.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.80,0:06:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -真是太少见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my god! - How weird is this!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.47,0:06:18.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点快点  想一件事情来吓他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Quick. Quick, tell me something to say that will freak him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.91,0:06:21.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说我怀孕了  -不  那个可不能乱说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Tell him I'm pregnant. - No, not gonna say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.99,0:06:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,响了响了  真是太有趣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, here we go. How funny is this!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.73,0:06:31.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是菲尔  有事请留言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, it's Phil. You know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.11,0:06:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是"有趣"呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that was pretty funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.50,0:06:43.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.78,0:06:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.00,0:06:50.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.64,0:06:56.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.68,0:07:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.00,0:07:04.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  噢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.27,0:07:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多了  失陪一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's much better. Excuse me. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.44,0:07:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.50,0:07:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里进来一只鸽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There is a pigeon in our house.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.66,0:07:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do I do? What do I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.19,0:07:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谁呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.19,0:07:17.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不搞笑  一点都不搞笑  -冷静\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Never funny. Not funny now. - Calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.58,0:07:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小就是在动物的陪伴下长大的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know I grew up around many animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.12,0:07:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次一只公鸡袭击我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time, a rooster attacked me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.59,0:07:22.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈把它脖子拧了  然后晚上就吃鸡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and my mom wrung its neck, and we had it for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.45,0:07:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真会挑时间讲故事  速回来救我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great time for an anecdote. Help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.65,0:07:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实它更怕你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's more afraid of you than you are of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.39,0:07:28.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸽子什么都不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pigeons aren't scared of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.50,0:07:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电线他们都敢站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They stand on electrical wires.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.22,0:07:33.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会没事的  米奇尔  只要你不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be fine, Mitchell. Just as long as you don't-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.60,0:07:34.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  他们要开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what, they're starting.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.77,0:07:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得挂了  拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gotta go. Okay, bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.54,0:07:38.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我不怎么  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As long as I don't what? Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.07,0:07:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我不怎么  我的个娘亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As long as I don't- Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.53,0:07:44.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷  接吻镜头来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cool. The kiss cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.92,0:07:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果镜头圈到了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wouldn't it be embarrassing if the camera
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.54,0:07:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-会不会很尴尬  -我们是亲戚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- was on us and then the crowd started- - We're related.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.63,0:07:49.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有血缘关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not by blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.70,0:07:51.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢碰我  就让你"血溅当场"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Touch me and there will be blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.53,0:07:57.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们不行  -你怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Not us. - What's wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.69,0:07:58.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是接吻镜头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the kiss cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.43,0:07:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是圈到我们  我们就得接吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When it lands on you, you're supposed to kiss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.30,0:08:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我岳父的二婚妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is my wife's dad's second wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.17,0:08:07.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法律上没问题  但是很怪异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So legally okay, but still weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.87,0:08:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太尴尬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.24,0:08:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we're back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.59,0:08:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  又没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Ay! Come on. It's not a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.63,0:08:28.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了来电显示\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank God for caller I.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.96,0:08:30.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是你不想接你老婆电话就可以挂掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you don't have to talk to your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.67,0:08:33.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我回来收拾你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we're gonna talk, mister.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.43,0:08:35.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会慢慢慢慢说死你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna talk and talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.32,0:08:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  妈妈在电视上看到你了  你死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, Mom saw you on TV. You're dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.52,0:08:46.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的  接吻镜头应该只针对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's the thing. The kiss cam is only supposed to be...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.95,0:08:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现场观众娱乐一下的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for the enjoyment of the people at the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.61,0:08:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视上根本不该播\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They never show that on TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.91,0:08:55.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们在自己的比赛场上做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What people do in the privacy of their own sports arena...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.08,0:08:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他们的自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}should be their own business.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.73,0:09:02.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,66年的时候我在我爷爷的办公品公司打工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So in '66, I worked in my grandfather's office supply business-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.24,0:09:04.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是墨水啊  订书钉啊  纸张之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, your ink, your staples, your legal pads.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.43,0:09:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说得太快了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I going too fast for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.01,0:09:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听得都睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I fell asleep for a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.97,0:09:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在60年代就没做过有意思的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you do anything interesting in the '60s?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.50,0:09:12.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个夏天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, one summer,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.26,0:09:14.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在姥爷的理发店里帮忙扫头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I swept up hair at my other grandfather's barbershop.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.93,0:09:16.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别折磨我了  -你想要什么样的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're killing me. - What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.71,0:09:17.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.79,0:09:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱恩·贝壳维斯的爷爷当年在华盛顿游行过呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brian Beckwith's grandfather marched on Washington.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.55,0:09:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿蒂·贝壳维斯吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Artie Beckwith?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.68,0:09:24.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个整天啰里吧嗦  怨天尤人的怂货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He couldn't walk two feet without complaining.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.49,0:09:26.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他去华盛顿游行过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He marched on Washington?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是这样告诉布莱恩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He told Brian he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.81,0:09:29.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟马丁·路德·金一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}With Martin Luther King Jr.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.49,0:09:30.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马丁·路德·金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Martin Luther King?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.97,0:09:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你以为他的理发师是谁  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Guess who cut his hair. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.68,0:09:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道马丁·路德·金的理发师是谁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know who cut Martin Luther King Jr.'s hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.67,0:09:39.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克的老师怕是也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Neither does Luke's teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.12,0:09:42.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以理发店是在华盛顿啊  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So the barbershop was in Washington? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.14,0:09:45.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还为其他名人理过发吗  -那当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you cut any other famous hair? - Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.20,0:09:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼迪家族  理查德·尼克松  各位宇航员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The Kennedys, Richard Nixon, all the astronauts.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.58,0:09:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为巴斯·奥尔德的外号是哪来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you think Buzz Aldrin got his nickname?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.58,0:09:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[巴斯·奥尔德  人类首次登陆月球的宇航员之一]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.88,0:09:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷毙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.23,0:09:54.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*莉莉的屋里最好玩*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*We love to play in Lily's room*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.14,0:09:56.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*要不要牛奶无所谓*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*We don't need any milk*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.17,0:10:00.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  莉莉  你老爸是铁血真汉子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know what, Lily? I am a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.39,0:10:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸这就去厨房给你拿牛奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am going into the kitchen to get your milk.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.76,0:10:56.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*万福玛利亚*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Ave Maria*
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:04.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*满被圣宠者*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Gratia plena*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.47,0:11:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*玛利亚  满被圣宠者*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Maria, gratia plena*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.37,0:11:19.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*玛利亚  满被圣宠者*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Maria, gratia plena*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.54,0:11:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*圣洁的天主*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Ave, ave dominus*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.63,0:11:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*主与尔偕焉*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Dominus tecum*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.54,0:11:40.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*女中尔为赞美*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Benedicta tu in mulieribus*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.56,0:11:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*尔胎子耶稣*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Et benedictus fructus ventris*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.55,0:11:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*并为赞美*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Ventris tui, Jesus*
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.36,0:12:12.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*万福玛利亚*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Ave Maria*
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.70,0:12:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次  威尔特·张伯伦来光顾了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then one day, Wilt Chamberlain shows up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.70,0:12:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[威尔特·张伯伦  美国男篮巨星]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.36,0:12:23.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说"你能帮忙修下我朋友的头发吗"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He says, "Can you take a little off the top for my friend here?"
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.39,0:12:25.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-竟然是猫王艾维斯  -不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And it's Elvis. - No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.46,0:12:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是世上最了不起的歌手  除了西纳特拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Greatest singer that ever lived, after Sinatra.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.77,0:12:29.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁敢反驳我就跟他急\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll fight any man who says different.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.50,0:12:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爸说最棒的歌手是彼柏·布莱森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad says the greatest singer who ever lived is Peabo Bryson.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.05,0:12:34.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我只好找你老爸算算账了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then I guess I gotta fight your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.05,0:12:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.20,0:12:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克说外公要找你算账\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke says Grandpa wants to fight you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.93,0:12:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛什么都跟我过不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why does everything have to suck?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.33,0:12:58.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是改天照相吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's just do the picture another day.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脸上马上要冒痘痘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I'm getting a pimple.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.34,0:13:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.92,0:13:03.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我多辛苦才约到那位摄影师吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know how long it took me to book this photographer?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.16,0:13:06.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在壁炉那里照怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe by the fireplace.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.23,0:13:11.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  旧时代的老人都喜欢在那儿画塑像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. That's a classic old-person spot for a portrait.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.00,0:13:13.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉倒吧  墙的颜色太恶心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, if I'd ever bothered to paint that hideous wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.83,0:13:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔是个完美主义者  这有时候是好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire is a perfectionist, which sometimes is a good thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.24,0:13:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如选个绝代老公什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like when it comes to picking a husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.55,0:13:21.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候就不太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes it's a bad thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.76,0:13:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如大家都觉得某样东西很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like when everyone else sees something beautiful...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.67,0:13:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而她的眼里就只有那些丁点大的瑕疵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and all she sees is the teeny-tiny flaw.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.13,0:13:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  坚决不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.18,0:13:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.98,0:13:36.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我的房子遭殃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. My house is a disaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.86,0:13:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能在你那里拍照吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we do this picture at your place?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.93,0:13:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  怕是不太可能了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that's- that's not gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.94,0:13:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.13,0:13:53.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再缠一圈吧  粘紧点  用点力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe one more layer. And tight, really tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.08,0:13:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  能再催催他们吗  -刚打过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad, can you call them again? - I just did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.51,0:13:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在路上了  比赛打进加时赛了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're on their way. Game went into overtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.55,0:13:58.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但是太阳都快落山了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, but we're losing the light,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.79,0:13:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且摄影师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the photographer's
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.42,0:14:01.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10分钟后还要去个犹太男孩成人仪式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}gotta get to a bar mitzvah in 10 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.20,0:14:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红酒  现在  你不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, red wine. Really? Now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.04,0:14:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, honey,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.64,0:14:05.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你有点太神经质了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you're getting a little too uptight about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.17,0:14:08.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我呼吸困难了  -你没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's hard to breathe. - Oh, you're fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.63,0:14:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把他怎么了  他脸都绿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What'd you do to him? He's turning blue.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.02,0:14:11.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要他的衣服是白色的就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But his clothes will stay white.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.29,0:14:15.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们回来咯  -谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We're home! - Oh, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.25,0:14:16.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  我们换衣服去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, let's go change.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.90,0:14:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  又看见我美丽的贤妻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, there's my beautiful wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.82,0:14:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你生我的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know you're mad at me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.88,0:14:22.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道这泡沫手指无法弥补我的过错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I know this foam finger can't make up for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.93,0:14:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你赶紧换衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you just go change,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.89,0:14:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那事儿我们回头再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we'll talk about what you did later.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.61,0:14:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  谢谢你买票给我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, thank you so much for those tickets.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.97,0:14:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚说你们玩得很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria tells me you had a real good time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.71,0:14:30.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没没  我可没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not really. No, I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.97,0:14:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上苍作证  我爱你女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}God, I love your daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.85,0:14:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到时候再回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should- I should come by
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.18,0:14:35.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲下这台阶  修好这台阶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and kiss that step- fix that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.62,0:14:39.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的好像我是故意把家里弄得一团糟一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you're acting like I wanted to destroy the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.09,0:14:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是觉得奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I just think it's odd
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.52,0:14:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你毁掉的大部分东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that the majority of things you destroyed...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.16,0:14:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我妈送给我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}were sent to us by my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.27,0:14:44.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.28,0:14:46.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说我和那臭脏鸟周旋的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So while I'm fighting off that filthy creature,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.06,0:14:48.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会有时间停下来想  哎呀真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I actually stop and say, "Oh, you know what,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.04,0:14:50.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算可以借机毁掉那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}here's the opportunity I've always been looking for
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.08,0:14:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庸俗不堪的东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to destroy our kitschiest objects."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.81,0:14:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庸俗不堪  她听到一定会很"开心"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kitschiest? Oh, she's gonna love that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.05,0:14:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实如果你跟着我去婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you would've come with me to the wedding,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.83,0:14:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都不会发生了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}none of this would have happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.00,0:14:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真生气了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. So you are angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.12,0:14:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.26,0:15:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讨厌扯家常  还不喜欢鸟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're terrified of small talk and birds.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.49,0:15:01.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定很庆幸那小鸽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're just lucky that pigeon
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.48,0:15:03.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没缠着你聊天气状况吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}didn't want to chat you up about the weather.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.13,0:15:04.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  杰  -你们也好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello, Jay. - Hello, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.02,0:15:08.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你怎么穿得跟"舞迷"节目的选手似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. Oh, you look like the guy from Dance Fever.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.82,0:15:09.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢夸奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.38,0:15:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼·特里奥  俄亥俄州克里夫兰市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Deney Terrio. Cleveland, Ohio.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.38,0:15:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}["舞迷"节目的主持人]
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.60,0:15:13.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  非要这样吗  我不是在夸你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, really? That is not a compliment.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.93,0:15:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以之前我才让你先穿上试试  转过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why I wanted you to try those on earlier. Turn around.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.75,0:15:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不能拍照  我的痘痘越发明显了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The picture can't happen today. My pimple's getting worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.75,0:15:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可怜的小宝贝  你还能站着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey, I am so sorry. Can you stand?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.36,0:15:23.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-能  -那就得拍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Well, then the picture's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.61,0:15:25.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一定会紧盯着我不放的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's all anybody's gonna see.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.48,0:15:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看可不一定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.52,0:15:31.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见她穿的裙子了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you get a look at her dress?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.39,0:15:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  我看她裙子干嘛  我爱的是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Why would I look at her dress? I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.90,0:15:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲太太  太阳就快下山了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, Mrs. Dunphy, the sun is setting.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.12,0:15:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  这就拍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Yeah, this is happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.97,0:15:39.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  快来  我们出去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody, come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.10,0:15:41.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点  我下午才给家具刷了漆摆外边呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Be careful. I stained some furniture out there this afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.94,0:15:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是嘛  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course you did, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.16,0:15:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么需要注意的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anything else I need to know about?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.46,0:15:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准旁边邻居正忙着打彩弹呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe the neighbors on either side are having a paintball fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.98,0:15:49.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都看好了  我那睿智无比的老爹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now watch this. Dad, in his infinite wisdom,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.59,0:15:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天给家具刷了漆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}stained furniture today.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.74,0:15:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别碰着了  还没干呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't touch it. It's wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.17,0:15:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快点快点  -别照了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hurry, hurry. - Put that down, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.24,0:15:56.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好  大家都过来了  现在站这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Okay, we got it. Now we're gonna go out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.48,0:16:00.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  你在耍我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.17,0:16:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那洒水器怎么关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do- How do you turn the sprinklers off?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.95,0:16:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又问我  当然了  就因为我是拉丁人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay! Of course! Because I'm Latina,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.09,0:16:06.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就该对花园  洒水器什么的了如指掌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm supposed to know everything about gardening and sprinklers!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.91,0:16:08.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们装这东西的时候就你在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were here when they installed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.09,0:16:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是诶  控制器在草坪那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, yeah. The box is across the yard.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.45,0:16:14.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说要跨过这片黄浦江吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean your now-soaking-wet yard?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.36,0:16:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好  彻底歇菜了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's great. We are screwed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.79,0:16:17.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  还没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.38,0:16:19.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没出秘密武器呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We haven't unwrapped our secret weapon yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.24,0:16:23.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拆弹特工--卢克小神童过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke walks over there, Hurt Locker style...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.89,0:16:25.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关掉开关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}flips the switch,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.75,0:16:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘭  或者不嘭  水就关了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and boom- or not boom- water off.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.87,0:16:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好男儿志当英雄  儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Put the "he" in "hero," son.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.38,0:16:42.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拆弹专家  洒水器终结者还差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hurt Locker? It's more like Squirt Locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.83,0:16:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  不搞笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? That wasn't funny?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.40,0:16:47.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真同情你们这群没幽默感的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I actually pity you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.31,0:16:54.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没空庆祝了  都给我停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No time to celebrate! Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.06,0:16:57.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们时间不多了  -好的  大家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We don't have a lot of time. - All right, everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.25,0:16:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请小个子的站前面  -先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- If I can have the little ones down front- - You know what, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.22,0:17:00.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不介意的话  我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you don't mind, I've got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.70,0:17:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙  都过来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, people, let's get out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.08,0:17:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  艾丽克斯  你们给弟弟拆胶带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, Alex, I need you to unwrap your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.68,0:17:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲一家站这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, I need the Dunphys over on this side.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.44,0:17:08.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  你站中间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, you're in the middle.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.88,0:17:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  小卡  莉莉站那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, Cam, Lily on this end. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.65,0:17:14.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听我说  -怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Listen. - Uh-huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.93,0:17:18.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我错了  如果你再次投入我怀抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I screwed up, but if ever you're in my arms again-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.96,0:17:20.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  现在不说这些  -就得现在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil, not now. - Yes, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.60,0:17:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想日后看到这张照片时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to look at this picture...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.65,0:17:23.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如我80岁  而你早已与世长辞的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I'm 80 years old and you're long dead...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.32,0:17:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想到你拍照时心里深藏的怒气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and know that you were angry at me when we took it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.12,0:17:26.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  回头再说行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, we'll talk about what you did later.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.68,0:17:28.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大家  请看这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, everybody. Eyes over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.71,0:17:30.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不关我的事  是她亲的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't do anything. She kissed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.37,0:17:32.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.83,0:17:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁亲了你  -歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who kissed you? - Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.88,0:17:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -是接吻镜头[同音:亲了小卡]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - It was the kiss cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.29,0:17:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你亲小卡做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why did you kiss Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.34,0:17:40.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我亲了菲尔  他说必须那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I kissed Phil. He told me I had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.44,0:17:42.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是这样的  -等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, no. - Okay, hang on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.21,0:17:43.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在你无视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was this before or after
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.60,0:17:45.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆电话之前还是之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you ignored the phone call from your wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.31,0:17:47.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个你也看见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You saw that too?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.11,0:17:50.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就不能先把相照了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could we please just take the damn picture?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.44,0:17:53.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大伙  再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Everybody, one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.36,0:17:55.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道吗  我很生你的气  -我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just so you know, I am angry with you. - I knew it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.62,0:17:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我靠  -今天对我来说很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, damn it! - It was a big day for me,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.03,0:18:00.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他不参加的原因是他不喜欢扯家常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he didn't want to go because he doesn't like small talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.08,0:18:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你们这些小吵小闹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would it be terribly inconvenient...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.97,0:18:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推迟那么几分钟就有那么难吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to just postpone this hissy fit for a few minutes?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.23,0:18:06.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  或许我们根本就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ok, you know what? Maybe some of us don't
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.08,0:18:07.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不想今天拍照  -多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- want to take a picture today. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.49,0:18:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And please, Claire,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.28,0:18:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逼米奇尔做他不想做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}don't try to make Mitchell do something he doesn't wanna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.26,0:18:12.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴吧  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, shut up, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.51,0:18:14.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, stop it! Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.36,0:18:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都听好了  我真的好不容易才筹划好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everyone, listen. This took me forever to put together,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.11,0:18:18.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我真的不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I don't really care
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.84,0:18:21.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁亲了谁  谁额头上长了痘痘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who kissed who and who's got a pimple on her head...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.83,0:18:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者谁穿了超级不得体的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and who is wearing an outrageously inappropriate dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.28,0:18:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要打起精神  假装一切正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We are gonna get together and act like a normal family...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.15,0:18:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持续十分之一秒就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for one-tenth of a freaking second,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.16,0:18:31.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就这么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we're gonna do it right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.12,0:18:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快点  -别碰我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on, let's go. - Get your hands off of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.88,0:18:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不  就不  你怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No. Make me. Make me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.95,0:18:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒唐了  你们两个对每件事都那么纠结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, this is ridiculous. You're both uptight about everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.27,0:18:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想陪他去参加婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You didn't want to go to a wedding with him
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.87,0:18:42.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为不愿意和别人聊天是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you didn't want to make small talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.70,0:18:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这样认识歌洛莉亚的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's how I met Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.00,0:18:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我对你说的第一句话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you remember the first thing I said to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.73,0:18:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得  "我喜欢巧克力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. "I like chocolate,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.29,0:18:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢水果  但不喜欢两样加在一起"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like fruit, but not together."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.57,0:18:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常青藤高材生  你忍不了是吗  还有你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You couldn't come up with that, lvy League? And you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.43,0:18:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是不那么完美主义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You would be a lot happier if you weren't
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.14,0:18:57.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会活得开心得多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so obsessed with everything being perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.16,0:18:59.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧我们一身白  什么东西  板球队吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at us here all in white. What are we, a cricket team?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.96,0:19:03.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你吧  生活本就不完美  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}News flash. Life is not perfect, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.40,0:19:05.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在都给我冷静下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now calm the hell down.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.49,0:19:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧老爸  很好  对你来说当然轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Dad, that's great, and that's really easy for you to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.56,0:19:11.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你以为是我想这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But do you think I like being like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.17,0:19:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.30,0:19:13.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果你有什么良方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So if you have some quick-and-easy fix,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.89,0:19:15.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何不现在就说来听听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why don't you just give it to me right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.19,0:19:24.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  -我的老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Jay! - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.31,0:19:26.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I got this, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.02,0:19:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你干  你干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. What did- What did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.06,0:19:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在两个人都弄脏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now two people are dirty.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.09,0:19:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, three.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.99,0:19:35.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你自找的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.27,0:19:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你说"庸俗不堪"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's for "Kitschy."
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.53,0:19:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泥巴大战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mud fight!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  别别  停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Don't do that. No, no, no! Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.70,0:19:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都站好  都听话  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody get back in line. Come on, guys, stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.70,0:19:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it. Damn it! Guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.47,0:19:53.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.96,0:19:56.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底拍不拍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are we still doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.60,0:19:58.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不拍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, we're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.38,0:20:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在拍吧  -准备好咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Now we are. - We're ready!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.13,0:20:16.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说"茄子"  -"茄子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Say "cheese." - Say "cheese"!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.13,0:20:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,68年我在理发店扫头发的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Back in '68, when I was sweeping up hair in that barbershop,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.88,0:20:22.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾幻想今后自己家庭的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had this mental picture of the family that,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.03,0:20:23.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果够走运的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I was lucky enough,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.39,0:20:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天我会坐拥完美的妻子  完美的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}one day I would end up with- perfect wife, perfect kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.34,0:20:29.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果呢  我没那运气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess what. I didn't get any of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.71,0:20:31.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后捞到这么一群二货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wound up with this sorry bunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.16,0:20:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我每天都对此充满感激\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm thankful for that every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.35,0:20:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分时候吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, most days.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.80,0:20:40.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是就提猫王艾维斯的事好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I'm just gonna go with the Elvis stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.40,0:20:41.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换我也会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. I would.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.31,0:20:48.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右边点  右边点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, to the right. To the right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.26,0:20:50.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微往左一点点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A skosh to the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.41,0:20:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.89,0:20:54.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管了  反正重刷墙壁的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whatever. I'm gonna have to take the picture down
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.55,0:20:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是得把这幅照片取下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I repaint the wall anyhow.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.84,0:20:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杀了我吧  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Kill me now. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.24,0:21:02.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是太幸运了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't know how I got so lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.28,0:21:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.53,0:21:07.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我喜欢这张照片  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I love that picture. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.75,0:21:13.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-相框那里是有个缺口吗  -没有没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is that a chip on the frame right there? - No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.93,0:21:15.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看得到  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can see it. - Honey.

