[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.09,0:02:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.09,0:02:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.09,0:02:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十六集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.74,0:00:06.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最怕什么  让我想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What am I most afraid of? Hmm. Let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.09,0:00:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球变暖  还有考试拿B\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Global warming... and getting a "B."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.22,0:00:11.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午夜凶铃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The phone ringing in the middle of the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.22,0:00:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕自己太过追求完美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That I'm too much of a perfectionist.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.97,0:00:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  这不是应聘面试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, this isn't a job interview.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.97,0:00:18.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.98,0:00:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最怕应聘面试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Job interviews.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.98,0:00:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我无所畏惧  -对哦  那鸽子呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing. - Yeah, right. What about the pigeons?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.11,0:00:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢鸽子  太奸诈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I don't like them. They're shifty.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.32,0:00:29.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-失去米奇尔  -噢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Losing Mitchell. - Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.09,0:00:33.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-酒店床单  -呃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hotel bedspreads. - Ooh.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.46,0:00:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿不到驾照\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Never getting my driver's license.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.83,0:00:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是驾照上的照片很丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or getting one and the picture sucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.54,0:00:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤独终老\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dying alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.05,0:00:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  亲爱的  找到你的鞋了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Haley, sweetie, did you find your shoes?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.84,0:00:44.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  拜托今天别烦我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, please, not today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.94,0:00:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想知道你找到鞋没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just wanted to know if you found your shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.67,0:00:49.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别缠着我了  我现在紧张死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you hounding me? I'm freaking out right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.64,0:00:51.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松  不过是路考而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You need to relax. It's just a driver's test.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.98,0:00:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的第三次路考  如果再考不过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's my third driver's test, and if I fail again,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.64,0:00:57.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要等六个月才能再考\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have to wait six months to retake it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.14,0:00:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意味着还要坐半年你开的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's six more months of you driving me everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.24,0:01:01.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就说"我绝对不会穿的"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then I'm, like, "There's no way I'm wearing that."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.80,0:01:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她就说"如果你不穿  -别老说"就"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And she was, like. "Well, if you don't wear it, -Like
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.18,0:01:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就没得玩"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then you can't play."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.19,0:01:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后我就说"我无所谓"  -亲爱的  就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And then I was, like, "That's fine by me." - Honey, like.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.77,0:01:08.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后她就说"如果你不玩"  -就就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And then she was, like, "Well, if you don't play" - Like! Like!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.11,0:01:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈  -别老说"就"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mom! -Stop! Stop saying "Like" All the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.41,0:01:13.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别给我丢脸  -别说了  就就就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're embarrassing me! - Stop it! Like, like, like, like, aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.38,0:01:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  我找到你的外套了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley. Found your jacket.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.71,0:01:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么都跟我过不去  我的神啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is everyone on me? God!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.55,0:01:24.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别管她  -她一心不能二用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ignore her. - She can't focus on two things at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对司机来说倒是好品质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Always a good quality in a driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.19,0:01:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  我们得去给你买今晚穿的舞鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, we need to get you some shoes for the dance tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.39,0:01:30.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要  我不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we don't. I'm not going.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.84,0:01:31.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:33.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不去跳舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would you not be going to the dance?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.83,0:01:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为学校的舞会很没劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because school dances are lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.66,0:01:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群稚嫩男生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A bunch of immature boys
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.39,0:01:39.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表面上假装成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}trying to impress you with how cool they are...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.56,0:01:41.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实则是乳臭未干的呆瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when they're really just a bunch of dorks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.44,0:01:43.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好去下面探险了吗  伙伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ready to go down under, mate?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.52,0:01:45.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.29,0:01:49.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Treasure hunting.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.71,0:01:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几天前  有线电视修理工去了屋子下面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A few days ago, the cable guy was under the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.68,0:01:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走的时候  跟海莉说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When he was leaving, he said to Haley,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.02,0:01:58.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"哇  下面的藏品真丰富"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Wow. That's quite a collection you've got down there."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.19,0:02:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是  我们不知道下面有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's the thing. We have no idea what he's talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.61,0:02:04.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个星期以来  卢克和我越来越好奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All week, Luke and I have been getting more and more
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.47,0:02:06.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些东西是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}excited about what it could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.81,0:02:09.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是很酷的旧杂志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bet it's really cool old magazines.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.47,0:02:13.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能  或者是动物牙齿做的项链\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Or a bunch of necklaces made out of animal teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.35,0:02:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是虫子琥珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or bugs frozen in amber.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.60,0:02:17.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是几瓶好酒呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if it's really expensive bottles of wine?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.52,0:02:19.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是一套盔甲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or a suit of armor.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.86,0:02:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是古老的印第安箭头呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if there's ancient Indian arrowheads under there?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.16,0:02:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说不定是金条呢  -你觉得是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What if it's gold bars? - Oh, you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.28,0:02:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊  你们为什么不直接去下面看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For God sakes, why don't you go under the house and look?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.85,0:02:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  这个娃娃从哪来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Cam. Cam, where did we get this dolly from?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.35,0:02:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珍妮丝和奥利维亚给的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From Janice and Olivia.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.41,0:02:53.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们昨天拿过来的  莉莉很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They brought it over yesterday. Lily loves it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.60,0:02:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有太多"蕾丝边"了  就跟她们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seems a little frilly, you know, coming from them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.99,0:02:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为她们是拉拉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, because they're lesbians?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.24,0:02:59.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这是偏见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's sort of an offense stereotype, don't you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.35,0:03:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I suppose. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.26,0:03:03.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们把咖啡机还回来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hey, did they bring back our coffee maker?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.60,0:03:05.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  太大了  她们是骑摩托车过来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It was too big. They were on their motorcycle.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.65,0:03:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们跟莉莉的儿科医生初次见面时很尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We got off to an awkward start with our pediatrician,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.84,0:03:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个热心的亚裔女性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a very nice Asian lady-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.06,0:03:11.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别走题  -叫作缪拉医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Irrelevant. - Named Dr. Miura.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.77,0:03:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我冒昧请她过来吃早午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I took the bold step of inviting her over for brunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.19,0:03:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  你说冒昧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. Uh, bold?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.11,0:03:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说之前没有病人请过她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She said no patient had ever done it before.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.88,0:03:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  潜台词就是"这很奇怪"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Subtext, "This is weird."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.46,0:03:23.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不觉得有潜台词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't hear any subtext.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.76,0:03:25.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也觉得没有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you hear any now?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.47,0:03:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不知道为什么要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't even know why we're doing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.89,0:03:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为万一哪天莉莉病了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because what if Lily gets sick
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.67,0:03:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抗病毒药又短缺了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and there's a Tamiflu shortage?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.93,0:03:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得谁会拿到药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who do you think's gonna get that medicine?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.73,0:03:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是她喜欢的病人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The patient she likes, that's who.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.48,0:03:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你给她烤个蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, maybe if you bake her a cake,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.97,0:03:39.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许就能免费照X光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she'll give us free X-rays.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.27,0:03:40.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要套近乎  搞好交情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's all about making connections.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.86,0:03:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为牙医为什么老免费送我东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you think the dentist gives me all that free stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.11,0:03:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他是个女王受  对你情深难自拔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, because he's a huge queen and he has a big crush on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.70,0:03:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  你这么觉得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Do you think so?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.72,0:03:52.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈妈  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mom? - Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.48,0:03:53.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发烧了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a fever.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.60,0:03:55.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  过来让我摸摸看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, mi amor. Come here and I feel you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.56,0:03:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想传染给你  可能会致命的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh. I don't wanna get you sick. It could be fatal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.71,0:03:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那站在我身边就可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then by all means, stand next to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.24,0:04:02.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我量一下你的体温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me feel you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.53,0:04:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你没有发烧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, papi, but you're not warm.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.78,0:04:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是因为你在做饭  手温高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, probably because you were cooking and your hands are warm.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.75,0:04:12.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天还是不去参加派对了  安全起见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I better skip the party tomorrow just to be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:15.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  明天的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Yeah, the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.38,0:04:18.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -派对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - The party.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.05,0:04:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只明白了五分之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I understand about 20% of what goes on around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.30,0:04:24.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的派对在游乐场举办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The party is at an amusement park,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼怕坐过山车  -可怜的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and Manny's afraid of roller coasters. - Poor kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.72,0:04:29.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道他的胆小是遗传谁的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know where he gets his fear from...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.23,0:04:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的爸爸什么都不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because his father's not afraid of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.23,0:04:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕公牛  不恐高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No bulls, no heights,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.65,0:04:34.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕电梯和高速行驶的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}no helicopters, no fast cars-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.48,0:04:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是跟他一起去吃饭  等结账的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But go to dinner with him and wait for the check to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.98,0:04:39.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以从他眼里看到恐惧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then you'll see fear in his eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.28,0:04:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像服务生是鬼似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like the waiter's a ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.81,0:04:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-兴奋吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Excited? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.58,0:04:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就像庞塞·德莱昂和他儿子小庞塞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're like Ponce de Leon and his son, Little Ponce.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.58,0:04:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[庞塞·德莱昂  15世纪西班牙探险家]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.96,0:04:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们是谁  -著名的寻宝家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Who's that? - Famous treasure hunters.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.88,0:04:55.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫庞塞  他在我们学校会被嘲笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His name was Ponce? He'd get made fun of at my school.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.55,0:04:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能会叫他"瓶塞"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They'd probably call him "Pants."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.43,0:05:00.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓶塞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.43,0:05:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者"高级皮条客"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or maybe, um, "Fancy Ponce."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.68,0:05:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个说得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's a good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.60,0:05:06.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.14,0:05:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吧  爸爸  -恩  我还好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You okay, Dad? - Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.61,0:05:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  这个算什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yep. Gonna take a little more
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.57,0:05:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困在黑漆漆的小洞里  与野兽共舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}than getting trapped in a small, dark space with a wild animal
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.20,0:05:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可吓不到你老爸  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- to rattle your old man. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.86,0:05:20.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当父亲的永远都不想在孩子面前露怯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never want your kids to see you scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.69,0:05:21.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想成为他们心中的坚石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna be that rock
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.98,0:05:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在暴风来临时让他们依靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that they can grab ahold of in a stormy sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.87,0:05:27.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  石头会沉底  那就当漂浮的石头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, a rock would sink. So a floating rock.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.04,0:05:32.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新说一遍  风很大  你有很多张纸在手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's start over. It's windy, and you've got a lot of papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.29,0:05:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Let's do this, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.01,0:05:40.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  侦查成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay! Good recon.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.05,0:05:42.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道地形了  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got the lay of the land, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.10,0:05:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不进去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aren't we going in?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.18,0:05:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yep, we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.85,0:05:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是用上滑雪护目镜和烧烤工具会更有趣吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But won't it be fun if we did it with ski goggles and barbecue tools?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.65,0:05:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-应该是的  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I guess. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.86,0:05:55.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就这么干  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. Let's do that. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.82,0:06:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说你这身衣服真好看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I just say that is a lovely outfit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.24,0:06:01.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.15,0:06:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不穿白大褂挺好看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's just nice to see you out of your lab coat.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.37,0:06:05.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你身材很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You actually have quite a nice figure.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.62,0:06:06.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take it down a notch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.27,0:06:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是在结交朋友  不是找3P伙伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're trying to make a friend, not initiate a three-way.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.38,0:06:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉看起来很健康\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily looks great.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.90,0:06:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think so?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.97,0:06:16.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的牙齿不够多吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shouldn't she have more teeth?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.11,0:06:17.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看公园里跑来跑去的孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see these kids running around at the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.66,0:06:18.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牙齿锋利得像鲨鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they look like sharks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.47,0:06:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  她很好  是不是呀莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry. She's perfect. Aren't you, Lily?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.52,0:06:24.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跟你一起好乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, look how calm she is with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.56,0:06:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般见到生人她都没这么安静的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's usually very fidgety around new people.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.88,0:06:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她大概是觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just think she senses
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.10,0:06:28.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会是她在平日里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're gonna be a good friend for her...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.07,0:06:32.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和流感季节的好朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}during good times and- and flu season.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.29,0:06:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.00,0:06:37.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚刚...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did she just-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.66,0:06:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚刚说...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did she just say-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.88,0:06:42.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她开口说的第一个字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, her first word...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.04,0:06:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是每一个男同父亲最糟的噩梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was every gay father's worst nightmare.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.34,0:06:47.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"妈咪"  -心绞痛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "Mommy." - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.43,0:06:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  他不承认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, he won't admit it,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.01,0:06:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我知道曼尼因为错过派对而伤心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I know that Manny's sad because he's missing the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.92,0:06:58.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们带他出去散散心吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't we take him somewhere to take his mind off it, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.28,0:07:00.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道他怕过山车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could have guessed he'd have trouble with roller coasters.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.26,0:07:01.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次他坐在理发店的转椅上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That kid gets woozy at barbershops
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.86,0:07:03.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店员把他转向镜子  他都会头晕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when they spin his chair towards the mirror.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.51,0:07:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带他去码头钓鱼怎么样  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How about we take him to the pier and go fishing, huh? Manny!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.89,0:07:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他喜欢钓鱼  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He likes to fish? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.98,0:07:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的祖上都是渔夫和走私贩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He comes from a long line of fishermen and smugglers.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.75,0:07:14.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我支持钓鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I encourage the fishing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.11,0:07:15.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你喜欢钓鱼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you like to fish?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.35,0:07:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钓鱼  喜欢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fishing? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.24,0:07:19.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天想去码头吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to go to the pier today?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.96,0:07:22.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是要测试我有没有生病吗  -不是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is this a trick to see if I'm really sick? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.85,0:07:26.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许新鲜空气会让你好受点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe the fresh air will make you feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.51,0:07:28.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好啊  因为没有什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then yeah, 'cause there's no place
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.08,0:07:29.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-能让我更加...  -滚去拿你的外套吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- where I'm more at one with  - just get your coat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.71,0:07:32.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你紧张吗  -闭嘴艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you nervous? - Shut up, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.72,0:07:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是问问  换做我肯定会紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just asking. I'd be nervous if I were you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.22,0:07:37.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  别惹你姐姐  她没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, leave your sister alone. She's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.35,0:07:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不是同一个监考员  他很刻薄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As long as I don't get the same guy. He's so mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.72,0:07:41.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很可能会遇上  -不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You probably will. - You won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.31,0:07:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他讨厌我  -他不讨厌你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He hates me. -He doesn't hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.11,0:07:45.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他吼我  -你把车开到灌木丛里去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He yelled at me. - You drove into the bushes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.75,0:07:48.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  是他  别叫我  别叫我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. It's him. Please don't be for me. Please don't be for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.82,0:07:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我  别叫我  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please don't be for me. Please don't be me. Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.90,0:07:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.11,0:07:58.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来  我待会还有事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, come on. I don't have all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.87,0:08:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吐了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna throw up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.47,0:08:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的  你这样办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, no. This is what you're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.96,0:08:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你进到车里  系好安全带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna get in that car, put on your seat belt...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.93,0:08:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸三下  放松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and take three deep breaths and relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.14,0:08:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙每天见几百个小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This guy sees hundreds of kids every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.20,0:08:10.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他很可能不记得你了好吗  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He probably doesn't even remember you, all right? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.48,0:08:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了  两次不过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yo. Let's move it, two strikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.85,0:08:18.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不止三下深呼吸了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's more than three breaths, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.43,0:08:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次好多了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See how much better this is?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.26,0:08:25.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把卡车放进去  拍摄视频\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The truck goes in. It gets video.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.20,0:08:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就能知道下面有什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then we get a preview of whatever's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.77,0:08:28.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多妙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How ingenious is that, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.16,0:08:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是害怕不敢进去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you just scared to go in?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.27,0:08:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would you say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.49,0:08:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把头伸进去的时候  尖叫了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, when you stuck your head in, you screamed a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.77,0:08:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说了  那是房子的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told you. That was the house settling.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.60,0:08:41.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说这样酷多了  航天航空局就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Besides, this is so much cooler. This is how NASA does it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.44,0:08:43.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在把迷你读书灯递给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, hand me the ltty Bitty Book Light.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.31,0:08:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  这就完工了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Final piece of the puzzle.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.62,0:08:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Blast off.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.33,0:08:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  -恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Dad?  - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.42,0:09:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道路  你怎么控制车的方向呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How are you supposed to steer if you don't know where you're going?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.63,0:09:03.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时刻注意着  靠感觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stay in the present, buddy. Gotta do it by feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.94,0:09:07.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像绝地武士那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gotta get all Jedi on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.18,0:09:20.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把我的车弄丢了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you just lose my truck? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.83,0:09:22.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把我的车弄丢了  -我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You just lost my truck! - No, I didn't!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.54,0:09:24.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的车  外公才送给我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was my truck! Grandpa just gave it to me!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.59,0:09:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟你说了要时刻注意着的  -别吼我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I told you to stay in the present! - Stop yelling!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.47,0:09:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-休战  -好的  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Truce? - Yeah. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.51,0:09:38.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is delicious.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.52,0:09:39.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.12,0:09:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食谱来自《已故美食家》杂志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The recipe's from the now-defunct Gourmet magazine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.10,0:09:45.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何我所爱之物都要离我而去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do all the things I love go away?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.11,0:09:49.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  我觉得她没说那个词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I don't even think she said the "M" Word.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.40,0:09:51.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们听到了  再清楚不过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we heard it. It was clear as day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.35,0:09:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我们做错了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I just don't know what we've done wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.70,0:09:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特地辞职在家里带她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I quit my job so I could stay at home with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.71,0:09:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这还不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But maybe it's not enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.99,0:10:01.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们没能满足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe we're not providing her
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.14,0:10:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她需要的女性气息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the feminine energy that she needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.93,0:10:09.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我觉得你不必太放在心上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I wouldn't be too concerned about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.73,0:10:11.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这是因为你是亚洲人  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You- You know it's because you're Asian, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.02,0:10:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  -不  抱歉  什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cam. - No, I'm sorry. What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.63,0:10:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该对房间里的"大熊猫"视而不见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I just supposed to ignore the giant panda in the room?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.91,0:10:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊猫是中国的  而我...算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pandas are from China. I- Well, it doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.78,0:10:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我这位歇斯底里的伴侣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, okay. I think what my hysterical partner
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.56,0:10:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想说  我就替你说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is just trying to say, if I may,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.57,0:10:27.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉生命的前六个月里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that for the first six months of her life,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.74,0:10:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在孤儿院由一位热心的亚洲女性抚养\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily was raised by very loving Asian women, in an orphanage,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.65,0:10:33.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和莉莉的感情很深\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with whom she clearly bonded.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.51,0:10:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你带着你的亚洲气息来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then suddenly you come in with all of your Asian-ness...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.68,0:10:41.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及胸部  子宫  女性特征\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and-and breasts and womb, lady bits-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.18,0:10:44.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唤起了她的回忆  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it all just comes rushing back to her, and I-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.39,0:10:46.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真的是反应过度了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys are overreacting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.18,0:10:51.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉肯定只是随意发出了两个音节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure Lily just strung a couple of random syllables together,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.27,0:10:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来刚好像那个词而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they happen to sound something like that word.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.02,0:10:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.70,0:11:00.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真的这么想吗  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you really think that? - Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.37,0:11:01.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说的对  她说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's right. She's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.85,0:11:02.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们太可笑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're being ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.95,0:11:04.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们太可笑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're being ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.10,0:11:06.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的爸爸们很可笑哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your daddies are being ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.00,0:11:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.00,0:11:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Well-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.50,0:11:13.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔克先生  -不不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mr. Tucker  - No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.15,0:11:16.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她做出了决定  她要个妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's made her choice! She's made her choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.00,0:11:18.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  左转  -在这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right, left turn. - Here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.22,0:11:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  在十字路口  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- At the intersection, yeah. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Left.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.10,0:11:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我说左转  但是你右转了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - I said left. You're going right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.85,0:11:29.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  我在努力了好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. No, wait. I'm trying, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.07,0:11:29.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠边停车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pull over.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.77,0:11:32.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我做得到的  -立刻靠边停车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, I can do this! - Pull over now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.40,0:11:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哭什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you crying?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.84,0:11:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么讨厌我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you hate me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.99,0:11:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要命  海莉  我不讨厌你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hell. Haley, I don't hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.11,0:11:44.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去是个好女孩  让我想起了我女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You seem like a nice girl. You remind me of my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.24,0:11:47.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我希望你快乐长寿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which is why I want you to live a long and happy life...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.20,0:11:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全行车  不要伤到我女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and be safe and not hurt my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.42,0:11:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很想拿到驾照\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really want my license.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.71,0:11:56.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我练了很久  我发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been practicing a lot, I swear.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.42,0:11:58.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你会酒后驾驶吗  -不会的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You gonna drink and drive? - No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.34,0:12:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-驾驶时发短信  -不会的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You gonna text and drive? - No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.13,0:12:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们再考一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Let's start this from the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.89,0:12:08.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能先笑一笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you smile first?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.85,0:12:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑的话我就不会这么紧张了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be less nervous if you smile.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.15,0:12:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  似乎没什么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that didn't help.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.61,0:12:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开车吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.41,0:12:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是捕大比目鱼的好日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Today feels like a good day for halibut.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.91,0:12:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我有没有跟你说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay, did I ever tell you about the time...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.95,0:12:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用黄油和果冻做鱼饵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I used peanut butter and jelly for bait
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.69,0:12:31.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钓到一条长尾鲨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I caught a thresher shark?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.91,0:12:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了  你跟我讲过很多趣事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. You tell me a lot of funny things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.08,0:12:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么从这边走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are we going this way?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.38,0:12:39.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也可以到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just another way to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.30,0:12:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙  有情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-oh. Something's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.01,0:12:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.36,0:12:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒吧  老男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wake up, old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.61,0:12:45.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想让我去坐那个过山车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's trying to get me on that roller coaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.55,0:12:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  她不会的  -我就是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, she's not. - Yes, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.89,0:12:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我就说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.64,0:12:53.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你得直面自己的恐惧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you have to face your fears.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.33,0:12:54.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们来这儿的目的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why we're here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.02,0:12:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不先跟我知会一声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why didn't you let me in on your little plan?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.95,0:12:58.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你最不擅长说谎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you're the worst liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.56,0:12:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定会看穿你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He would have seen right through you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.07,0:13:02.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想坐过山车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't wanna go on the roller coaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.11,0:13:04.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你以前不敢给烧烤点火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you were afraid to light the barbecue,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.02,0:13:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在你的眉毛已经长回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but now your eyebrows have grown back...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.78,0:13:08.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你烤的三文鱼超级美味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and your salmon is legendary.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.99,0:13:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-万一我掉下来呢  -我会接住你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What if I fall out? - I will catch you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.45,0:13:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不可能  他会把你碾成肉酱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not possible. He would crush you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.16,0:13:15.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我吐了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if I throw up?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.01,0:13:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你清理  反正也不是第一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will clean it up. It wouldn't be the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.63,0:13:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天  我穿了双新鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, these are new shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.30,0:13:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会放弃的  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not gonna let up, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.92,0:13:24.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你心里很清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Baby, I think you know the answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.93,0:13:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  去克服恐惧吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. Let's get it over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.35,0:13:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的勇敢儿子  来吧  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's my boy. Vamos, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.31,0:13:33.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我才不去  对背不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm not going on that. That's bad for my back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.10,0:13:36.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的背没有受伤啊  -我耳水不平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Your back is fine. - I got an inner-ear thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.06,0:13:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拜托  别告诉我你也怕这个  -怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, please. Don't tell me you're scared too. - Scared?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.11,0:13:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"怕"字从何说起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is this "Scared" Stuff from?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.15,0:13:43.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是小孩子  我才不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What am I, a child? I'm not scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.90,0:13:45.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  就说你不擅长说谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You see? You're the worst liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.61,0:13:48.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他不去  那我也不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if he's not going, I'm not going.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.44,0:13:51.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的神啊  好吧  我自己去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, for God's sake, fine! I'll go alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.20,0:13:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  拿好我的"女士"包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Take my girlie purse
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.72,0:13:55.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你戴上我的"花边'帽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you my floppy hat,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.25,0:13:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二位如果需要的话  那边有女士洗手间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and if you need it, there's the ladies' room.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.71,0:14:02.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的男子气概尚不足与之抗争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not man enough to fight this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.88,0:14:07.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  拿好包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Hold my purse.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.76,0:14:11.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.73,0:14:19.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么这么久  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's taking them so long? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.27,0:14:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好没有间歇泉  不然我早发疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The only reason I'm not panicking is I haven't seen a giant geyser.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.23,0:14:25.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  我知道你今晚不想去的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, honey, I think I know why you don't wanna go tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.03,0:14:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为学校舞会很没劲  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Because school dances are lame? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.28,0:14:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为你不会跳舞  -才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 'Cause you don't know how to dance. - That's not it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.16,0:14:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以帮你  来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can help you with that. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.52,0:14:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-来吧  -我的天  不要  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on. - Oh, God, no. No, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.37,0:14:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  我曾经可是一代舞后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. Back in the day, I was quite the dancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.87,0:14:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  突然间明白你和老爸为何走到一起了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. You and Dad together suddenly makes so much sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.38,0:14:40.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  妈  停下来  停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom. Mom, stop. Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.83,0:14:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  别跳了  我会跳舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please, stop. I know how to dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.16,0:14:46.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想参与那个怪胎秀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just don't wanna be part of that freak show.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.22,0:14:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你是个漂亮女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetheart, you're a beautiful girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.22,0:14:49.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有人邀请你跳舞的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Someone will ask you to dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.97,0:14:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但是太傻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know that. It's just stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.97,0:14:53.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有人邀请你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Somebody will ask you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.49,0:14:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你老说这句\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you keep saying that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.93,0:14:57.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有人邀请你跳舞的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Somebody will ask you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.64,0:14:59.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没有人邀请我呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But what if they don't?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.73,0:15:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  如果他们不邀请你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, if they don't,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.73,0:15:04.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就照我跟你姐姐说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then you do the exact same thing I told your sister, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.07,0:15:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸三下  放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take three deep breaths and relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.61,0:15:09.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连收到的建议都是二手货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Even the advice I get is a hand-me-down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.74,0:15:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我成功了  我考过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I did it! I passed!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.87,0:15:13.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.03,0:15:15.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我拿到驾照了  -恭喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got my license! - Congratulations!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.83,0:15:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿到驾照了  拿到驾照了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have my license! I got my license!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.79,0:15:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-车还没停好  -糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Car's not in "Park." - Oh. Oops.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.92,0:15:21.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧去拿驾照\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You better run to that counter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.92,0:15:23.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在就去  -快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go. Right now. - Run! Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.71,0:15:29.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不敢相信你把我的卡车弄丢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still can't believe you lost my truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.80,0:15:31.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了就是没了  伙计  忘了它吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gone, buddy. Let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.43,0:15:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不去揭秘更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, maybe it's better we don't solve this little mystery.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.47,0:15:38.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时想象中的宝藏更诱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes treasure's more sparkly in your imagination.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.89,0:15:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是金子  棒球卡或者海盗藏宝图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or it could be gold or baseball cards or pirate maps.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.06,0:15:45.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的觉得下面可能有海盗藏宝图吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you really think there could be pirate maps under there?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.07,0:15:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢肯定是有可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a hundred percent sure it's possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.61,0:15:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  我进去  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. I'm going in. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:58.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.96,0:16:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you see?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.59,0:16:06.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都看不见  下面真黑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing. It's really dark in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.17,0:16:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我看到我的车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait a minute. I think I see my truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.84,0:16:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的旁边是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's right over there by the- Uh-oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.26,0:16:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -我卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - I think I'm stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.64,0:16:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡在哪了  -我的皮带挂在管子上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are you stuck? -My belt loop got caught on a pipe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.14,0:16:19.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-管子好烫  -试着摆动一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And it's hot. - Have you tried wiggling?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.73,0:16:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  好烫  快来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, it's hot! Hurry!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.89,0:16:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我来了伙计  -快来  下面有蜘蛛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm coming, buddy! - And hurry. There's spiders in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.57,0:16:29.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.57,0:16:31.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉给你带来不快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry if we got all weird in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.61,0:16:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It was fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.15,0:16:35.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想说平时不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we'd like to say it's different than how it usually is,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.87,0:16:38.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你也知道那是假话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but you've seen us enough to know that that's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.66,0:16:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  同志们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.41,0:16:42.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我母亲的关系不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had a very complicated relationship with my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.37,0:16:45.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她生于日本  非常传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She was born in Japan- crazy traditional.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.67,0:16:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不希望我成为医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She didn't want me to become a doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.13,0:16:48.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她希望我结婚生子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She wanted me to get married and have kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.88,0:16:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我父亲  可以和我沟通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But my father, we would talk...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:54.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会听取我的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he would actually listen to what I wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.55,0:16:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样  我想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, what I'm trying to say...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.64,0:17:00.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲的角色并不一定那么重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is having a mother isn't always what it's cracked up to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.22,0:17:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh! Thank you. - Well, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.23,0:17:04.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if you ask me,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.69,0:17:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能有你们两位如此慈爱的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}having two fathers who care as much as you do...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.41,0:17:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉真是世界上最幸运的小女孩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}makes Lily the luckiest little girl in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.86,0:17:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -谢谢你这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh! Thank you so much. - Thank you. Thank you for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.67,0:17:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你人真好  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's very sweet. Thanks. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.71,0:17:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你妈妈现在关系怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And how are things with you and your mom now?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.22,0:17:20.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是个典型的传统亚洲女人她就高兴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The only way she'll be happy is if I'm some Asian stereotype.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.05,0:17:24.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那不是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that just isn't me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.14,0:17:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道后面有垃圾桶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't see those!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.56,0:17:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我来了  伙计  -我在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm coming, buddy. - Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.81,0:17:40.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜘...蛛网  要命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's... a spider web. Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.03,0:17:42.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子有困难了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My boy was in trouble,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.61,0:17:46.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我忘却恐惧  跑去救他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I put my fears aside, and I came to his rescue.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.20,0:17:48.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我算是英雄了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, does that make me a hero?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.53,0:17:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.33,0:17:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.29,0:17:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Everything's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.21,0:17:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  -谢谢爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There. - Thanks, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.58,0:18:01.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲就该救孩子于危难之中  我们出去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, that's what dads do. Let's get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.21,0:18:03.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想拿回我的车  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I want my truck. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.96,0:18:06.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是我的圣诞礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was a Christmas gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.09,0:18:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能去把它捡回来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you go get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.39,0:18:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以  可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.47,0:18:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  我们钻过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure. Let's go- Let's go through it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.48,0:18:19.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  就在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. There it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.44,0:18:25.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.44,0:18:28.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吗  -嗯  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You okay? -Yeah. Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.74,0:18:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I am okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.41,0:18:34.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.83,0:18:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到房子下面来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're under the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.62,0:18:41.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  我们进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the heck. We're down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.46,0:18:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不如看看下面有什么吧  -好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why don't we see what we got, huh? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.84,0:18:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个无畏的冒险者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two intrepid explorers...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.01,0:18:51.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踏上了冒险的旅程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}make their way on a journey-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.93,0:18:53.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dead bodies!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.01,0:18:56.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们报了警  叫来了一群警探\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We called the police and got a bunch of detectives over.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.89,0:19:00.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果那些是屋子前主人的万圣节装饰品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turns out it was the last owner's Halloween decorations,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.27,0:19:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is pretty funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.27,0:19:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我是这么觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Least I thought it was.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.21,0:19:08.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都有怕的东西  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody's afraid of something, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.25,0:19:11.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕高  怕小丑  怕窄小的空间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Heights, clowns, tight spaces.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.88,0:19:13.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢吗  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You like it, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.44,0:19:16.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.74,0:19:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都可以克服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those are things you get over.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.32,0:19:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们还有孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But then there's our children.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.04,0:19:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是否合群\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Will they fit in?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.20,0:19:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Will they be safe?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.06,0:19:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们注定要担心一辈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those are fears you never get past.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.36,0:19:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有时  我们只能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So sometimes all you can do...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.61,0:19:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸  拥抱他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is take a deep breath, pull 'em close...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.95,0:19:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望一切安好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and hope for the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.74,0:19:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  -注意路面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye! - Eyes on the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.33,0:19:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爱你们  -注意路面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Love you! - Eyes on the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.33,0:19:47.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.91,0:19:51.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  人不可能事事顺心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, things don't always work out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.50,0:19:53.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  她应该是想要娃娃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Cam, I think she wants her doll.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.88,0:19:56.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道在哪里  -妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't know where it is. - Mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.93,0:20:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.93,0:20:05.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一捏这娃娃  它就会说"妈咪"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When you squeeze the doll, it says "Mommy."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.89,0:20:08.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你之前知道吗  -毫不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did-Did you know that - Not a clue.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.10,0:20:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娃娃说的"妈咪"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The doll says "Mommy."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.44,0:20:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是娃娃说的"妈咪"  -娃娃说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The doll says "Mommy." - The doll says "Mommy."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.94,0:20:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若事事顺心  则要珍惜当下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you gotta love it when they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.53,0:20:22.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  -什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Dad. - Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.03,0:20:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈说阁楼里有个旧行李箱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom says there's an old trunk in the attic.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.24,0:20:27.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我爷爷的旧扁平行李箱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. My grandpa's old steamer trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.33,0:20:30.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看的一个电影  里面有一个行李箱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In this movie I saw, there was this old trunk...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.33,0:20:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一间秘室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and there's a secret compartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.04,0:20:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开以后  里面有很多幅画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And when you opened it, there was a whole bunch of paintings,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.75,0:20:37.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是战争时期藏起来的大画家的作品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by the world's greatest painters, hidden in the war.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.49,0:20:40.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爷爷参与过战争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My grandpa was in the war.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.63,0:20:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要上去看一看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Should we go up there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.73,0:20:43.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对的  说不定里面是钻石呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Totally. It could also be diamonds.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.52,0:20:44.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是日本武士军刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or a samurai sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.53,0:20:46.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是《独立宣言》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or the Declaration of Independence.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.53,0:20:51.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阁楼里有什么并不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, it almost doesn't even matter what's up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.78,0:20:54.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是怎么花用它换来的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What matters is what you do with the money from what's up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.95,0:20:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以买艘汽艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We could get a motorboat.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.62,0:20:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者下水道清理机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or a robotic gutter cleaner.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.41,0:21:01.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-或者室内泳池  -或者双人潜水艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Or an indoor pool. - Or a two-man submarine.

