[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.28,0:03:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.28,0:03:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.28,0:03:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.42,0:00:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美好的清晨  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Beautiful morning, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.58,0:00:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜你还得工作  是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a shame you have to work, huh? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.46,0:00:10.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正  我想要个大香肠和意大利辣肠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I'd like a large sausage and pepperoni-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.49,0:00:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的东西好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's my stuff, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.33,0:00:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碰我的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just keep your hands off my stuff!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.61,0:00:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没碰你的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't put my hands on your stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.91,0:00:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  稍等一下  德里克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey! Just a second, Derek.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.66,0:00:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.89,0:00:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾丽克斯偷看了我的日记  -我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Alex read my journal. - I did not!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.41,0:00:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要偷看你那愚蠢的日记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would I even want to read your stupid journal?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.87,0:00:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那详细记述了丰富多彩的美好生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it contains the details of a life,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.16,0:00:28.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你从来不曾享受过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you don't have one!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.54,0:00:30.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  别偷看海莉的日记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, don't read Haley's journal.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.96,0:00:32.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  是我的女儿们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry. My daughters.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有孩子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got kids?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.26,0:00:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-噢  读几年级了  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh. What grade are you in? - Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.01,0:00:38.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  是我老婆  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's my wife, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.72,0:00:42.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克竟然用我的电脑看这种东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke was using my computer for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.89,0:00:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先挂了  有空再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna have to, uh, call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.56,0:00:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说要用电脑做家庭作业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He told me he needed it to do homework,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.96,0:00:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我发现这个  一张图片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then I find this, a-a picture...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.85,0:00:50.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面是个裸着上身的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of a topless woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.08,0:00:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部是我见过最大的  而且在开着拖拉机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the biggest boobs I have ever seen, driving a tractor.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.65,0:00:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  首先\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Um- Uh, first of all,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.75,0:00:59.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是台联合收割机  不是拖拉机  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- that's a combine, not a tractor. - Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.67,0:01:00.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  那是淫秽内容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil! It is smut,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.74,0:01:02.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们10岁大的儿子在看淫秽内容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and our 10-year-old is looking at smut!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.83,0:01:05.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太恶心了  -完全无法接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's disgusting! - Completely unacceptable.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.00,0:01:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情是这样的  那是我的图片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's the thing. That was my picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.33,0:01:08.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实也不是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, not really mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.77,0:01:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个同事发给我的一个链接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's this guy at work who sends out these links.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.79,0:01:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doesn't matter who.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.94,0:01:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是格尔·索普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gil Thorpe.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.00,0:01:13.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还发了另外一张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He sent out another one
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.82,0:01:16.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那同一个女人打扮得像个战舰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of the same woman dressed as a battleship.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  那个部位...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, the- You get- Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.94,0:01:21.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后又打扮得像变形金刚  就是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then one of the Transformers- And then it-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.64,0:01:25.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  我很想如实向克莱尔坦白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I had every intention of telling Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.27,0:01:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想让她先冷静下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just wanted her to calm down first.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.14,0:01:28.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.96,0:01:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去把卢克从同学家接回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm going to pick up Luke from his sleepover.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.26,0:01:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须现在就跟他谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We need to talk to him about this now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.06,0:01:35.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  此事切不可鲁莽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, this is a very delicate situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.44,0:01:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们处理不当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If we don't handle it right,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.39,0:01:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克可能会对性产生不健康的观点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke might end up having an unhealthy attitude about sex...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.15,0:01:41.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或农业综合产业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or agribusiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.16,0:01:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要等他回来再跟他谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll talk about it when he gets home.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.28,0:01:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.99,0:01:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我要告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I am telling him
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.79,0:01:50.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他每看一次色情图片  上帝就会弄死一只狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that every time he looks at porn, God kills a puppy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.33,0:01:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许该由我去跟他谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe I should be the one to talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.38,0:01:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个非常幸运的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am a very lucky woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.71,0:01:56.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个幸福的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a wonderful family,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.71,0:01:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美丽的家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a beautiful home.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.54,0:02:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直没有我想改变的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's nothing that I would change.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.39,0:02:06.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨死那个狗管家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate the dog butler.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.79,0:02:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总忘记它的存在  每次迎面撞上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I keep forgetting it's there. And every time it happens,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.06,0:02:12.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都把我吓得半死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it scares me all over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.44,0:02:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候深更半夜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes, at night,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.48,0:02:16.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那就是魔鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think it's the devil.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.69,0:02:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}El diablo.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.94,0:02:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴克利  他超好笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Barkley? He's hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.62,0:02:23.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上个月去维加斯  赢了不少钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was in Vegas last month and I was winning.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.70,0:02:25.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就想  我可以像往常那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I thought, I could do the usual,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.93,0:02:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当个笨蛋  再把钱吐回给赌场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}be a chump, give the money back to the casino,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.81,0:02:30.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我可以做点明智的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or I could do something smart
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.46,0:02:32.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在赌场商店为我自己买点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and buy something for myself at the casino store.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.40,0:02:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经是全家人的最爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's already a family favorite.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.04,0:02:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抚摸他的下巴  再往下一点  他喜欢那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Rub his chin, a little under there. He likes that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.21,0:02:40.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  超帅的  太上镜了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you go. Beautiful. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是条狗  也是个管家  谁会不爱他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a dog and a butler. I mean, who couldn't love him?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.52,0:02:50.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.29,0:02:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.30,0:03:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  可以走了  -你先尿一泡吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, ready to go. - Make sure you pee first.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.90,0:03:18.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  当我是7岁小孩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What am I, seven years old?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.87,0:03:20.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你在演出中途去厕所会被鄙视的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You do not want to go during the show.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.15,0:03:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些木偶会停下动作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The marionettes stop what they're doing,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.67,0:03:23.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行进到舞台边缘  然后指着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}march to the edge of the stage and point at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.88,0:03:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  听着好吓人  -其实很搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, that sounds terrifying. - No, it's really funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.73,0:03:29.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最美好的童年记忆之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, one of my favorite childhood memories
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.00,0:03:32.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是去看莫斯科木偶戏剧团的演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was attending the Moscow Marionette Theater.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.46,0:03:35.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老家离密苏里最大的水上滑道只有1英里远\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I grew up one mile away from Missouri's largest waterslide.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.54,0:03:36.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是全国第三大的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And third largest in the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.68,0:03:39.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  小卡  以前从没听你提过呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, really, Cam. You never mentioned that before.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.47,0:03:41.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你会感觉  -感觉像鱼雷一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You feel like- - Feel like a torpedo.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.18,0:03:46.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小卡  我们家园丁通常周六来工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Cam, does the gardener usually work on Saturdays?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.86,0:03:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我们需要他时  他就会过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. He comes when we need him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.10,0:03:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就像是蝙蝠侠  不过是直男\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's like Batman but straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.07,0:03:52.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是在哭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is he crying?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.46,0:03:56.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我们或许  该从后门出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. We should probably go out the back, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.94,0:03:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他显然处于痛苦中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's clearly in pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.17,0:04:01.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎能如此冷漠对待一位朋友呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How can you just turn your back on a friend like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.19,0:04:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  是吗  他叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A friend? Really? What's his name?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.40,0:04:05.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯撒·萨拉扎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Caesar Salazar.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.03,0:04:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞎编的吧  你准备说"凯撒沙拉"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You made that up. You were gonna say "Caesar Salad."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.49,0:04:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才不是呢  -小卡  别  不是吧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Was not. - Cam. Come on. Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.87,0:04:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  别担心  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, don't worry, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:17.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证我们会准时去看木偶秀的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure we'll get to the show on time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.75,0:04:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确定爸爸只是出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure Dad is just gonna go out
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.31,0:04:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安慰一下那个园丁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and give an encouraging word to the gardener,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.91,0:04:23.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望顺便提一下蜗牛泛滥的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}hopefully mention the snail problem,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.53,0:04:26.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就...不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we are gonna be on- - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.01,0:04:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  小卡  不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. Cam, no-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.35,0:04:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好呀  -他应该不会说英语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello. - I don't think he speaks English.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.77,0:04:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那我正好不用顾忌地告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, this might be a good time to mention to you...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.39,0:04:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些木偶们对迟到者可不友善\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that the marionettes are not kind to latecomers.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.39,0:04:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会弯下腰  露出灯笼裤以示嘲弄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They bend over and show their bloomers.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.91,0:04:41.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我会说一点西班牙语  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I speak a little Spanish. Seor-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.98,0:04:45.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(193,240)}你想撒尿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.26,0:04:48.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(192,240)}然后睡在我们的床上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.88,0:04:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gracias.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.00,0:04:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.80,0:04:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚问他要不要喝杯水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just asked him if he wanted to have a glass of water...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.54,0:04:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后坐下休息一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and sit down for a minute,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.45,0:04:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何有善心的人都会这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like any kind person would.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.00,0:05:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我查看了家里的其他电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I checked the rest of the computers in the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.67,0:05:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没发现更多的色情内容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't find any more porn.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.16,0:05:21.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那根本算不上色情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was hardly porn.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.12,0:05:22.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个没穿上衣的女人坐在拖拉机上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was a topless woman on a tractor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.98,0:05:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那在欧洲叫什么吗  谷物广告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what they call that in Europe? A cereal commercial.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.53,0:05:28.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要去找他谈谈  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I should go talk to him. - Honey,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.18,0:05:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  交给我吧  交给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}honey, honey. I got this. I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.24,0:05:31.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  交给我吧  让我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no. I got this. I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.77,0:05:32.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也曾经历他这样的年纪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was his age once.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.97,0:05:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳房就像是可怕而又神秘的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Breasts are like these scary, mystical things...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.05,0:05:40.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被诱惑了  就像弗罗多被魔多诱惑一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that he's drawn to like Frodo to Mordor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.96,0:05:42.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看来我是非去不可了  -不不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, I'm definitely going- - No, no, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子们不希望妈妈和他们谈论性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boys don't want their moms talking to 'em about sex...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像女孩们不希望父亲和她们谈月经\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}any more than girls want their dads talking to 'em about periods,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.35,0:05:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸罩  紧身褡之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}bras and girdles and all that stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:53.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道女人30年前就不穿紧身褡了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You do know that women stopped wearing girdles, like, 30 years ago?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.33,0:05:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我知道  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I know, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.40,0:05:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一场性革命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That-That-That is exactly the kind of sexual revolution...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.60,0:06:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们家儿子正经历的情况是一样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that our son is going through right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.69,0:06:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你要对我有信心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, just- Let's just- just trust it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.44,0:06:06.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得修楼梯  你要知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fix that step. Just know,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.94,0:06:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会处理好的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will handle this, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.83,0:06:15.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}El diablo.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.92,0:06:16.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Gloria,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.86,0:06:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道巴克利为什么跑到客房去了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}do you have any idea why Barkley was in the guest room?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.08,0:06:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是对家里翻新装饰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just doing a little redecorating.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.00,0:06:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候把东西挪动一下挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes it's good to move things around
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.69,0:06:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会试出新感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just to see how they look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.26,0:06:28.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但放在客房里  也太疯狂了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but the guest room? That's crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.26,0:06:30.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是客人  他是为我们工作的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not a guest. He works for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.59,0:06:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  帮我个忙  可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, give me a hand here, will you?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.05,0:06:35.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他移下来时  似乎把他的衣服扯歪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think his jacket shifted while I was moving him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.10,0:06:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让你衣衫不整呀  小管家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can't have you untucked, our little butler.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.05,0:06:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也太不成体统了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That doesn't make any sense, does it, boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.60,0:06:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  没伤着他吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What was that? Is he all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.37,0:06:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  我的手镯似乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, no. My bracelet got
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.23,0:06:44.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡在这里了  -别慌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- caught a little bit here. - Well, don't panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.90,0:06:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没慌  -很好  试着放松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm not panicking. - All right, try to relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.09,0:06:48.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以修好他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can fix him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.03,0:06:50.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我好好看看  来  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me take a better look. Come here, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.45,0:06:53.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  -嘿  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke? - Hey, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.49,0:06:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小老弟  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy. Um, look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.20,0:06:59.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得小小地谈一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You and I need to have a little talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.91,0:07:03.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-关于什么  -关于  电脑方面的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- About what? - Well, it's about computer stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.34,0:07:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如何确保看过某东西之后  删除浏览痕迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you make sure you've deleted something after you read it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.06,0:07:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  杰  纯属意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, Jay. It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.62,0:07:20.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在觉得你不怎么喜欢巴克利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I'm beginning to think you don't like Barkley that much.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.39,0:07:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先是把他藏在客房  现在又来这么一出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, first you hide him in the guest room, and now this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.87,0:07:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒谬了  我根本不是有意伤害它的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's ridiculous. I didn't mean to hurt it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.44,0:07:28.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  请别再用"它"了  是"他"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}First of all, let's cut the "It"s. He is a he.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.53,0:07:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以继续堂而皇之地装无辜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you can pretend to be innocent all you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.06,0:07:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事实胜于雄辩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but action speaks louder than words.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.49,0:07:35.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  事实可以反映很多事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. They can be very revealing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.33,0:07:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you trying to say?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.91,0:07:39.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  但你必须承认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing. But you have to admit
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.26,0:07:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗头管家有点可笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that the dog butler is a little ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.48,0:07:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我觉得什么很可笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what else I think is ridiculous?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.95,0:07:46.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在我们床上堆起来的枕头山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That mountain of pillows you have on our bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.21,0:07:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我就像个码头工人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel like I'm working on a loading dock
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.39,0:07:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛辛苦苦就为了能钻进被子底下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just trying to get under the covers.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.71,0:07:51.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那很漂亮  -那很令人讨厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They're pretty. - They're a damn nuisance.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.08,0:07:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  原谅我想要让我们家显得漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, forgive me for trying to make our home beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.80,0:07:56.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我可以忍受那些枕头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, if I can put up with those,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.43,0:07:57.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也该忍受一件艺术作品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you can put up with a piece of art.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.06,0:08:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才不是艺术  只是人与兽的邪恶组合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is not art. This is an unholy mix between man and beast.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.69,0:08:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  如果你那么爱它  随你放哪儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, fine, if you love it so much, put it wherever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.87,0:08:09.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你要去哪儿  去买更多的枕头吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Where you going? To get some more pillows?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.02,0:08:12.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  别担心  很长时间内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, don't worry. It'll be a long
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.26,0:08:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的枕头都不会去烦你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}time before I bother you again with my pillows.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.48,0:08:20.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么爸爸在卢克的房间  还把门关着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is Dad in Luke's room with the door closed?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.08,0:08:22.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要稍微谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They are having a little talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.50,0:08:23.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克被惩罚了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is Luke being punished?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.00,0:08:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你最爱的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that just your favorite thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.91,0:08:26.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你姐姐或弟弟惹麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when your brother or sister gets into trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.04,0:08:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最爱的是他们都惹麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My favorite is when they're both in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.71,0:08:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他犯什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what'd he do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.41,0:08:32.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是不是考试作弊了  他是个作弊狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did he cheat on a test? He's a cheater.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.42,0:08:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没有考试作弊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He did not cheat on a test.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.22,0:08:35.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他撒谎了吗  他整天撒谎  -艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did he lie? He lies all the time. - Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.98,0:08:39.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾丽克斯  -抱歉  我只是担心卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Alex. - Sorry. I'm just worried about Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.47,0:08:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多家长又开始打小孩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A lot of parents are hitting again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.05,0:08:43.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你的关心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I appreciate your concern,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.48,0:08:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你爸爸控制的很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your father has it under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.19,0:08:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,24\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Twenty-four.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.94,0:08:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,25\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Twenty-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.15,0:08:55.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缩手了  让我打  快伸出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Flincher! Free slap. Bring it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.58,0:09:01.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,29\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Twenty-nine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.48,0:09:03.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以换我把手放下面吗  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I be on the bottom now? - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.30,0:09:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How'd it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.20,0:09:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得非常尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, he was really embarrassed,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.34,0:09:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在  一切都没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but everything's- everything's fine now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.51,0:09:16.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么教育他的  -那个  其实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What'd you say? - Well, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.57,0:09:19.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向他保证  谈话内容绝对不外泄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I kinda promised him we'd keep everything between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.62,0:09:20.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Matter of fact,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.20,0:09:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远都不能向他提起此事  否则他会觉得受辱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he'd be mortified if you brought it up with him... ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.34,0:09:26.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  真的吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, God, really? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.32,0:09:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真让我觉得有点愧疚呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That actually makes me feel kinda bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.91,0:09:34.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能只是因为这事儿搞的有点紧张过度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you're probably just feeling a little tense from all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.24,0:09:36.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.05,0:09:40.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道什么有助于缓解紧张吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what might help the situation?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.30,0:09:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧你  大白天的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.80,0:09:50.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是出去吃点匹萨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I meant going out for a few pizzas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.42,0:09:53.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想哪儿去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.84,0:09:56.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家色情狂还真多呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I live in a house full of sex maniacs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.71,0:10:00.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Amigo?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.99,0:10:03.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不出来  我们怎么能帮到你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can't help you if you won't come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.94,0:10:09.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他说什么  -什么房子什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What'd he say? - Something "House" Something.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.69,0:10:11.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  演出半小时后就开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. The show starts in a half hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.67,0:10:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还得去接曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we still have to pick up Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.74,0:10:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就...快  不理这事儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we just- Come on. Move this thing along!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.45,0:10:16.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这男人现在陷入了危机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, this man is in crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.24,0:10:18.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的家人可能出现了健康问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He could have a family health issue
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.31,0:10:20.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是他个人有健康问题  或是经济困难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or a personal health issue or a financial matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.54,0:10:23.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停  你从一句"房子什么的"就推断出这么多吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop. You're getting all this from "Something house something"?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.42,0:10:26.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打电话让歌洛莉亚来处理它吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's just call Gloria and have her deal with it, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.92,0:10:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"它"可是个人啊  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Lt" Is a human being, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.05,0:10:30.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-名叫"凯撒沙拉"  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Named Caesar Salad. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.05,0:10:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是怎么回事  -小卡  你老是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's going on with you? - Cam, you- you always do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.26,0:10:37.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你每次都喜欢听别人的伤心事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like you're incapable of hearing anyone's sad story...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.10,0:10:38.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再热心地去帮助他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without making it your job to fix it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.10,0:10:41.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我的需求  总被你排在第二位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then, my needs- my needs come second.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.57,0:10:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在的需求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your needs right now...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.10,0:10:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是场木偶秀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are a puppet show.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.63,0:10:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人的哥哥可能丧生于缆车事故\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This man could have lost his brother in a cable car accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.94,0:10:49.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过是听懂了一个"房子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You understood "Casa."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.90,0:10:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  行  如果能向你证明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fine. If it'll prove to you...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.60,0:10:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并未患有你口中说的那种"助人为乐上瘾症"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'm not the obsessive helpaholic that you make me out to be,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.49,0:10:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就去看木偶秀吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}let's go to the puppet show.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.79,0:10:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  -走呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cam. - Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.00,0:11:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她肯定是来找园丁的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think this has something to do with the gardener.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.22,0:11:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.34,0:11:10.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走到走廊尽头向右转  -谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just down the hall to the right. - Ay. Gracias, gracias.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.17,0:11:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不好意思  -他在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Perdn. - In there. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.45,0:11:15.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  走吧  -不  算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, let's go. - No, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.18,0:11:16.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你内心煎熬的要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it's killing you
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.09,0:11:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能跟进去搀和一脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not to get back there in the middle of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.36,0:11:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不不  我们一定要去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, no, no, no. We are going.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.55,0:11:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人闹完了自然会出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These folks can find their own way out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.56,0:11:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你就会知道我不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And now you'll know that I'm not a
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.26,0:11:25.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特瑞萨修女  整天帮助那些迷失的灵魂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}manic Mother Teresa out there collecting lost souls.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.94,0:11:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.07,0:11:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  -在后院呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad? - Back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.44,0:11:36.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is Manny ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.51,0:11:37.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没收到信息吗  他不去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Didn't you get the message? He's not going.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.95,0:11:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -学校突然强令要大扫除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Ah, some mandatory cleanup at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.41,0:11:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-到底是什么原因  -那是个木偶秀啊  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's the real reason? - It's a puppet show, Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.37,0:11:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  那就剩你  我和小莉莉去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perfect. All right, it's just you and me then, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.92,0:11:52.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小家伙怎么样  -她很好  她很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How's the little fortune cookie? - Ah, she-she's good. She's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.25,0:11:55.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡呢  -我们吵架了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where's Cam? - We got into a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.72,0:11:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为他  我家里挤满了拉丁人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because of him, I have a house full of Latinos.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.14,0:11:59.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎进入我的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Welcome to my world.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.16,0:12:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"同志天堂"也有闹矛盾的时候哈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, trouble in gay paradise, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.82,0:12:04.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是无法拒绝任何向他求助的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just can't say no to anybody who needs help.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.35,0:12:05.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么总是不分场合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And why do you have to always
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.46,0:12:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么话都要加个"同志"做限定词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}add the word "Gay" Where it doesn't belong?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.98,0:12:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你别把气撒在我身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey, you're not mad at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.53,0:12:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在气你家那位"球形娇妻"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're mad at the old balls and chain.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.45,0:12:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧老爸  谈话很愉快  再见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Dad, good talk. See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.27,0:12:13.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别啊  我不是有心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, I didn't mean it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.50,0:12:15.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我真不是有心的  我有点不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, I didn't mean it. I'm a little cranky.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.65,0:12:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和歌洛莉亚闹得有点不愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got into it with Gloria a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.43,0:12:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢不  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:20.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她讨厌巴克利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, she hates Barkley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.62,0:12:22.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前你妈也老是为这些东西跟我过不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the same stuff I went over with your mom all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.91,0:12:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"把那船卖了""把那摩托车扔了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Get rid of the boat." "Get rid of the motorcycle."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.99,0:12:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道  我就是喜欢这些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I liked those things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.97,0:12:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么要扔掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you have to get rid of it then?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.42,0:12:32.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我没扔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, actually, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.25,0:12:36.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把他的手粘上去  他的手断掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I'm gluing his hand on over here. His hand came off.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.76,0:12:38.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真不顺啊  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Rough day, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.18,0:12:39.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你性感年轻的娇妻不喜欢你的玩偶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your hot, young wife doesn't like your doll.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.05,0:12:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  跟你的大问题不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, unlike your big problem,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.15,0:12:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我男友对人太热心了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"My boyfriend's too nice to people."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.76,0:12:46.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  其实并不仅仅是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, see- mmm- that's not all it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.22,0:12:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢帮助小动物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He helps animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.91,0:12:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他总是参加一些志愿活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's always volunteering for things.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.87,0:12:52.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  真实情况比听起来严重多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trust me. It-lt's worse than it sounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.44,0:12:55.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全懂你  我们都面临类似的难题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who are we kidding? We both got it pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.11,0:12:56.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  我可能和你妈较劲儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hell, I'm probably fighting with your mom
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.86,0:12:58.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我现在跟歌洛莉亚较劲儿还厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}more than I'm fighting with Gloria on this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.70,0:13:00.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟从树上掉下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A bird fell out of a tree
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.37,0:13:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会用滴眼药水的管子去喂它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he fed it with an eyedropper.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.74,0:13:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just drop it, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.18,0:13:04.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的爱人都跟我们不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're both with people different from us,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.70,0:13:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样肯定会产生矛盾  但你想要的就是不同的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that's gonna create stuff, but you want different.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.10,0:13:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈和我各方面都很般配\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mom and I were perfect on paper
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.09,0:13:11.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道最后的下场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you know how that ended.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.35,0:13:15.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在拥有的要好得多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What I got now is a lot better.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.50,0:13:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  外人会对我们侧目非议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure, people look at us sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.41,0:13:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候我也不相信我们竟然在一起了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And sometimes even I can't believe we're together.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.13,0:13:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们很幸福   归根到底  夜晚来临时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we're happy. At the end of the day
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.97,0:13:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想回到她的身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's no one I'd rather come home to.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.20,0:13:31.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说歌洛莉亚吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.06,0:13:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然还能有谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who else?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.07,0:13:36.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.92,0:13:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚些再见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll see you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.02,0:13:40.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.78,0:13:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在我的海报上乱画了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you draw on my poster?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.33,0:13:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  是我干的  或许下次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I did. Maybe you'll think
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.98,0:13:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再敢读我日记  就该想想这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about that the next time you read my journal.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.50,0:13:51.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有读你愚蠢的日记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't read your stupid journal,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:53.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我排了好长队才弄到签名的  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I waited in line to get this signed, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.00,0:13:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别孩子气了  不过是个发型古怪的老兄罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't be such a baby. It's just some dude with weird hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.53,0:14:01.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是玛雅·安琪洛  你个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's Maya Angelou, you idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.82,0:14:04.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[玛雅·安琪洛是美国著名女作家和诗人]
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.51,0:14:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我不看女子篮球赛的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sorry. I don't follow the WNBA.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.37,0:14:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你  这是你做过的最缺德的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? This is the worst thing you've ever done,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.21,0:14:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远都不会原谅你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'll never forgive you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.02,0:14:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你先挑起的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You started it!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.60,0:14:14.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看什么看  -我只是听到...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What are you looking at? - Well, I just heard-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.44,0:14:17.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷看海莉日记的人其实是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was the one who read Haley's diary.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.94,0:14:20.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时正在玩她的电脑  日记本身就是开着的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was playing on her computer and it just opened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.53,0:14:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  是我打开的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I opened it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.69,0:14:26.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想她们为此争吵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I didn't mean for anyone to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.70,0:14:30.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  回来得这么快  米奇  嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh,ome already. Mitchell, hi..
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.95,0:14:33.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  小卡  -你是忘了带票吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, Cam. Hi. - Did you forget the tickets?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.96,0:14:36.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不在我一个人看也不会很享受的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You know, I was never gonna enjoy the show without you, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.59,0:14:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你那么兴奋地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. But you were so excited
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.76,0:14:39.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想带莉莉去看俄罗斯木偶秀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to take Lily to see the Russian marionettes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.75,0:14:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能有点年纪太小了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, she's probably a little young anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.51,0:14:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以把她放在烘干机前半小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can just prop her in front of the dryer for a half hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.09,0:14:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, Cam,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.24,0:14:47.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很欣赏你想让世界更美好的心愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I love that you try and help the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.67,0:14:50.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很庆幸我的生命中有你的存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm very lucky to have you in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.84,0:14:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.79,0:14:53.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,园丁那事儿处理得怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How'd everything work out with the gardener?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.49,0:14:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, great. Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.58,0:14:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来今天是他的结婚日  他只是有点紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turned out it was his wedding day, and he was a little nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.65,0:14:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  其实你也没必要道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you know what? There's no need to apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.02,0:15:01.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我一定要  我太自私了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I need to. I've been very selfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.11,0:15:02.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  有时候是我热心过头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. Sometimes I take things too far.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.11,0:15:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  如果那样  我会提醒你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. If that ever happens, I will let you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.31,0:15:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.79,0:15:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么原因不能让我进去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there a reason I can't go inside?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.50,0:15:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没  没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, no. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.37,0:15:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  我宣布你们结为夫妻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Y ahora te pronuncio hombre y esposa.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.79,0:15:20.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请亲吻新娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}La puedes besar.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.30,0:15:31.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我能跟你谈谈吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, can I talk to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.00,0:15:32.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  宝贝  什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure, honey. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.29,0:15:34.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对自己的所为感到很愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel bad about something I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.89,0:15:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  是因为电脑那事儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sweetie. Is this about the computer?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.52,0:15:41.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -你看了不该看的东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Something you shouldn't have been looking at?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.14,0:15:44.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  真的好古怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. It was just so freaky.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.19,0:15:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看了一眼就停不下来  -我懂的  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I couldn't stop looking. - I know, sweet pea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.66,0:15:50.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但重要的是你最终确实停下来了  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But the important thing is you did stop looking. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.16,0:15:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了一小时之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}After about an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.29,0:15:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  对那些东西好奇也是很正常的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Well, it's perfectly normal to be curious about these things.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.08,0:15:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些部分很搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some parts were funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.30,0:16:01.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些部分简直太疯狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And some parts just seemed crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.63,0:16:05.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你知道  有些部分并不是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I hope you realize that some of those parts weren't real.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.09,0:16:06.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很显然嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Obviously.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.88,0:16:09.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有可能完全是真的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But they can be totally real, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.47,0:16:11.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-像《安妮日记》那样  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Like Anne Frank's? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.30,0:16:13.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道  那让我老想着海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All I know is it really made me wonder about Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.06,0:16:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真愁人  宝贝  为什么是海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's disturbing, sweetie. Why Haley?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.81,0:16:19.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是她的日记啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was her journal.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.56,0:16:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你读了我的日记  你个小变态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You read my journal? You little creep!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.44,0:16:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我没忍住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry! I couldn't help it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.23,0:16:24.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你还读了海莉的日记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. Haley's journal too?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.99,0:16:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  从今以后不准你接近电脑  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, you are now banned from the computer. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.36,0:16:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了  谁惹麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened? Who's in trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:31.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克读了我的日记  -我就说不是我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke read my journal! - I told you it wasn't me!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.78,0:16:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要宰了你  -海莉  冷静\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know, I'm gonna kill you. - Haley, calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.08,0:16:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你都不打算吼他几句吗  那是隐私啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, you're not even gonna yell at him? That was private.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.50,0:16:38.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  里面最令人震惊的就是你稀烂的拼写\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, please. The most shocking thing in there was your spelling.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.87,0:16:40.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也读过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You read it too?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.13,0:16:42.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道只有我一个人没读过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I the only one who hasn't read it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.29,0:16:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我翻电脑查看色情图片时不小心读的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was looking through the computers in the house for pornography.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.30,0:16:47.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真恶心  -不是我要看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sick. - Not for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.26,0:16:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看你们有没有"涉黄"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanted to see what you guys are looking at.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.01,0:16:50.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就公然侵犯我们的隐私\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you're violating our privacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.84,0:16:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现我的孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I find out that my children...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.60,0:16:54.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在网上浏览裸体图片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are looking at a naked picture online,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.47,0:16:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就没有隐私可言了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they don't have any privacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.93,0:16:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁浏览裸照了  -那不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who was looking at naked pictures? - That doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.16,0:17:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.56,0:17:03.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是我  真恶心  我才10岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wasn't me. That's gross. I'm 10!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.52,0:17:05.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等一下  -你们是怎么回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wait a minute. - What's wrong with you people?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.28,0:17:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是你  那是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If it wasn't you, who was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.24,0:17:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼佳匹萨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mangia!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.78,0:17:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-洛萨  谢谢你赶来  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Rosa, thank you for coming. - Gracias.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.08,0:17:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡洛斯  告诉我你和那牙医的发展结果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Carlos, let me know how it works out with that dentist.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.18,0:17:18.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维克托  你欠我一支舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Victor, you owe me a dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我是一个博爱的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I'm a caring person.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.37,0:17:21.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And without Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.32,0:17:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会一直不断地奉献  奉献  奉献\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would just keep giving and giving and giving.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:25.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就像一辆奔跑的慈善卡车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm like a big runaway charity truck
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.52,0:17:28.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇就像是我的匝道  铺满安全碎石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Mitchell is my off-ramp full of safety gravel.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.76,0:17:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道如何拒绝别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He knows how to say no.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.54,0:17:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他总是可以将自己放在第一位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He always can put himself first.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.72,0:17:35.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他绝对可以漠视那些受苦受难的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He certainly can turn his back on someone suffering.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.73,0:17:41.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  真的  继续说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, really. Keep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.65,0:17:45.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他...  -别再说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He- - Don't keep going!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.77,0:17:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-非常感谢  -嘿  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Muchas gracias. - Hey, good-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.61,0:17:50.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.78,0:17:54.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  好吓人  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.70,0:17:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我似乎错过派对了嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Looks like I missed the party, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.54,0:17:57.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  把这玩意儿带来干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is- What is that doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.04,0:18:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是我送给你和小卡的礼物  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He is a gift for you and Cam. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.33,0:18:04.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在途中缺了一只眼镜片  当时头伸出了窗外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He lost his monocle on the drive. Head was out the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.71,0:18:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-狗都喜欢把头伸出车窗外  -先把他放这儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, they love that. - Let's put him here for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.96,0:18:09.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不想要那玩意儿  -我觉得他很可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't want that. - I think he's cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.84,0:18:10.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他个表现机会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's give him a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.68,0:18:12.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一收到你的短信就赶来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I came as soon as I heard your message.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.51,0:18:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前是说有人要结婚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You said that somebody was getting married?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.52,0:18:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  你来啦  我有好消息要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, there you are. I've got good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.56,0:18:24.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.24,0:18:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey? Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.49,0:18:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.70,0:18:35.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张图片只是别人传给我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That picture was just something that someone sent me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.29,0:18:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doesn't matter who.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.97,0:18:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是格尔·索普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gil Thorpe.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.79,0:18:42.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我不需要那些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I don't do that stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.46,0:18:44.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对我来说已经够调情了  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're all the porn I need. That's- Uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.63,0:18:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, it's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.63,0:18:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.72,0:18:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在才真没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, it's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.93,0:18:56.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不在乎那张图片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I couldn't care less about the picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.10,0:18:59.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为那是卢克的所为  才很生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just upset when I thought it was Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.48,0:19:00.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  宝贝  我真的希望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, honey, I really wish
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.62,0:19:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮我洗一下衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you would give me a hand with all this laundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.69,0:19:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从来不...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never, ever-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.69,0:19:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉有她自己的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley's off in her own world.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.15,0:19:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯从来就不像个小孩样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex has never really been a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.82,0:19:12.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卢克是我的小宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But Luke is my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.57,0:19:14.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是我太奢望吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it really too much to ask
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.31,0:19:17.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让他永远当个可爱  纯真的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that he stay a sweet, innocent kid...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.83,0:19:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}forever?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.25,0:19:27.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老弟  听着  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy. Um- Here. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.96,0:19:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿再拍球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll dribble later.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.97,0:19:33.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是  只是想说我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I just, uh- I just want to say I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.84,0:19:37.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是有意让你为那张图片背黑锅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never meant to blame you for that whole picture thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.31,0:19:38.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈以为那是你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mom sort of thought it was yours
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.82,0:19:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该站出来说实话的  但我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I should have stopped it, but I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.27,0:19:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张图片拍的是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what was the picture of?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.56,0:19:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于一个女人在拖拉机上  没穿上衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it was a woman on a tractor and she had her shirt off.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.24,0:19:53.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很热吗[性感]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was it hot?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.28,0:19:55.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  既然要开诚布公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, we're being honest here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.41,0:19:59.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,图片中的那个女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, this particular woman-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.16,0:20:01.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确很欣赏她的性感曲线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, my tastes do run to the curvy,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.71,0:20:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宽大的牛仔帽并没有破坏整体美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the cowboy hat did not hurt one bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.29,0:20:05.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和超短牛仔裤相映成趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Couple that with the cutoff jeans-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.63,0:20:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其实问的是天气热不热  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you were asking about the weather, weren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.71,0:20:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.34,0:20:14.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, this is good. This is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.59,0:20:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很快就将经历一些成长变化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be going through some changes soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.05,0:20:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你不管有什么事  都可以放心跟我说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I think now you can feel safe talking to me about whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.24,0:20:33.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切到此为止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And so it ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.15,0:20:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可悲的是  我被仓促地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sadly, I've been summarily dismissed
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.58,0:20:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从卡梅隆和米奇尔主人家解雇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from the employ of Masters Cameron and Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.91,0:20:40.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前者是个高尚的正人君子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The former being an utter delight,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.08,0:20:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后者则是个毫无幽默感的势利小人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the latter being a humorless snoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.29,0:20:45.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  把他弄上车  旧货店要关门了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just come on. Get him in the car. The thrift shop's closing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.54,0:20:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的有趣的旧货店是什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is this exciting thrift shop you speak of?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.00,0:20:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的很多亲戚成年后都被赶出家门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Many of my relatives were taken out of their homes...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.84,0:20:53.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被流放到大草原上自生自灭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to be released into the green pastures in their maturity-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.59,0:20:56.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你刚说了"尘脸猴"吗  -放开我  你个禽兽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you just say "Matoority?" - Unhand me, you brute!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.47,0:20:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不后悔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I regret nothing!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.47,0:21:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以给你钱  我生活富足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll pay you. I'm a comfortable man.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.68,0:21:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直从你父亲那里偷钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been stealing from your father for days.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.89,0:21:05.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上有什么能比得上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, is there any better feeling in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.20,0:21:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让耳朵在风中摇摆的感觉呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}than having your ears flap in the wind?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.69,0:21:08.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  滚出去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? Get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.68,0:21:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说真的吗  要放我自由了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean it? Sweet freedom?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.15,0:21:12.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是说你  巴克利  卡梅隆  滚下车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, not you, Barkley. Cameron, out.

