[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第二十集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.47,0:00:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛排五分钟后就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Steaks will be ready in five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.25,0:00:05.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在暴殄天物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're destroying those things.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.62,0:00:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  少点意见  -恕难从命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay, Jay, leave him alone.  - No, I'm sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.62,0:00:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那头牛已经吃够了苦头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but that cow has suffered long enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.53,0:00:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真幽默  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Fun. - Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.78,0:00:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别玩了  晚饭马上就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hang on. Dinner's ready in five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.49,0:00:15.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练布置我们练习带球上篮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coach wants us to practice layups.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.44,0:00:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超难的动作  是舞蹈与力量的怪混搭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They are deceptively hard- a curious mix of dance and strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.88,0:00:21.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你这又把档次拉低了  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're making it lame again. - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.22,0:00:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  那个教练  -我讨厌那家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay, Dios mio, that coach. - Oh, I hate that guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.85,0:00:26.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他激发了俩小子的积极性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He seems to have the kids motivated.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.66,0:00:27.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你没亲眼见过那家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Dad, you haven't seen him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.99,0:00:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对小家伙们又是讽又是骂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He taunts the kids. He's abusive.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.63,0:00:32.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要是在哥伦比亚足联  老早之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, if this was a Colombian soccer league, long time ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.59,0:00:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队里孩子就会把他拉出去  咔嚓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}one of the kids would have taken that guy out and-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.02,0:00:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练本就该严格要求他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A coach is supposed to ride the kids hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.59,0:00:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  你说句话  -那家伙过分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil, help me out here. - He's a mean man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.71,0:00:42.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真是妇人之仁  -你去看场比赛就明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Oh, you're such a woman.  - Come to the game. You'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.04,0:00:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙真的很操蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This guy's a real motherscratcher.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.37,0:00:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我的脏话  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pardon the language, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.02,0:00:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只对歌洛莉亚说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Gloria"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.63,0:00:46.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他最好淡定点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He better cool it,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.34,0:00:49.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则就别怪左将军和右元帅出手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or I'm gonna introduce him to the Captain and Tennille.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.26,0:00:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  迟了  我工作缠身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry we're late. I was at work.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.39,0:00:55.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他最近爱念工作  -烧烤快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, he loves to say that. - And happy barbecue.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.73,0:00:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从米奇尔待业家中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Since Mitchell is between jobs,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.83,0:01:00.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在一家贺卡店找了份兼职\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've taken a part-time job at a greeting card store,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.50,0:01:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱死这份工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which I love.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.46,0:01:04.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  因为我有员工折扣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Plus, with my discount,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.21,0:01:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可省下了一笔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we're saving a fortune.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.26,0:01:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花一大笔钱去买贺卡  哪里算省钱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How is spending a ton of money on greeting cards saving us a fortune?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.77,0:01:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算算就知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's math.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.57,0:01:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  我算给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really not. Look it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.60,0:01:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2.95美元  2.95美元  4.95美元\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}2.95. 2.95. 4.95.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.42,0:01:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-六折  -2.95美元\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Forty percent off.  - 2.95.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.32,0:01:22.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-3.95美元  -六折  六折\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-3.95.  - Forty percent off. Forty percent off.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.96,0:01:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我有个高尔夫球友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, I got this golf buddy of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.29,0:01:27.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不错  事业有成  你们找机会谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great guy. Super successful. You two should talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.99,0:01:29.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准他有适合你的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It could mean a job for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.24,0:01:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  爸  但是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thanks, Dad, but I'm-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.63,0:01:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现阶段还没找工作的打算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not really looking for anything right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.32,0:01:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不过  -对  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But-  - Yeah, that's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.25,0:01:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我挣钱养家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}With me bringing home the bacon,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.29,0:01:36.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔不急着找工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell doesn't have to rush into anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.20,0:01:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们那个只要贺卡不要钱计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I know you have all that greeting card "Screw you" Money,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.71,0:01:40.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  跟这家伙谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but, uh, talk to the guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.51,0:01:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他说  你明早会给他电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's expecting your call in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.92,0:01:44.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  我心领了  但以后  -受不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, I appreciate it, but in the future- I can't stand this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.38,0:01:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  但是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am sorry, but I-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.77,0:01:48.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  那几块牛排五分钟前就烤好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Those steaks have been done for five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.68,0:01:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把它们从烤架上夹下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm taking 'em off the grill.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.14,0:01:54.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  你的心情我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I know how it feels
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.00,0:01:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事他都要插上一脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to have him stick his nose where it doesn't belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.67,0:01:57.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  又不是第一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No biggie. It's just Jay being Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.97,0:01:59.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天我也会为人岳父\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But one day I'm gonna be a grandfather,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.39,0:02:01.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时各位最好都把自个儿的"肉"藏好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then everybody better hide their meat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.57,0:02:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这美女是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh. Who's she?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.08,0:02:21.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate it when you do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.50,0:02:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这帅哥是谁  -查理·宾格温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who's he? - It's Charlie Bingham.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.44,0:02:25.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我爸让我联系的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's the guy that my dad wanted me to call.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.11,0:02:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搜了他  看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&} I googled him. Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.95,0:02:28.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是"地球人"服装企业的老板\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, he owns Earthgear Apparel.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.27,0:02:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的滑雪裤就是这牌子的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have their ski pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.85,0:02:31.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你又  你又不滑雪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? You don't- You don't ski.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.77,0:02:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有好几件工装裤  我也没在码头上班呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have cargo pants and I don't work at the docks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.45,0:02:35.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  真是让我自惭形秽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}God, I feel like such a slacker.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.86,0:02:38.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他年纪轻轻就已大有作为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, he has done so much for being so young.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.39,0:02:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  他创立了不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, look. He's opened up a dozen
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.22,0:02:42.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,环保基金会和管理委员会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}environmental foundations and conservancies.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.09,0:02:44.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真牛  -那你要给他电话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wow.  - So, you gonna- you gonna call him?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.71,0:02:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想好  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. I mean, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.94,0:02:49.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前说好了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I sort of promised myself and you...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.01,0:02:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先休息一段时间  而且\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'd take a little time off, and-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.74,0:02:53.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-而且你也享受这份闲暇  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And you are loving your time off.  - Totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.19,0:02:57.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快要抓狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am losing my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.90,0:02:59.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我爱莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As much as I love Lily-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.52,0:03:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她看得比什么都重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is, you know, more than life itself-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.76,0:03:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  没办法做个居家奶爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am- whoo- not cut out to be a stay-at-home dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.68,0:03:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但该轮到卡梅隆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, but it's Cameron's turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.56,0:03:09.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该轮到他到外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's Cameron's turn to be out in the world...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.31,0:03:11.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟其他成年人打交道  而我待在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}interacting with other grown-ups while I get to stay at home...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.88,0:03:14.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把《爱探险的朵拉》游戏给解决掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and plot the death of Dora the Explorer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.50,0:03:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如拿砖头塞满她背包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like to fill her backpack with bricks
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.36,0:03:20.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把她扔进拐杖糖河里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and throw her into Candy Cane River.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.81,0:03:23.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我应该  应该打给他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I don't know. Should I- Should I call him?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.07,0:03:25.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  打了让你爸死心也好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. Maybe just to get your dad off your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.78,0:03:27.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  没错  -我觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. Yeah. - I mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.24,0:03:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想你现在去上班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because the last thing I want for you is to take a job right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.04,0:03:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对现状很满意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am loving our life.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.94,0:03:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正陷入绝境\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am in a really dark space.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:37.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与莉莉分开简直像酷刑一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Being away from my Lily is literally torture.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.11,0:03:39.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我又不能给米奇尔压力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I can't pressure Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.11,0:03:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我真的真的真的想他快点再就业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I really, really, really just want him to get a job...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.37,0:03:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我又能做回居家奶爸兼贤妻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I can go back to being a stay-at-home dad/trophy wife!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.72,0:03:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.32,0:03:52.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加把劲  姑娘们  跑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, ladies! Move it!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.01,0:03:55.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  乌龟都比你们爬得快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Goodness gracious! Turtles run faster!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.84,0:03:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.57,0:03:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还能跑得再慢一点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you run any slower?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.72,0:04:00.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢说你们跑得更慢都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I dare you to run slower!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.55,0:04:02.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看  -他不过是在激发大家斗志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You see?  - He's just trying to light a fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.39,0:04:04.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿我就把丫给"治"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'll light him on fire!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.39,0:04:06.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么老是要我来看这玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do I always have to come to these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.62,0:04:08.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你爱你弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you love your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.79,0:04:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你不让他来我的管弦音乐会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you make him come to my orchestra concerts?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.27,0:04:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们爱你弟  好样的卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because we love your brother. Good job, Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.16,0:04:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投篮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shoot!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.65,0:04:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪尔加多  你是要把我气死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Delgado, you're killing me, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.98,0:04:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样我都爱你  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you, Manny, no matter what!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.49,0:04:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.45,0:04:29.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. That's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.58,0:04:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我再给你回复  对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, well, I'll let you know. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.58,0:04:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.05,0:04:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理·宾格温邀请我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, so, Charlie Bingham just invited us over...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.04,0:04:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他的海边别墅聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to his beach house for a little get-together.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.76,0:04:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  你是怎么答复他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Uh, what did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.33,0:04:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我先跟你商量下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said I'd check with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.06,0:04:43.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得要去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, what do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.90,0:04:46.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.97,0:04:49.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得推掉人家的盛情邀请不大礼貌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I think it'd be rude not to hear him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.26,0:04:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  是这样  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. I mean, yeah. You're probably right.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.47,0:04:53.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那就去  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.11,0:04:55.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过虑了  我不会再就业的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And don't worry. You know, I'm not gonna take any job.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:57.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You better not.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.40,0:05:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just miss-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.44,0:05:02.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.30,0:05:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.16,0:05:11.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太想  我的烤奶酪三明治了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just miss...  my grilled cheese sandwiches!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.69,0:05:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表现不错  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're doing great, Luke-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.08,0:05:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是比谁打得烂得话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if your goal is to suck!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.47,0:05:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  你  -我出手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil, you-  - I'm on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.36,0:05:17.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  -等等我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay.  - Wait for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.52,0:05:19.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-教练  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Coach. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.62,0:05:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指导很投入很激情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, look. We appreciate your passion,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.52,0:05:23.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but some of us are worried that
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.12,0:05:24.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚷嚷可能会起反效果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the yelling is getting counterproductive.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.53,0:05:26.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心里有数  跑  笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got this. Come on, stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.44,0:05:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你没  你有的只是烂态度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you don't "Got this." What you got is a bad attitude.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.20,0:05:31.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.99,0:05:34.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是家长  就是那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I happen to be the stepfather of-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.59,0:05:40.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是谁不重要  你要做的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doesn't matter who. What you need to start doing...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.13,0:05:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多一些指导  少一些嚷嚷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is a little more coaching and a little less yelling.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.34,0:05:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我要是再听见你叫他们笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause if I hear you call one of these kids stupid again,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.24,0:05:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓  我会脱鞋对着你的脑袋砸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I swear to God, I'll throw a shoe at your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.42,0:05:51.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操  我才懒得教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Screw it. I don't need this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.49,0:05:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你能教得比我好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think you can do a better job?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.43,0:05:54.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来教啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.62,0:05:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我刚在跟他谈呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you know, I was handling it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.38,0:06:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我注意到你的小左和小右爆发了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I saw how you broke out Peaches and Herb.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.82,0:06:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是左将军和\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the Captain and-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.21,0:06:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你们之前的教练要离开一段时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. So, your old coach had to leave for a little while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.67,0:06:12.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  他病了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? Is he sick?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.21,0:06:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  他病得很严重  -那他会死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. He's very, very sick.  - Is he going to die?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.75,0:06:17.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人皆有一死  孩子们  现在关注当下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody dies, boys. Let's focus on what's important.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.33,0:06:19.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时后下场就开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our next game is in one hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.15,0:06:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要团结一致  重拳出击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We are going to go from being five fingers to being a fist.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:24.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么样  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How does that sound?  - Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.10,0:06:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听不到  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can't hear you.  - Great!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.94,0:06:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.85,0:06:30.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  我刚和裁判谈过了  我来执教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, gentlemen. I talked to the referee. I'm coaching.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.33,0:06:33.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是我  -菲尔  我以前教过橄榄球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, really? 'Cause I-  - Phil, I coached football.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.67,0:06:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我之前教过篮球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, I actually coached basketball.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.29,0:06:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我能让小家伙们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I can get these guys-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.64,0:06:39.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别急  让你当助理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Relax. You've already got the assistant job.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.09,0:06:41.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在去给我们带几瓶水好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now you think you can round us up some waters?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.32,0:06:44.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  -去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah.  - Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.96,0:06:46.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  你们要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gentlemen, this is what I need.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.27,0:06:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们把他们打败  打得落花流水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you to hit 'em, and I want you to hit 'em hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.27,0:06:50.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟岳父相处真不易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Father-in-laws are tough,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.58,0:06:52.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为既不能让他对你呼来喝去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you can't let 'em push you around...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.44,0:06:54.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时又要对他表示尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you also have to show them respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.59,0:06:56.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是在走钢丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like walking a tightrope.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.19,0:06:58.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便提一下  我能走  因为我练过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which, by the way, I can do, because I went to trapeze school.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.77,0:07:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰呢  我深表怀疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did Jay? I doubt it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.68,0:07:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  当你进入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, when you back into-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.41,0:07:04.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我要走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I'm gonna take off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.51,0:07:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去给艾丽克斯买几件衣服  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm gonna buy Alex some clothes.  - Okeydoke.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.26,0:07:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不是你在指导\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How come you're not coaching?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.72,0:07:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你爸教过橄榄球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause your dad coached football.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.44,0:07:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.07,0:07:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚会补偿你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I am going to make it up to you tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.91,0:07:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-而我会在脑子里想着你爸  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And I'll be thinking of your dad while you do.  - Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.06,0:07:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没心思了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Disturbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.73,0:07:23.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  -来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Phil.  - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.12,0:07:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How's it going?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.35,0:07:27.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好着呢  你爸教过橄榄球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. Great. Your dad coached football.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.46,0:07:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一个受害同胞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah. A fellow victim.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.95,0:07:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你帮我们带莉莉  我知道有点急\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you again for taking care of Lily. I know it's last-minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.38,0:07:33.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别见外了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. Don't be silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.48,0:07:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们或许该待一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll probably just stick around for a few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.97,0:07:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不跟我们在一起的时候会抓狂  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know how fussy she gets when we pass her off, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.90,0:07:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她好着呢  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh. She seems fine.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.54,0:07:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在要上班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. I think she's getting used to
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.84,0:07:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看她已经习惯你不在身边了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}being away from you now that you have the new job.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.54,0:07:50.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈以你为豪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mwah! So proud of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.57,0:07:53.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得谈谈  -好  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We need to talk.  - Okay. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.71,0:07:56.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I love you,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.66,0:07:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的鼓励\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your words of encouragement
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.56,0:08:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼓励了其他队员开我玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}encourage the other kids to make fun of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.18,0:08:02.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.78,0:08:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下场比赛我会一声不发  保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I won't say anything else on the next game. Promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.85,0:08:08.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都很清楚  你的拉丁热血会让你的保证无效\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We both know that your Latin blood makes that impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.81,0:08:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你下场回避一下会更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think it would be better if you didn't come to the next game.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.73,0:08:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.13,0:08:30.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们家简直就像贫民窟  -就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I hate our house.  - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.84,0:08:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  这是干嘛用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's- What's this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.40,0:08:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  但是很高级\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know, but it's fancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.15,0:08:37.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别在上面跳  来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop- Stop playing with it. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.18,0:08:38.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别弄坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just- Don't break it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.00,0:08:42.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Mitchell!  - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.76,0:08:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-查理·宾格温  -幸会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Charlie Bingham.  - Nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.24,0:08:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -这是我的伴侣卡梅隆·塔克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi.  - This is my partner, Cameron Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.53,0:08:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-幸会  -卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Pleasure.  - Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.51,0:08:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚刚直开进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, we just went ahead and
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.82,0:08:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停在车道那个圆盘上面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}parked on that round thingy in the driveway.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.65,0:08:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这样  没问题吧  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is that- That's fine, right?  - No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.08,0:08:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是转盘  这样你就不用倒车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a turntable, so you don't have to back out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.86,0:08:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有车用转盘  穿着胶皮衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have a car turntable and you're wearing rubber.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.88,0:08:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是高富帅蝙蝠侠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're like Batman.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.42,0:09:00.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还真是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really am.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.43,0:09:01.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.85,0:09:03.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把音乐关小点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turn the music down!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.71,0:09:08.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒舍  见谅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pardon the get-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.76,0:09:10.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的浪很棒  你们冲浪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Killer waves today. You guys surf?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.82,0:09:12.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只网上冲浪  跟卖家讨价还价\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, only for bargains on the Web.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.70,0:09:13.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙打个招呼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody say hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.47,0:09:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们好  -你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi.  - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.41,0:09:15.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们好  -这是茱莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Hi.  - That's Jolie.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.98,0:09:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的欧洲分部总监\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's head of my Europe division.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.35,0:09:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她打牌出老千  你就有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She cheats at poker. You do.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.40,0:09:20.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边是我的女友珍妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's my girlfriend, Jenny.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.77,0:09:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她调的玛格丽塔好极了  来一杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She makes a hell of a margarita. Want one?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.19,0:09:25.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然要  -不  现在  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Absolutely.  - Oh, not right- Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.43,0:09:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  米奇尔·普里契特和他的伴儿卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody, Mitchell Pritchett and his partner, Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.15,0:09:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生意伙"伴"  做并购的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Business partners. Mergers and acquisitions.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.50,0:09:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开玩笑啦  我们是同志  -别多话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm kidding. We're gay.  - Stop talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.29,0:09:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没压力的时候  我是社交场上的好手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When things are relaxed, I'm great in social situations.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.99,0:09:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔冈琴圆桌会我也能轻松应对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would have fit in at the Algonquin Round Table.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.99,0:09:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[纽约市一些社会名流的非正式聚会]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.43,0:09:42.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是压力大的时候   我就紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But when the stakes are high, I get a little tense.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.74,0:09:44.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计会直接把那圆桌打翻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd be the guy that would knock over the round table.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.95,0:09:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后桃乐茜·帕克[已故名诗人]会嘲弄我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then Dorothy Parker would make a quip,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.44,0:09:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詹姆斯·托伯[已故名作家]大笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}James Thurber would laugh,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.51,0:09:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后我哭着鼻子  掩面而逃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then I would end up leaving, crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.93,0:09:52.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你已经潜逃多久了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How long you been on the lam?  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.99,0:09:55.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你四周顾视像是有联邦探员在追捕你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you are looking around like the feds are after you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.41,0:09:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有  我们赶快把衣服买完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm not. Let's just get this over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.89,0:09:59.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.59,0:10:00.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  是她们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. It's them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.46,0:10:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们不是你的同学嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Oh, you know those girls from school.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.84,0:10:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  -走  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey!  - Let's go! Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.07,0:10:09.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你  你这是怎么了  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What- What is your problem?  - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.59,0:10:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时后车上见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll meet you at the car in an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.75,0:10:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  妈  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please, Mom. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.52,0:10:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  珍娜  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, Jenna.  - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  我的宝贝女儿长成了少女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And just like that- my baby girl became a teenager.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.64,0:10:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她进入了那个讨厌的阶段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She entered that dreaded phase
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.89,0:10:26.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的存在让她感到尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where my very existence embarrasses her.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.65,0:10:28.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我来安慰一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I think I can help.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.65,0:10:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟你妈不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.22,0:10:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  这是你妈的经典表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. That's your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.78,0:10:36.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背脊一阵发凉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I just got chills.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.36,0:10:41.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先要坦白我是你的粉丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, first off, I'm a fan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.20,0:10:45.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在法庭上有一面之缘  -当真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Saw you in court once.  - Seriously?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.02,0:10:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  梅休诉普罗泰克一案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Mayhew versus Propyltech.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.05,0:10:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是个不可多得的好律师  -不敢当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You are a good lawyer.  - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.15,0:10:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我的离婚交给你处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you'd handled my divorce,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.78,0:10:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这房子肯定是现在的两倍大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this house would be twice as big.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.49,0:10:56.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好到不行  你可争不赢他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, he's better than good. Try winning an argument with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.31,0:10:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-昨晚我想去吃印度菜  -你又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Last night I wanted to have Indian food-  - And we're talking again.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.06,0:11:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康奈尔大学和哥伦比亚法学院第一名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Top of your class at Cornell and Columbia Law.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.74,0:11:02.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作机会一大把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Had your pick of jobs,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.89,0:11:07.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却选择专攻环保法  直到上个月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but instead chose to work in environmental law- until last month.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.40,0:11:09.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还曾是优秀的花样滑冰运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well- And he used to be a really great figure skater.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.15,0:11:12.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么不干了  -他姐不想滑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why'd you quit?  - His sister lost interest,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.31,0:11:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后就  -他问我为什么辞职\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and then there was- - He means my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.38,0:11:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说花样滑冰也行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could tell me about figure skating too.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.16,0:11:19.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  她确实不想滑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, well, it was- She did lose interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.39,0:11:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行了  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's enough.  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.00,0:11:23.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美人啊小美人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, que linda. Ay, que linda.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.04,0:11:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我不知道你们也来这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my gosh. I didn't know you guys were gonna be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.81,0:11:25.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hola, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.73,0:11:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.30,0:11:29.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是看够篮球赛了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had enough basketball for one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.59,0:11:31.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是嘛  来  抱抱  小可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I know. Come here, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.51,0:11:35.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小可爱  你爱我  你要我给你买裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sweet thing. You love me and you want me to buy you a dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.73,0:11:38.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  但是我先要给她买几双鞋子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. But I'm gonna buy her some shoes first. Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.64,0:11:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  莉莉  要我给你买裙子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that, Lily? Do you want me to buy you a dress?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.48,0:11:42.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说"好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She said "Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.79,0:11:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Yes"?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.77,0:11:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没说"好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She did not say "Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.12,0:11:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  数到三说"胜"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, "Win" On three.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.79,0:11:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二三  胜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One, two, three- Win!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.20,0:11:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了掩护走位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't forget the pick and roll.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.38,0:11:56.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对手不知道怎么防  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- These guys won't know how to defend it.  - Phil,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.83,0:11:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别把我的队员搞糊涂了好吗  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- try not to confuse my boys, okay?  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.30,0:12:00.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我睡了你女儿  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I sleep with your daughter.  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.41,0:12:01.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good luck!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.49,0:12:03.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  上场  快快快  跑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Let's go! Let's go! Come on. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来  快快快  记住我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's get out there. Hustle up. Get the tip, get the tip.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.84,0:12:08.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意  抢球  走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Watch, skip and go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:11.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  跑起来  跑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! All right. Keep the hustle, keep the hustle.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.24,0:12:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  小子  别让他们掌握主动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, boys. Don't let 'em push you around.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.06,0:12:15.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  防守好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! All right, little defense!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.64,0:12:17.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意防守\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Play defense!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.55,0:12:18.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微侦探了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did a little scouting,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.49,0:12:20.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对手只有两个投手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the other team only has two shooters.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.15,0:12:21.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们把他俩防好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If we isolate both of them-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.49,0:12:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  菲尔  好  谢谢  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good, Phil, good. Thank you. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.32,0:12:25.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  集中精神  你看什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, pay attention! What are you looking at?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.48,0:12:26.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.75,0:12:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是2004年的事情了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that was in 2004.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.62,0:12:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, tell me this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.19,0:12:38.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳能电厂会有哪方面的阻力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are the regulatory challenges of a solar farm?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.03,0:12:41.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各方面都有  农业方面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, well, you know, it could be anything- uh, agricultural-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.74,0:12:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军队方面  物种保护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Military, protected species,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.65,0:12:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讽刺的是  甚至会牵扯某些环保组织\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}ironically, even some, uh, environmental groups.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.82,0:12:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该喝完了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you got all of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.96,0:12:48.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think you got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.23,0:12:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我去满上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. I'm just gonna freshen this up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.51,0:12:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-问你个问题  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let me ask you a question.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.98,0:12:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留胡子感觉如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you like the beard?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.10,0:12:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想留  珍妮不同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm thinking of growing one. Jenny's against it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.35,0:13:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  我觉得挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Well, I-I've been very happy with mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.50,0:13:03.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  决定留了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it. I'm doin' it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.32,0:13:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挣不少钱  我想用来做些好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I've made a fortune. I want to use it for some good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.98,0:13:09.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要律师帮我定位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need a lawyer to help me navigate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.30,0:13:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺喜欢你  你懂我  你意下如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like you. You get me. So, in or out?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.73,0:13:15.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.58,0:13:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm very sorry.  - It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.55,0:13:24.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个重大的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, that's a very big question.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.26,0:13:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我要先跟我家那位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I'm obviously gonna have to
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.11,0:13:27.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莽撞的"野牛"  商量一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}go talk to my- bull in a china shop.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.99,0:13:29.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-失陪一下  -行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'll be right back.  - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.76,0:13:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好谈  这可是人生重大决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Talk it over. It's a major life decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.95,0:13:34.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  珍妮  胡子我留定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jenny! The beard is on!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.06,0:13:40.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  该给你买美美的鞋子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Lily, it's time to buy you beautiful shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.26,0:13:42.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  我刚看到有条很好看的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, no, no. I saw another really cute dress for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.58,0:13:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她已经买了6件新裙子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. But she has already six new dresses.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.35,0:13:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在要的是绑带鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What she needs is strappy shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.31,0:13:50.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯过来了  待会见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's Alex. I'll-I'll see you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.92,0:13:52.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, honey. Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.61,0:13:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我说了待会儿车上见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I said I'd meet you at the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.79,0:14:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.63,0:14:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.62,0:14:06.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想要个女儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still wish you had a daughter?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.78,0:14:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼不想我去看他比赛  -深表同情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Manny didn't want me at the game today.  - Oh, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.00,0:14:14.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没什么  -不  怎么会没什么  烂透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's okay.  - No, it's not okay. It sucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.93,0:14:17.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想念宝宝  他们从不会让我们走开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss babies. They never tell you to go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.58,0:14:19.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  也不会让我们在车里等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Or wait in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.07,0:14:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know about you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.84,0:14:23.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不会站在这自怨自艾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I'm not gonna stand here and feel sorry for myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.62,0:14:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们该做什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what we should do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.19,0:14:26.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把肚子搞大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get pregnant.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.91,0:14:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说的是去吃冰淇林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was gonna say go for ice cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.92,0:14:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我们先实施你的方案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. We'll do yours first. Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.10,0:14:33.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke! Luke!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.95,0:14:37.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周围没有对手  有什么好防守的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's hard to guard a player if there's no player near you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.48,0:14:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We good in the hood?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.34,0:14:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那帮家伙简直让人倍受打击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a uniquely frustrating group of boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.59,0:14:43.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实  我有个小建议  停止联防\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hear you. Um, one thing that might help- instead of a zone,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.94,0:14:45.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转而进行一对一防守\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if you switch to a simple man-to-man.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.85,0:14:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可以的  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got this.  - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.64,0:14:48.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是根据记分板数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause according to the scoreboard,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.66,0:14:50.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只拿了四分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the only thing you got is four points.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.76,0:14:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.12,0:14:56.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要跟你谈谈  -我要跟你谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I need to talk to you.  - I need to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.27,0:14:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice top.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.67,0:15:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这来  你  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come here. You- You-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.16,0:15:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  小卡  你得放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam- Cam, you have got to relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.64,0:15:09.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过我不会接受新工作的  除非\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told you I wouldn't take a job without-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.87,0:15:11.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快接受吧  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Take the job.  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.35,0:15:13.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你答应下这份工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you to take the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.48,0:15:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你想让我在家带莉莉呢  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you liked having me home with Lily. I-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.75,0:15:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想  我是说  我想  我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't. I mean, I do. I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.09,0:15:19.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怀念和莉莉一起的好时光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss my time with Lily,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.57,0:15:21.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这太自私了  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I know it's selfish of me, but-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.38,0:15:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我想要工作  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, I want the job.   - You do?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.24,0:15:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.75,0:15:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱莉莉  但是我讨厌说话依依呀呀地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I love Lily, but I hate baby talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.76,0:15:30.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢依依呀呀地说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love baby talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.05,0:15:35.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-答应下这份工作  -答应下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let's go get this job.  - Let's get this job.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.18,0:15:38.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay.  - Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.17,0:15:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锁住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's locked.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.13,0:15:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, just
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.79,0:15:44.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello? Hey, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.37,0:15:46.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.12,0:15:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们听不到  我们困在这了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're not gonna hear us. We're trapped out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.10,0:15:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么一惊一乍的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just stop being so dramatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.74,0:15:51.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从车库出去  这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll just go through the garage, with the-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.42,0:15:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪他要雇你  你能应对危机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why he wants to hire you. You're good in crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.82,0:15:57.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, yeesh. What-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.36,0:16:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没开  -再按按看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's not opening.  - Push it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.14,0:16:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我听到动静了  但是  -用力点按\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm hearing things, but it's not-   - Push it harder.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.23,0:16:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个  这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not- Is it this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.39,0:16:12.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也听到了  什么声响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hear something. What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.37,0:16:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  别乱按  住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Stop touching- Stop-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.24,0:16:23.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  是这个  行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This- Oh, that was it. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.43,0:16:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  天啊  这  -天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell! Oh, my God. Did-   - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.86,0:16:29.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -不  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God!   - No, Cam!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.22,0:16:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  我们  我们弄的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, we- Did we do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.94,0:16:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么交代\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are we gonna say?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.32,0:16:37.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作我答应下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will take the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.27,0:16:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不然你哪来钱修车  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Kinda think you have to now.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.43,0:16:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伙子  你们一个队的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, you're on the same team!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.67,0:16:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Time out!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.12,0:16:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-暂停  -给我过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Time out! - Get over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.52,0:16:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  我们刚刚合计的几个战术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys, earlier we practiced a few set plays.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.15,0:16:58.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里提到让你们从队友手中抢球了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did any of them involve wrestling the ball from your own teammate?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.69,0:17:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说要使出浑身解数的  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But you said to be aggressive.  - Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.64,0:17:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是对你队友使  待着别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not on your own team! Wait here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.69,0:17:07.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得你来教  我干不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You gotta coach. I can't take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.26,0:17:08.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是在跟我说吗  -是  是跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You talkin' to me?   - Yeah, I'm talkin' to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.58,0:17:10.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得接手  我就快输了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You gotta take over. I'm about to lose it out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.61,0:17:11.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真不容易  教练\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That sounds tough, Coach.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.84,0:17:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你这是怎么回事  -教练  该继续了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's your problem? - Hey, Coach! Ticktock.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.13,0:17:17.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前跟教练交涉  你把我挤开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was dealing with the coach. You pushed me aside.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.30,0:17:19.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给孩子们指导  你把我挤开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was dealing with the boys. You pushed me aside.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.38,0:17:20.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信不信由你  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Believe it or not, Jay,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.77,0:17:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事我比你擅长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}there are some things that I am better at than you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.65,0:17:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-砰  终于把话摊开了  -老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bam! It's out there.   - Oh, for God's sake.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.64,0:17:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-教练  -他叫你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Coach!   - He's calling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.42,0:17:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我能理解你很不爽  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen. I don't blame you for being angry. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.10,0:17:31.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我习惯了主事  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm used to taking charge. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.30,0:17:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始就该让你来做教练\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should have let you coach from the get-go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.59,0:17:35.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.03,0:17:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你  -不  烧烤那事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I love you.  - No. The barbecue.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.08,0:17:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, for God's sake.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.69,0:17:47.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你烤的牛排肯定好吃  不会咬不动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure your steaks would have been delicious... and not chewy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.43,0:17:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  我来  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. I'll do it.  - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.29,0:17:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说青出于蓝而胜于蓝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And so the student becomes the master.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.55,0:17:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-昔日王者  -算了  不劳你驾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The once mighty- - You know what? Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.67,0:17:56.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不不  我来  我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no. I'm good. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.31,0:17:59.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队员们  想不想以赢家的身份走出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey. Guys. Who wants to go out like a champ?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.06,0:17:59.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah!  - Me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.99,0:18:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这态度  好  乔迪  你发球给卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love it! Okay, Jordy, you inbound to Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.81,0:18:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你把卢克的防守挡开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you set a pick on Luke's man
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.61,0:18:05.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后去球篮下面候位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and roll to the bucket.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.86,0:18:08.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克你知道该怎么做了  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, you know what to do.  - No, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.84,0:18:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-传地板球给曼尼  -但是  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bounce-pass to Manny.  - But, Dad-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.53,0:18:15.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练  曼尼整个赛季都没进过球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coach, Manny hasn't taken a single shot all season.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.11,0:18:16.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机会来时他会把握住的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then chances are he'll be open.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.58,0:18:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  队员们  上场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, guys. Let's bring it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.98,0:18:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  都伸出手来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey. Bring it in.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.26,0:18:23.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给对手秀秀我们的气势\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's show these guys what kind of team they're about to beat.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.50,0:18:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数到三喊"小德伯必胜"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Huh? "Li'I Dribblers" On three.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.07,0:18:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二三  小德伯必胜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One, two, three- Li'I Dribblers!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.48,0:18:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红队场边发球  开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, red ball. Side out. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.07,0:18:36.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的执教理念是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's my coaching philosophy?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.77,0:18:40.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-给孩子一只鸟  -就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Give a kid a bird-  - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.51,0:18:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就会像那些怪叔叔一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he becomes one of those weird dudes
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.90,0:18:44.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把鸟放在肩膀四处晃荡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who walks around with a bird on his shoulder.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.71,0:18:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但给他一双翅膀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But give him a pair of wings,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.31,0:18:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就能飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he can fly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.35,0:18:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他眼高手低  技术太烂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Unless he has absolutely no hand-eye coordination.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.14,0:18:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I support you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.07,0:19:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.66,0:19:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你晚了20分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.48,0:19:11.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  我非常非常抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, I am so, so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我不该这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it's no excuse,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.77,0:19:16.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我人在学校身不由己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I've been feeling a lot of pressure at school.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.59,0:19:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自朋友圈的压力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, with friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.84,0:19:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常非常爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I love you so much,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.25,0:19:22.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为我所做的一切我都心存感恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I appreciate everything you do for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.94,0:19:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是你的乖乖女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm still your little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.78,0:19:32.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  妈妈听你这么说真开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey! That was so sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.24,0:19:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我20美元吗  我们想去看电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I get $20? A bunch of us are going to a movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.66,0:19:37.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再去吃个饭什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we're gonna get something to eat afterwards.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.71,0:19:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珍娜她哥会载我们回家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jenna's brother's gonna take us home.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.19,0:19:44.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  没问题  亲爱的  给你40\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Of course. Sweetie, you know what? Take 40.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.28,0:19:46.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -没什么  给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my gosh.  - Yeah. That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.25,0:19:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢妈  -去吧  玩得开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks, Mom.  - Go on. Have a great time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.56,0:19:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  亲爱的  逛街的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Alex, honey? When you're out shopping,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.45,0:19:56.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好给自己买件胸罩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you might wanna pick yourself up a training bra.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.92,0:19:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在用不上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know you don't need one now,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.07,0:20:00.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的小咪咪早晚会长出来的嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your little boobies are gonna come in soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.24,0:20:02.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈爱你  小猫猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mommy loves you, kitten!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.12,0:20:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲亲  亲亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mwah! Mwah!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.54,0:20:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你还敢耍我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Teach her to screw with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.70,0:20:15.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我阻断了防守  然后跑到球篮下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I set a pick and then rolled towards the basket.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.57,0:20:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克把球传给我  我投篮  几乎进了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke passed to me. I shot the ball and almost made it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.58,0:20:23.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天给莉莉买了件非常萌的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bought Lily the cutest little dress today.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.96,0:20:27.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我从对手那里抢到球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then I stole the ball from the other team,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.12,0:20:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后360逆天翻转上篮  几乎灌篮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}did a 360 and almost dunked it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.81,0:20:30.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真牛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.06,0:20:34.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天跟莉莉玩得太开心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. I just had the best day today with Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.83,0:20:36.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小姑娘萌翻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That girl's so sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.94,0:20:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我下周六有比赛  你来看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a game next Saturday. You could come.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.84,0:20:42.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  谢谢  我不想去给你丢脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's okay. I wouldn't want to embarrass you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:46.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天我应该会带莉莉去吃纸杯蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll probably take Lily out for cupcakes. Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.78,0:20:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.75,0:20:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提点一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Any suggestions?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.25,0:20:53.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一般用耳环哄她开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I usually go with earrings.

