[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.79,0:04:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.79,0:04:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.79,0:04:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.92,0:00:04.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  吃早饭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids, breakfast!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.10,0:00:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.08,0:00:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  把他们叫下来好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, would you get them?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.48,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Just a sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.94,0:00:13.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.74,0:00:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这真是  -算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That is - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.49,0:00:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  快下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids? Get down here!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.86,0:00:22.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们远在楼上  你们喊也没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you guys yelling at us when we're way upstairs?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.48,0:00:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-发个短信不就行了  -那是不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just text me. - All right. That's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.49,0:00:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能穿这套衣服出门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, wow! You're not wearing that outfit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.58,0:00:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这衣服怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's wrong with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.50,0:00:28.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  对你女儿这条裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, do you have anything to say
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.86,0:00:31.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有什么意见吗  -不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- to your daughter about her skirt? - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.79,0:00:34.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-挺可爱的嘛  宝贝  -谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, yeah. That looks really cute, sweetheart. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.40,0:00:35.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  这裙子太短了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It's way too short.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.62,0:00:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家知道你是女生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People know you're a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.64,0:00:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要穿这么少给他们看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't need to prove it to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.38,0:00:40.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克又把头卡在栏杆里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke got his head stuck in the banister again.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.80,0:00:42.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去吧  婴儿油在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got it. Where's the baby oil?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.01,0:00:46.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们床头的  我不知道  你自己找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's on our bedside tab- I don't know. Find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.64,0:00:49.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.69,0:00:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(190,42)\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1}菲尔&克莱尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.69,0:00:52.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在成长期间简直无法无天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was out of control growing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.77,0:00:54.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  我坦白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There, you know? I said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.27,0:00:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(191,233)\fs26\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1}结婚16年
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.77,0:00:57.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想让我的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I just don't want my kids...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.53,0:00:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重蹈我的覆辙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to make the same bad mistakes I made.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.32,0:01:03.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要海莉没有半裸着在佛罗里达沙滩上醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-If Haley never wakes up on a beach in Florida, half-naked,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.53,0:01:05.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算完成我的任务了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've done my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.54,0:01:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我俩的任务  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Our job. - Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.29,0:01:10.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算完成了我俩的任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've done our job.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.29,0:01:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  曼尼  踢球啊  踢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Vamos, Manny! Kick it! Kick it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.83,0:01:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让他  踢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't let him- Kick it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.59,0:01:17.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  加油  往右跑  往右\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, go! A la derecha! A la derecha!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.51,0:01:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.01,0:01:22.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他下绊子  杰  怎么没人吹犯规\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He tripped him, Jay. Where's the penalty?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.39,0:01:24.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  他们已经落后了6个球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, they're 0 and 6.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.08,0:01:24.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小点声叫喊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's take it down a notch.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.08,0:01:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(193,41)}杰&歌洛莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.36,0:01:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(195,220)\fs26\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1}结婚6个月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.36,0:01:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不同世界的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're very different.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.28,0:01:29.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰来自城市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay's from the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.87,0:01:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的生意做得很大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He has a big business.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.44,0:01:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来自一个小山村\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I come from a small village.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.73,0:01:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穷困潦倒  但风景怡人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Very poor but very, very beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.23,0:01:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们村拥有全哥伦比亚最多的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the number one village in all Colombia for all the-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.32,0:01:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个词怎么说来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the word?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.19,0:01:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶杀案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Murders.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.58,0:01:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  凶杀案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. The murders.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.58,0:01:47.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  拦住他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, stop him!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.41,0:01:49.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拦住他  你可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop him! You can do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.96,0:01:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真烂  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it, Manny!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.75,0:01:58.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练  该让那孩子下场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, coach. You gotta take that kid out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.38,0:02:01.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让他下场吗  不如我让你"下场"如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna take him out? How about I take you out?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.33,0:02:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  -你还是操心你的儿子吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Honey, honey. - Why don't you worry about your son?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.69,0:02:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他整个上半场光忙着抓裤裆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He spent the first half with his hand in his pants!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.69,0:02:12.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那话我6周来一直想对她说来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've wanted to tell her off for the last six weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.92,0:02:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫乔希  莱恩的爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm Josh. Ryan's dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.47,0:02:19.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫歌洛莉亚·普里契特  曼尼的妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, I'm Gloria Pritchett. Manny's mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.28,0:02:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这位是你父亲吧  -她父亲?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, and this must be your dad. - Her dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.10,0:02:22.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -不  不是  真搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - No, no. That's funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.70,0:02:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能  我是她老公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, no, I'm her husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.28,0:02:25.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别被外表给骗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't be fooled by the, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.73,0:02:27.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give me a second here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.51,0:02:32.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是乖宝宝啊  是谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who is a good girl? Who's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.61,0:02:34.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.42,0:02:37.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她真可爱  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, she's adorable. - Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.92,0:02:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  小公主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, precious. Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.01,0:02:44.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚从越南领养了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, we just, uh- We just adopted her from Vietnam.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.93,0:02:47.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们第一次带她回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we're bringing her home for the first time, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.30,0:02:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她像个小天使  你们夫妻俩一定很激动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's an angel. You and your wife must be thrilled.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.18,0:02:53.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我来晚了  老爹去买点心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, sorry, sorry. Daddy needed snacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.08,0:03:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家在聊什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what are we talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.72,0:03:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在一起已经...5年了吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, we have been together for- guh, five- five years now?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.07,0:03:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们非常想要一个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, uh, we just- we decided we really wanted to have a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.39,0:03:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(193,41)}米奇尔&卡梅隆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.12,0:03:10.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始  我们想找一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, we had initially asked one of our
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.13,0:03:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女同性恋朋友做代孕母亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}lesbian friends to be a surrogate, but-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.20,0:03:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来又想  她们平时就够刻薄了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then we figured, they're already mean enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.21,0:03:16.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能想象她们怀孕后会如何变本加厉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you imagine one of 'em pregnant? Pregnant, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.08,0:03:17.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了吧  想想就怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, thank you. Ick.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.25,0:03:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到没  大家本来在逗莉莉玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You saw that, right? Everybody fawning over Lily,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.15,0:03:22.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一走进来  他们就装作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then you walk on and suddenly it's all,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.70,0:03:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看机上购物杂志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Ooh, SkyMall.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.44,0:03:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑买个电动领带架什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gotta buy a motorized tie rack."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.50,0:03:27.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得教育一下这帮人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, you know, I'm gonna give the speech.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.99,0:03:29.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are not giving the speech.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.52,0:03:31.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还得和他们一起呆上5小时呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be stuck with these people for the next five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.62,0:03:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你说得对  我错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're right, you're right. Okay. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.72,0:03:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Cream Puffs  意为泡芙或者娘娘腔]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.72,0:03:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看那个拿着泡芙的宝宝  -好吧  够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Look at that baby with those cream puffs. - Okay. Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.13,0:03:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.97,0:03:39.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这宝宝原本可能会在人满为患的孤儿院里成长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This baby would have grown up in a crowded orphanage
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.87,0:03:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏我们这些娘娘腔收养呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if it wasn't for us "Cream puffs."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.63,0:03:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们这些搞歧视的人  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And you know what? Note to all of you who judge- - Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.46,0:03:47.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我听好了  爱不分种族  信仰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hear this. Love knows no race, creed-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.02,0:03:47.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分性别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or gender.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.93,0:03:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我为你们感到羞耻  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And shame on you, - Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.27,0:03:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们这些狭隘愚昧的  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- you small-minded, ignorant few - Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.28,0:03:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干嘛  -人家说的是泡芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? -She's got the cream puffs.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位的耳机费我们请了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We would like to pay for everyone's headsets.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.05,0:04:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  你怎么老是卡在这里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buddy. Why do you keep getting stuck like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.11,0:04:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为这次能拔出来呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought I could get out this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.82,0:04:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直说了吧  他得去检查一下智商\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just gonna say it. He needs to be checked by a specialist.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.36,0:04:28.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你自由了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There. Be free.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.82,0:04:29.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚瑟王之剑拔出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excalibur.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.08,0:04:32.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-今天我有朋友来家里玩  -谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm having a friend over today. - Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.17,0:04:35.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不认识他  -是个男生吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, you don't know him. - Him? Him?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.04,0:04:39.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  男生  你会和他亲嘴吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, a boy. You gonna kiss him?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.01,0:04:41.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-闭嘴  -别激动  别激动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Shut up. - Easy. Easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:42.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-闭嘴  -你才闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, shut up! - No, you shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.51,0:04:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克和艾丽克斯  你们俩出去解决好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, Alex, why don't you take it outside, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.88,0:04:45.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And do what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.58,0:04:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在太阳下决斗  不错吧  -海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Fight in the sun. It'll be a nice change. - Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.36,0:04:49.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我逗你们玩呢  -是谁要来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm kidding. - Who's the boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.55,0:04:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His name is Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.86,0:04:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是别让他来算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I might as well tell him not to come...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.77,0:04:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你们又得让我丢脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you guys are just going to embarrass me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.88,0:04:57.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, hang on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.64,0:05:00.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你15岁了  还是第一次有男生来家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're 15, and it's the first time you've had a boy over.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.45,0:05:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是有点小吃惊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm bound to be a little surprised,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.34,0:05:04.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不会让你丢脸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I'm not gonna embarrass you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.49,0:05:06.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去给摄像机充好电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I better charge the camcorder.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.91,0:05:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逗你玩呢  别这样  也不看看我是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding. Come on. Who are you talking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.35,0:05:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是酷老爹  这是我的风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm the cool dad. That's- That's my thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.83,0:05:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我酷毙了  我会上网\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm hip. I- I surf the Web.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.62,0:05:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会发短信  LOL意思是癫狂笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I text. "LOL"- Laugh out loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.93,0:05:19.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OMG意思是饿滴神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"OMG"- Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.45,0:05:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,WTF意思是苦逼脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"WTF"- Why the face?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.80,0:05:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[WTF=What the FUCK意思是搞毛啊]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.65,0:05:25.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《歌舞青春》里所有的舞我都会跳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, you know, I know all the dances to High School Musical, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.81,0:05:28.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我们现在欢聚一堂*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*We're all in this together *
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:30.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*没错*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Yes, we are*
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.35,0:05:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我们都是大明星  嘻唰唰嘻唰唰*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*We're all stars Something, something you know it*
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.13,0:05:36.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈妈  爸爸  -什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mom! Dad! - What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.76,0:05:40.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克用枪射我  -我不是故意的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke just shot me! - I didn't mean to.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.16,0:05:42.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -没事才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you okay? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.27,0:05:43.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小贱人用枪射我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The little bitch shot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.98,0:05:48.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别说脏话  -只是塑料枪  这是意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Language!  They're only plastic BBs. It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.77,0:05:50.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就告诉你  给他枪就会出事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did I tell you would happen if you got him a gun?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.96,0:05:54.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看着办吧  -老弟  是你不对哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Deal with this. - Buddy, uncool.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.90,0:05:58.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就完了吗  不行  不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it? That's- No, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.55,0:06:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好他用枪射了别人  你就得射他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The agreement was that if he shoots someone, you shoot him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.04,0:06:04.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们当时是认真的吗  -当然是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We were serious about that? - Yes, we were.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.57,0:06:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你现在要按说好的执行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And now you have to follow through.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.13,0:06:09.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我错了  -你就装吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm so sorry. - Liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.09,0:06:13.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-去吧  -他还要去参加生日会呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go. - He's got a birthday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.02,0:06:14.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日会和家法哪个更重要  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's more important here, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.72,0:06:16.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以之后再射他  他两点就能到家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can shoot him afterwards. He'll be home at 2:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.54,0:06:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两点不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't shoot him at 2:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.62,0:06:18.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我两点还得带人去看房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm showing a house at 2:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.51,0:06:21.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三点吧  -不行  三点他有足球赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What about 3:00? - No, he's got a soccer game at 3:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.44,0:06:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们五点就得去赴宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then- Oh, we gotta leave for that dinner thing at 5:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.95,0:06:26.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4点15吧  你可以在那时候射他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}4:15. You could shoot him at 4:15.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.76,0:06:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  那个时候我有空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I guess that works for me. Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.12,0:06:31.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-射卢克  -抱歉老弟  铁板钉钉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "Shoot Luke." - Sorry, dude. It's on the calendar.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.13,0:06:34.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.74,0:06:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想踢足球了  那是小孩儿玩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm quitting soccer. It is a game for children.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.29,0:06:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不能放弃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you're not quitting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.96,0:06:41.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方之所以会进球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You would have stopped that goal
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.13,0:06:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全是因为你光顾着看小姑娘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if you weren't staring at that little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.02,0:06:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是小姑娘  她是成熟的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She is not a girl. She's a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.68,0:06:51.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  你犯得着非要和\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, Gloria, that little blowup with that other mom
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.11,0:06:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妈妈吵架吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you have to do things like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.28,0:06:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人敢对我的家人说三道四\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If somebody says something about my family,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.95,0:06:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我一定  -我只是说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm going to - I'm just saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.24,0:06:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你火气应该小一点  就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You could take it down here a little bit. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.42,0:06:59.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你总是这么忍气吞声的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. 'Cause that's where you live, down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.33,0:07:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可我咽不下这口气  -可是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But I live up here! - Yeah, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.54,0:07:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说  你别那么容易激动嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you don't have to be so emotional all the time.That's all I'm saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.91,0:07:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你也这么觉得吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, you're with me on this, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.29,0:07:07.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要告诉布兰达·费德曼我爱她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanna tell Brenda Feldman I love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -曼尼  她都16岁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, for God sakes. - Manny, she's 16.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.60,0:07:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就找了年长的对象吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. It's okay for you to take an older lover?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.42,0:07:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  说话注意点  -我要去她上班的商场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, watch it. - I wanna go to the mall where she works.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.77,0:07:17.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我先得换上我的白衬衫  丝绸的那件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But first I need to get my white shirt, the silk one.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.04,0:07:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  如果你真想这么做的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. If that's what you really want to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.17,0:07:21.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  不是我要当恶毒的后爹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously. Not to be the evil stepdad,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.78,0:07:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你要真穿着那臃肿的白衬衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but if you put on a puffy white shirt...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.75,0:07:25.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去向16岁的姑娘告白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and declare your love for a 16-year-old,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.87,0:07:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会被扒得只剩条白内裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're gonna be swinging from the flagpole
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.56,0:07:29.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被吊在旗杆上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in your puffy white underpants.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.33,0:07:31.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-停车  -你去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Stop the car. - Oh, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.92,0:07:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没  你伤他的心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? You hurt his feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.49,0:07:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这能让他变得坚强点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah- Well, if it toughens him up a little bit then-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.19,0:07:42.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妈呀  他居然去采野花了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, geez. He's picking flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.18,0:07:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼是个多情种  和他爹一个样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's very passionate, just like his father.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.07,0:07:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的前夫  风度翩翩  但太疯狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My first husband- he's very handsome, but too crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.26,0:07:52.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是在吵架就是在做爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It seemed like all we did was fight and make love,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.81,0:07:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵架  做爱  吵架  做爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}fight and make love, fight and make love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.66,0:07:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  有一次  我们从窗口摔下去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time, I'm not kidding you, we fell out the window together.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.99,0:08:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们当时在吵架还是做爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which- Which one were you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.97,0:08:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次听说这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm hearing this for the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.79,0:08:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不担心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This doesn't worry you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.50,0:08:10.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在飞机上就没怎么睡  现在还很清醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She barely slept on the plane and she's still wide awake.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.73,0:08:13.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别想多了  -不想才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, stop worrying. - I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.59,0:08:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孤儿院里都是女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That- That orphanage was all women.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.03,0:08:18.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许离开女性柔软的怀抱  她就睡不着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe she just- she can't fall asleep unless she feels a woman's shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.45,0:08:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有可能  -那你抱着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I guess that's possible. - So here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.09,0:08:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这话是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.70,0:08:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.76,0:08:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在等待领养孩子的期间  我是长胖了一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've gained a few extra pounds while we were expecting the baby,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.37,0:08:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过程相当艰辛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which has been very difficult.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.12,0:08:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但显然你的身体会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But apparently your body
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.42,0:08:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,产生一些母性的本能反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}does a nesting, very maternal, primal thing...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.55,0:08:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来储存养分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where it retains nutrients-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.04,0:08:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是分子生理学那类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}some sort of molecular physiology thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.89,0:08:40.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是科学事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's science.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.76,0:08:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类  根本无力抵抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't- You can't fight it, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.42,0:08:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没别的意思  -你就是话里有话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm not saying anything. - You're saying everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.54,0:08:53.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-数到3  -1  2\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Count to three. - One, two-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.46,0:08:54.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-3  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Three. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.84,0:08:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  真美  -我的天  你喜欢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, Cam. This is beautiful. - Oh, my God. Do you love it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.07,0:08:59.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.21,0:09:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么玩意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.69,0:09:03.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让安珠尔趁我们不在时画的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had Andre do it while we were gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.61,0:09:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我俩吗  还长着翅膀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that us, with wings?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.20,0:09:08.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在她的上方  永远守护着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're floating above her, always there to protect her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.77,0:09:10.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真让人心安  对吧  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Well, that's reassuring, right, Lily?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.66,0:09:12.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把你从熟悉的环境中抢出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, we tore you away from everything you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.46,0:09:13.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可别担心  新环境一切"正常"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but don't worry, things are normal here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.87,0:09:15.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的大爸二爸可是飞天小精灵哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your fathers are floating fairies.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.42,0:09:16.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  你能叫安珠尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, can you call Andre,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.83,0:09:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新画点不那么基情的东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}have him paint something a little less gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.23,0:09:20.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外  我们也该少和安珠尔往来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By the way, we need to stop having friends
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.61,0:09:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他名字也太娘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with names like Andre.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.87,0:09:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-红发老爹怒火旺盛  -我才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Redheaded dad is angry daddy. - No, I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.99,0:09:26.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来的路上  连胡娇都看出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Even Pepper pointed it out on the way home from the airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.04,0:09:29.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  又一个娘气的名字  胡娇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's another one- Pepper.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.96,0:09:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怎么不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, what's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.06,0:09:33.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, look. I-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.34,0:09:38.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没有告诉家里领养孩子的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I never told my family we were adopting a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.39,0:09:40.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-而且  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And... - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.78,0:09:45.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道  -我不怪你  我了解你家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You do? - Yeah, and I don't blame you. I know your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.30,0:09:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一告诉他们  他们就开始说三道四\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'd tell 'em. They'd say something judgmental.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.80,0:09:49.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是这样  -然后你就会生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Exactly. - You'd get mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.39,0:09:51.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  当爹本该是一件喜事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. And then something that's supposed to be nothing but joyful
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.57,0:09:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转眼就变成一团混战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}suddenly turns into this huge fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.36,0:09:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁愿意让事情变得一团糟呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And who wants a big, emotional scene like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.66,0:09:56.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.46,0:09:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能理解我  真是让我松了一口气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so- I'm so relieved you understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.20,0:10:01.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我邀请了他们今晚来吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I invited them over for dinner tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.89,0:10:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我也是不得已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - I had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.45,0:10:06.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去没完没了  你就只会逃避\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This would have gone on forever. You're an avoider.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.97,0:10:09.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  小卡  我现在就打电话取消这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No. No. Cam, I'm calling them right now and canceling.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:10.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准打\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.95,0:10:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你得把领养的事告诉全家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're telling your family you adopted a baby, tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.35,0:10:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是喜欢逃避  连朗吉娜都这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you do have avoidance issues. Even Longinus said so.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.76,0:10:18.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己听听  这些名字有多娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are- Are you really not hearing these names?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.19,0:10:24.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们别管了  我来开门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't answer it! I'll get it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.20,0:10:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  你一定是迪兰吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. Hey, you must be Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.40,0:10:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  迪兰  -我是海莉的妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. Dylan. Yeah. - I'm Haley's mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.03,0:10:40.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们走吧  -那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on. Let's go. - Okay. Um-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.47,0:10:42.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hang on one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.31,0:10:46.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  你还在念高中吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan, you're still in high school?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.47,0:10:49.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是  我高三了   -高三  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, I'm a senior. -A senior. Okay. Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.31,0:10:53.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  亲爱的  这是迪兰  他读高三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Phil. Sweetie. Honey. He is Dylan, and he is a senior.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.12,0:10:55.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得给他个下马威\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to scare him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.84,0:10:58.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我瞧瞧这个花心大少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me meet this "Playa."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.71,0:11:00.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下菲尔·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil Dunphy, yo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.12,0:11:08.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  你只需死盯着他们看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like that. You just- You just stare down at 'em,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.24,0:11:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用眼神中的杀气震住他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}let the eyes do the work.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.67,0:11:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘴上说着  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mouth might be saying, "Hey, we cool,"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.33,0:11:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你的眼神说  才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your eyes are like, "No, we not."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.68,0:11:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你  才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Nice to meet you." "No, it's not."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.49,0:11:19.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺不错嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"It's all good."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.84,0:11:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"No, it's not."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.19,0:11:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看你俩已经  -等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, I see you two guys- - Wait, wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.85,0:11:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You two-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.87,0:11:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩要坦诚相待  懂吗  小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You two keep it real, know what I mean, son?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.85,0:11:35.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.74,0:11:38.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-求求你  别说了  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Please, stop. - That's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.05,0:11:41.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈呀我的背  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ow. Oh, God! That's my back. - Oh, honey. Sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.77,0:11:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被婴儿油滑倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! Oh! I slipped in the baby oil.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.10,0:11:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪儿冒出来的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Oh, where you from originally?"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.31,0:11:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单挑的话  我轻而易举就能放倒你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I could defeat you if it came to a physical confrontation."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.67,0:11:53.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该怎么办  要打电话叫医生吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know about this. Should I call a doctor?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.70,0:11:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用不用  好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no, no. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.30,0:11:58.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小样儿挺强壮的啊  -谢谢夸奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're very strong, homes. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.68,0:12:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  轻轻放下我  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Nice- Nice soft landing. - There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.74,0:12:04.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行了我们走吧  -我还侧躺着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, let's go. Come on. - I am on my side though.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.04,0:12:06.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只需把我放平  就没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So just flip me right back, and we're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.89,0:12:07.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll be good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.80,0:12:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需要把我翻过来就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just need to get flipped right on my back,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.46,0:12:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we should be fine. So-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.36,0:12:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布兰达·费尔曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brenda Feldman.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.56,0:12:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你拿的什么  -我为布兰达·费尔曼写的诗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What is that? - A poem I have written for Brenda Feldman.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.17,0:12:24.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用想也知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.05,0:12:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将心事化为文字  将文字用于行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I put my thoughts into words and now my words into action.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.77,0:12:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你取消行动的话  我就给你50块钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, I'll give you 50 bucks not to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.32,0:12:32.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才11岁而已  要那么多钱干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm 11 years old. What am I gonna do with money?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.95,0:12:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这年纪要16岁的花姑娘又能干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you gonna do with a 16-year-old?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.94,0:12:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他就像个斗牛士  -你见过斗牛吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's like a bullfighter. - Mmm. You ever see a bullfight?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.21,0:12:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不下去了  -我知道你心情不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't watch this. - You're in such a bad mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.82,0:12:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道原因  因为那人以为你是我爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I know why. It's because that man thought you were my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.61,0:12:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是的  -就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.89,0:12:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是  -你这样否认时  就代表是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - When you say "No" like that, it's always "Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.20,0:12:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  我们都到商场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. We're in the mall.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.31,0:12:54.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你买点年轻的衣服吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's get you, like, some younger clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.71,0:12:57.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那边有家店  -我不需要年轻的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There's a store there. - I don't need any younger clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.64,0:12:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不在乎那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I don't care what some jackass
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.17,0:13:01.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着破牛仔裤的混蛋如何看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a pair of ripped jeans thinks about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.33,0:13:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你不用在乎他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good. You shouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.15,0:13:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要在乎我的想法就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should only care what I think.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.09,0:13:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  我不在意你的年纪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you, and I don't care how old you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.98,0:13:11.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以别郁闷了  对曼尼也别那么凶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So stop being a gloomy goose and stop being so hard on Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:13.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对曼尼严格只是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The only reason I'm hard on Manny...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.60,0:13:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让他出洋相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is just because I don't wanna see him make a fool of himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.60,0:13:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从这儿都能闻到他的发胶味了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I can smell that hair goo of his from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.26,0:13:21.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他那里会发生什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I don't know what's gonna happen to him over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.98,0:13:25.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你是他的家人  这就意味着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you're his family now, and that means only one thing-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.09,0:13:29.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只可背后送春风  不可当面唾其脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You be the wind in his back, not the spit in his face.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.75,0:13:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-啥玩意  -这是我妈常挂嘴边的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? -It's something my mom always says.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.32,0:13:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用西班牙语说很华丽的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gorgeous in Spanish.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.03,0:13:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, he's there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.50,0:13:45.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她名花有主了  -真遗憾  小宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She has a boyfriend. - Oh, I'm sorry, mi nino.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.97,0:13:47.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把心献给了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gave her my heart,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.46,0:13:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她却还了一幅把我画成老式警长的图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she gave me a picture of me as an old-time sheriff.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.15,0:13:56.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我真傻是吧  -才不是呢小宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That was pretty stupid of me, wasn't it? - No, mi amor.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.11,0:13:58.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是勇气可嘉  对吧  杰  勇气可嘉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was brave. Right, Jay? Brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.13,0:14:01.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次你就会进步了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}W-Well, you'll know better next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.50,0:14:02.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  我们买椒盐卷去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Let's get a pretzel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.84,0:14:07.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我挺喜欢这画的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mentira. A me se me gusta.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.16,0:14:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, excuse me, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.16,0:14:14.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在商场散步锻炼的人必须靠右边走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We ask that all mall-walkers stay to the right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.02,0:14:31.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  出去  妈妈你看她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, get out! Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.64,0:14:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  别去烦你姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, leave your sister alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.53,0:14:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是进去拿我的书而已  至于吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just getting my book. Gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.25,0:14:38.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  亲爱的  可你要尊重个人隐私\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, sweetie. But you need to respect their privacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.02,0:14:41.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们在楼上干嘛呢  -没干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What are they doing up there? - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.34,0:14:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺在她床上并肩看电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lying on her bed, watching a movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.82,0:14:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.20,0:14:49.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在为今晚的聚餐准备蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I'm making a cake for tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.70,0:14:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想帮我做糖霜吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna help me with the frosting?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.70,0:14:52.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.54,0:14:56.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是海莉怀孕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you know, if Haley got pregnant,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.73,0:14:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会假装她得了腮腺炎  请假在家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}would you ever pretend she has mono for a few months,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.93,0:15:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后告诉别人那孩子是你的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then, like, tell everyone the baby's yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.78,0:15:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -有个高中生请了4个月病假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - This senior at school was "Out sick" for four months,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.95,0:15:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉娜·瑞斯尼克发誓说看到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but Jenna Resnick swears she saw her breast-feeding
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.41,0:15:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在自助洗车站给孩子喂奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at a coin-op car wash.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.60,0:15:17.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  你穿了多少衣服啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buddy, what are you wearing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.07,0:15:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没穿多少  -把外套脱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing. - Uh-uh. No jacket.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.99,0:15:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能戴一顶帽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One hat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.67,0:15:23.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿了几条内裤啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How many pairs of underwear do you have on?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.93,0:15:25.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就1条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.31,0:15:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是6条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Six.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.67,0:15:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  看海莉怀孕变胖还蛮爽的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}First of all, it would be really cool to see Haley that fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.41,0:15:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更酷的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And how awesome would it be
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.73,0:15:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多了个假弟弟  实际上是我亲外甥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to have a fake little brother who's really my nephew.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.62,0:15:36.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉才不会怀孕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley is not getting pregnant.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.17,0:15:38.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是说假如  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just saying "If." - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.83,0:15:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你喜欢找你姐的茬儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I know you like to make trouble for your sister,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.25,0:15:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这次不管用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's not gonna work this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.70,0:15:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道为啥吗  因为你姐是个好女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know why? 'Cause your sister's a good girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.75,0:15:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白  因为她和我当年一模一...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I was just like her when I was-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.85,0:15:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道  我也不想这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you to know, I'm not enjoying this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.63,0:15:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你得吸取这个教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But this is an important lesson that you're learning.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.45,0:15:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  记好了  记住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, soak it. Keep it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.35,0:16:02.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你站太近了  这样会很疼的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're too close. It's gonna hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.37,0:16:04.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要你疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's supposed to hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.24,0:16:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干嘛贱贱地笑  -我笑了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And why are you smiling? - I'm- What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.21,0:16:22.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  我下不了手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, forget it. I can't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.15,0:16:25.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要让你害怕  你已经学到教训了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The point is you're scared. I think you've learned your lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.65,0:16:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  你干什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom! What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.29,0:16:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来放洗好的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hey! I was just, um, dropping off some laundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.30,0:16:35.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-打扰到你们了吗  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is this a bad time? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.00,0:16:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我走好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.23,0:16:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能把门带上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, can you shut the door, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.84,0:16:43.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是让门开着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, we're just gonna go ahead and leave that open.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.11,0:16:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.98,0:16:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这种场景我见多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I have, uh, seen this little show before-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.39,0:16:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和高大的学长共卧一塌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lying on the bed with a tall senior.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.06,0:16:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一秒还只是一起看《鹰冠庄园》的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One minute you're just friends, watching Falcon Crest,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.46,0:16:54.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一秒你们就钻进游戏桌下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the next you're lying underneath the air hockey table
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.29,0:16:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宽衣解带了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with your bra in your pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.58,0:16:56.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.25,0:16:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你打到我的骨头了  -纯属意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You hit my bone! - It was an accident!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.47,0:17:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我以为你是我哥们呢  -我是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I thought you were my friend! - I am your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.65,0:17:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  你必须和妈妈谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad! Dad, Dad. You have got to talk to Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.26,0:17:08.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她简直是疯了  而且丢尽了我的脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She is, like, completely freaking out and embarrassing me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.14,0:17:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你妈是不像你爸那么通情达理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, your mom isn't always as cool about things as-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.74,0:17:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意怎么回事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is with this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.80,0:17:17.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.44,0:17:21.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸对这事还是不太习惯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, my dad still isn't completely comfortable with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.89,0:17:24.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经过了5年了  他还是无法完全接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um- He-He still does this thing. It's been five years now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.93,0:17:27.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次他要进入我和小卡在的房间时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he still does this thing where he announces himself...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.21,0:17:29.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都会先喊一声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}before walking into any room we're in...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.32,0:17:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防撞见我和小卡亲嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just to make sure he doesn't have to ever see us kiss.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.04,0:17:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我妈也有这个习惯就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wish my mother had that system.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.19,0:17:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还记得吗  -以后再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Remember? - Not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.73,0:17:39.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不敢相信你这么对我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I still can't believe you did this to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.71,0:17:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能高兴点吗  这是个庆祝会啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you get in the spirit of things? It's a celebration.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.68,0:17:47.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.85,0:17:50.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去给莉莉打扮一下  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, I'm gonna go get Lily ready. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.74,0:17:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要你对他们实话实说  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And I want you to just come straight out with it. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.61,0:17:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听话  你能做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. You can do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.83,0:17:56.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来个运动员式的撞胸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Sports guy chest bump.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.19,0:17:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要  -来撞一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Sports guy chest bump.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.33,0:17:59.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  好了  -上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cam. Oh! All right. Go - Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.35,0:18:00.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好啊  -大家好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are you? - Hi, guys. Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.56,0:18:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很美味啊  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That looks good. Oh, thank you. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.68,0:18:16.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用谢  打开吧  爸爸后脚马上就到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't thank us. Open it. Dad is coming right behind.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.92,0:18:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗  我们要进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Knock, knock! We're here. Coming in!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.75,0:18:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心爸爸  我们没在里面搞基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry, Dad. Nothing gay going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.79,0:18:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮你脱下这缤纷外套和闪亮小帽吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}May I take your multicolored coat and bejeweled cap?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.29,0:18:28.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拿去吧  -杰你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. Yeah. - Hey, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.83,0:18:30.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  歌洛莉亚  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gloria, hi. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.78,0:18:33.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸你还好吗  -歌洛莉亚  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are you? Hi, Dad. - Hi, Gloria. How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.63,0:18:36.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-裙子真漂亮  -谢谢你  菲尔[摸摸]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, what a beautiful dress. - Ay, thank you, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.73,0:18:37.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.61,0:18:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hey, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.13,0:18:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}["Phil菲尔"和"feel触摸"音相似]
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.13,0:18:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是叫你名字  不是要你去摸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's how she says "Phil." Not "Feel." Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.85,0:18:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-旅行怎么样  -挺好的  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So how was your trip? - It was good. It was good actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.29,0:18:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, um, about that, I- I
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.00,0:18:48.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些事要告诉你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}have something that I need to tell you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.58,0:18:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去越南不光是为了旅游\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um- Uh, we didn't just go to Vietnam for pleasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.07,0:18:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有重要消息宣布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We, uh, kind of have some big news.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.72,0:18:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  要是小卡隆了胸  我立马走人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. If Cam comes out here with boobs, I'm leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.53,0:18:59.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  -我希望你的家长没让你觉得丢人  妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad. - I hope he didn't embarrass you, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.99,0:19:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管她  海莉今天首次带男生回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't mind her. Haley had her first boy over today...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.46,0:19:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔就给了他一枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Phil shot him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.49,0:19:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  一年前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, um, so, about- about a year ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.43,0:19:11.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡和我开始渴望有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam and I started feeling this longing, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.52,0:19:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for something more, like, uh, maybe a baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.48,0:19:17.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这主意很糟糕  -你说糟糕是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ooh, that's a bad idea. - What do you mean, "Bad idea"?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.12,0:19:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子需要有妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, kids need a mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.81,0:19:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们俩无聊了  可以养条狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean if you two guys are bored, get a dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.90,0:19:22.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是闲得无聊  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, we're not bored, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.45,0:19:25.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我支持米奇尔  尽管你不是我亲生的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I support you, Mitchell, even though you're not my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.26,0:19:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得爸爸的意思是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I-I-I think what Dad is trying to say...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.62,0:19:29.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  你有点紧张兮兮的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is that, Mitchell, you're a little uptight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.99,0:19:32.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子就意味着麻烦  你没法处理这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids bring chaos, and- and you don't handle it well.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.21,0:19:34.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸可不是这个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not what Dad's saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.26,0:19:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what you're saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.02,0:19:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是从另一个角度羞辱了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it's insulting in a whole different way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.83,0:19:39.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  各位都冷静点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, people. Let's all "Chillax."
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.74,0:19:42.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡梅隆舅夫呢  -多谢多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, where's Uncle Cameron? - Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.83,0:19:45.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算有人发现他不在了  而不是光羞辱我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Someone who's not insulting me notices he's not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.86,0:19:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你的重要消息就是这个啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, so that's the big announcement, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.76,0:19:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩分手了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You two broke up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领养个孩子也挽救不了破裂的婚姻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well- Well, a baby wasn't gonna help that anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.31,0:19:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  你们分了也好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And let me tell you. You're better off,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.82,0:19:55.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就喜欢小题大做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because he was a bit of a drama queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.56,0:19:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  打住  打住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. Stop. Stop. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.10,0:19:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到我家来  还羞辱我和我的男朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You come into my house and you insult me and my boyfriend,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.90,0:20:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他才没有小题大做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who, by the way, is not that dramatic-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.06,0:20:20.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们领养了一个宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We adopted a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.97,0:20:22.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她名叫莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Her name is Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.04,0:20:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-激动吧  -停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Exciting! - Just turn it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.66,0:20:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我停不下来  这就是我的个性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't turn it off. It's who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.05,0:20:30.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是说音乐  -关音乐啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The music. - Oh, yes, the music.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.11,0:20:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来和莉莉打招呼吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come say hi to Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.14,0:20:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个小公主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, miren a la princesita.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.76,0:20:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个小公主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The little princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.20,0:20:37.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她好可爱  -多谢夸奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She's so cute! - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.46,0:20:39.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看  让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me see her. Let me see her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.08,0:20:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi there, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.85,0:20:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  对她来说不是很难发音吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Lily." Isn't that gonna be hard for her to say?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.62,0:20:47.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔打住  -我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil. - Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.43,0:20:52.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我说了领养这个主意很糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I-I-I know that I said I thought this was a bad idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.36,0:20:55.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我又懂什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, uh, what do I know?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.27,0:20:58.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是个模范父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, it's not like I wrote the book on fatherhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.89,0:21:01.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子都想做好爸爸  可我还是搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Been trying all my life to get it right. I'm still screwing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.59,0:21:05.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对吧曼尼  -我在车上为此写了首歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Right, Manny? - I wrote a song about it in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.76,0:21:07.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意料之中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.89,0:21:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  我为你们感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, I'm happy for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.59,0:21:12.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, uh, you should know that, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.75,0:21:15.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是来唾你们脸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not here to spit in your face,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.76,0:21:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来给你们  吹吹后背春风的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm here to... blow at your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.34,0:21:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不懂你的意思  -我也不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't understand what that means. - I don't-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.67,0:21:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话用西班牙语说比较好听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's- it's supposed to sound better in Spanish.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.09,0:21:28.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[良言一句三冬暖  恶语伤人六月寒]
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.88,0:21:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好听  真美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's beautiful. That's really nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.86,0:21:32.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And thank you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.89,0:21:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyhow, Mitch, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.52,0:21:38.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Dad, it's- it's- -
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.55,0:21:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我来抱她  -她哭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got her. I got her. - Oh, she's crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.77,0:21:42.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要爷爷抱  她要爸爸抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She wants her grandpa! She wants her daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.42,0:21:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想见见爷爷吗  -开什么玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you wanna meet Grandpa? - What? Are you kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:47.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是自家人了  让我瞧瞧你这跟屁虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's one of us now. Let me see the little pot sticker.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.57,0:21:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个小可爱  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you're a cutie, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.55,0:21:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah. Look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.42,0:21:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来自不同的世界  但我们彼此相容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're from different worlds, yet we somehow fit together.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.34,0:22:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱将我们紧紧相连  共度风风雨雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Love is what binds us, through fair or stormy weather.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.80,0:22:08.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到你的前面  只有一事相许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I stand before you now with only one agenda-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.42,0:22:11.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心只属于你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"To let you know my heart is yours,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.22,0:22:13.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布兰达·费尔曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Feldman comma Brenda."
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.90,0:22:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧我靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.96,0:22:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止  卢克在篮球上还没赢过我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, so far, hasn't beaten me in basketball.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.39,0:22:24.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2比0  2比0  来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's 2-0. 2-0. Okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-手下败将  滚吧  -爸爸  住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Get that weak stuff out of my kitchen! - Dad, stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.09,0:22:31.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮个忙好吗  站过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you do me a favor? Just grab-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.55,0:22:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,篮下的滋味如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How's the weather down there?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.95,0:22:37.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到他赢过我的那一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But when the day comes that he does win-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.21,0:22:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有那么一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if- you know- if/when-
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.20,0:22:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打败了我  我会说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he beats me, I'm just gonna be like,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.50,0:22:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Well done. Well done."
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.37,0:22:45.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样支持他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just, like, let him- Just support him...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.83,0:22:47.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in- in- in that kind of stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.58,0:22:49.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能会说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I'd probably want to go, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.52,0:22:51.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三局两胜才算赢  再来一局什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}two out of three and just see what happens there, but-

