[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.09,0:00:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.09,0:00:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.09,0:00:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第三集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.94,0:00:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(198,209)}杰&歌洛莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.74,0:00:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为伟大父亲的秘诀是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the key to being a great dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.12,0:00:09.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点难回答啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, that's a tough one.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.88,0:00:12.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让孩子们自由成长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Giving them the freedom to be whatever they want to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.97,0:00:25.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(199,224)}米奇尔&卡梅隆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.98,0:00:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  没错  -不管是画家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Right. Exactly. - Whether that's a painter,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.85,0:00:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诗人  飞行员  总统[董事长]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a poet, a pilot, a president-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.48,0:00:18.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于我们来说  那就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And for us, we're gonna
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.79,0:00:21.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企业领头人  或是一国之君\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of a company or of a country.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:25.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耐心是关键\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.37,0:00:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(260,214)}菲尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.03,0:00:29.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单  做他们的好朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, be their buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.66,0:00:32.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的答案就是这个吗  -还有认真学习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's your answer? - And stay in school.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.70,0:00:37.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn方正硬笔行书_GBK\i1\pos(171,214)}克莱尔  &
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.15,0:00:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不对  -还有别吸毒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - And don't do drugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.60,0:00:34.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.17,0:00:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快告诉我正确答案嘛  -我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just give me the answer. - 0h, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:41.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.21,0:01:01.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  克莱尔  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, Claire. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.62,0:01:03.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. - Oh, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.42,0:01:06.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  这位是我老公  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. Um, this is my husband, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.74,0:01:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -那是我儿子  卢克  就那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi. - And, uh, that's my son, Luke, right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.75,0:01:11.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这位是  -德希蕾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is - Desiree.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.83,0:01:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-德希蕾  对  抱歉  -你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Desiree, right. Sorry. - Oh, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.11,0:01:16.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-德希蕾刚搬过来  -赞啊  哪户\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Desiree just moved in down the block. - Fun. Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.24,0:01:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-314  -是嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 314. - Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.41,0:01:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那栋双卧室别墅  室内外兼配家庭活动室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The two-bedroom cottage with the indoor-outdoor family room.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.90,0:01:22.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害  你怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Very good. How did you-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.14,0:01:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定很喜欢那个蒸气浴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bet you're lovin' that steam shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.42,0:01:24.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  别吓到人家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, that's creepy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.63,0:01:27.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  抱歉  我是  我是个房产大亨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, sorry. I'm a- I'm a real estate mogul.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.80,0:01:30.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么!  不  我是个房产中介\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"What?" No, I'm a- I am a real estate agent.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.51,0:01:33.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们展览过那个房子  装饰很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We caravanned that house. Great, uh, deck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.64,0:01:36.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  我离婚手续办好就搬走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks. I'm just there till my divorce is final.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.58,0:01:38.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  谁傻到想要跟你离婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, who is coconuts enough to divorce you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.86,0:01:41.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该走了  再见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We gotta go, but we'll see you around.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.71,0:01:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时间请你过来玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll have to have you over sometime.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.63,0:01:45.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很愿意  -好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'd love it. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.21,0:01:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拜拜  -拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bye. - Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.83,0:01:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她真不错  -滚  我们不可能请她做客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She's awesome. - No, we are never having her over.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.51,0:01:52.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说她已经勾引过两个孩子的爸爸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Heard she already slept with two dads from the school.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.87,0:01:53.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.99,0:01:56.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,品行不端啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's horrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.42,0:01:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  小心  -小心点呀  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad, watch out! - Whoa! Watch it, buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.59,0:02:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老太太  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Grandma. - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:03.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那车看起来还是像个女孩车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That still looks like a girl's bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.85,0:02:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再绑点黑胶带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll add more black tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.49,0:02:08.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子一直在骑他姐姐的旧车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My son has been riding his sister's old bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.60,0:02:11.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在还没能力照料好一辆新车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Until he's responsible enough to take care of his own bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.68,0:02:13.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把一瓶苏打水倒在我的电脑上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, he spilled a soda on my computer,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.68,0:02:15.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还把家里的数码相机弄坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he ruined our digital camera
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.36,0:02:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为他要给自己拍水下相片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}taking pictures of himself underwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.17,0:02:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是辆女车  我也想给他些教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a girl's bike. I'm all for teaching him a lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:24.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我担心大嘴巴的小混混们因此嘲笑他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I worry about the ridicule he might get from some loudmouth bully.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.17,0:02:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿嘿  车很漂亮啊  小姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey, hey. Nice bike, Sally.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.10,0:02:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.99,0:02:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  他骑女式车  像洋娃娃一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. He looks like Little Bo Peep on that thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.19,0:02:33.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再这样了  他下午就会有辆新车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, not for long. He's getting a new bike this afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.92,0:02:35.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I am? - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.19,0:02:36.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He is?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.07,0:02:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候做男人就应该一往无前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes a man's gotta put his foot down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.41,0:02:41.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢踏出自己的脚步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and do what a man's gotta do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.12,0:02:42.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那个死老太婆不满意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if the old lady don't like it-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.29,0:02:45.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.00,0:02:49.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她自己气死算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's too damn bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.98,0:02:52.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  激不激动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Who's excited, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.60,0:02:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  快点  要迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, come on. Hurry up. We're gonna be late.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.61,0:02:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是亲子课而已  又不是要飞到卡波去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a toddler play class, not a flight to Cabo.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.51,0:02:59.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为唯一的同性恋夫夫  我们已经赚够口水了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna be judged enough as the only gay parents there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.62,0:03:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再给人迟到的坏印象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't wanna be the late ones too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.62,0:03:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  又是旋花呢又是粉色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow! Paisley and pink.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.82,0:03:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,网眼套头衫为什么不穿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was there something wrong with the fishnet tank top?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.96,0:03:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿啊  穿在里面了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Obviously not. I'm wearing it underneath.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.23,0:03:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的  放松  给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kidding. Just chill, please. Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.86,0:03:12.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我只是想留下良好的第一印象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I just wanna make a good first impression.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.72,0:03:14.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想既融入大家又不吓到他们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna fit in and not terrify the villagers?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.62,0:03:15.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.36,0:03:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天莉莉才是主角  好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Today is about Lily, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.93,0:03:19.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个班上可能就有她以后最要好的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Her future best friend might be in that class,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.87,0:03:22.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想一开始就惹谁不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I don't wanna rub anyone the wrong way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.15,0:03:25.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能换件衬衫吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you please just change your shirt?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.45,0:03:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你猜怎么着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.49,0:03:27.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就去换上一条卡其布裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll just go put on a pair of khakis,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.88,0:03:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高尔夫衬衫  让每个人都以为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe a polo shirt, and everybody will think
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.45,0:03:31.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是一对直男高尔夫球友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we're a couple straight golfin' buddies...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.04,0:03:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧决定一起养个娃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who just decided to have a kid together.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.66,0:03:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给纳巴那边打电话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, I called that place in Napa and
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.28,0:03:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把房间升级成带温泉浴缸的套房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}got us upgraded to a villa with a hot tub.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.85,0:03:42.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以准备点泡温泉的衣服吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So pack whatever you wear in a hot tub.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.28,0:03:45.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我通常泡温泉都不穿衣服的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I usually wear nothing when I'm in a hot tub.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.60,0:03:49.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我同事的老婆就得做个屁股整形了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And my college roommate's wife just had to get a new hip.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.48,0:03:50.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.10,0:03:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼的爸爸带他去迪斯尼玩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's father is taking him for a couple of days to Disneyland,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.45,0:03:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们就脱身去葡萄酒园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so we're gonna go to the wine country.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.78,0:03:59.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去喝点小酒  吃些美食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna drink some wine, eat some good food.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.51,0:04:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本我们可以经常组织此类小资活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, we would do something like this
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.05,0:04:03.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  因为曼尼  就少了很多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a lot more often if it wasn't for, you know, Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.12,0:04:07.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他很好  他让我们过着朴实的生活  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's good. He keep us grounded. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.55,0:04:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Grounded：朴实的稳定的/搁浅停飞 ]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.79,0:04:10.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像机场起雾  飞机停飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like fog at an airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.08,0:04:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豪华轿车4点到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Limo gets here at 4:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.48,0:04:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上嘛  我想去俱乐部打会球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This morning, I thought I'd go to the club, hit a few balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.42,0:04:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  曼尼房间的风扇怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! What about the fan in Manny's room?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.21,0:04:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  叫个人修吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, yeah. Call a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.52,0:04:21.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  你该跟他一起修\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! You're supposed to do it with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.40,0:04:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得学着教他做些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's important that we teach him how to do things for himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.39,0:04:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的家乡  男人以干体力活为荣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In my culture, men take great pride in doing physical labor.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.28,0:04:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以我才雇你们那儿的人给我干活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. That's why I hire people from your culture.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.41,0:04:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真搞笑呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're too funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.01,0:04:36.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟我下个老公狂花你的钱的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna share that one with my next husband
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.14,0:04:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就给他讲这个笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when we're spending all your money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.96,0:04:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  这是全世界最酷的车  -必须的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad, this is the coolest bike ever. - Awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.99,0:04:45.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, listen, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.46,0:04:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里有些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Certain members of this family
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.73,0:04:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认为你照料不好这辆车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}don't think you can take care of this bad boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.01,0:04:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是说妈妈吗  -你说的  我可没说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You mean Mom? - Your words, not mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.24,0:04:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈和我是一个整体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, uh, your mom and I are a team,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.82,0:04:58.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而她  我们  觉得这是个好机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she- we feel like this is a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.37,0:05:00.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你学会负起责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for you to show some responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.27,0:05:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我们失望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't make us look like jerks here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.45,0:05:05.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不会的  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I won't. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.83,0:05:07.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-最后一点要求  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- One more rule. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.66,0:05:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我  玩得超级无敌开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Have, like, three butt-loads of fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.34,0:05:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:24.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们开始吧  -先说好3点前要弄完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So let's do this. - 0kay, but I need to be done by 3:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.04,0:05:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸3点来接我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's when my dad's picking me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.15,0:05:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果3点还搞不定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, if we're not done by 3:00,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.33,0:05:29.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就直接吊死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna tie a noose on this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.24,0:05:31.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哥伦比亚有句谚语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In Colombia there's a saying:
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.03,0:05:34.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"如果两头犟驴合不来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"If you have two stubborn burros that don't like each other,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.53,0:05:36.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把它们绑在一辆车上"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you tie them to the same cart."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.02,0:05:39.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊扇就是那辆车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The ceiling fan is the cart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸要带我去玩太空过山车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad's taking me on Space Mountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.26,0:05:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西超快  不过我爸爸什么都不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's supposed to be really fast, but he's not scared of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.37,0:05:47.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他玩的时候甚至都不系安全带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He doesn't even wear a seat belt when he drives.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.32,0:05:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇噢  也太厉害了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. How 'bout that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.17,0:05:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他还杀过熊  -真的假的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Killed a bear once. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.51,0:05:52.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊也坐在过山车上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was the bear sittin' in the passenger seat?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.89,0:05:56.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我念下说明书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Read me the instructions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.77,0:05:59.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"安全须知  警告:为避免遭受电击"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Safety tips. Warning: To reduce the risk of electrical shock"-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.90,0:06:01.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳过那段废话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can skip that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.99,0:06:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"若不听从警告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, "Failure to heed these warnings
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.99,0:06:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可导致重伤  甚至死亡"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}can lead to serious injury or death."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.87,0:06:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是瞎担心  你自己知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you worry too much. You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.54,0:06:10.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有人被电到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nobody's gonna get shocked.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.24,0:06:12.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次我爸爸被雷劈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time my dad was struck by lightning.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.58,0:06:15.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他现在喝多少酒都不醉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why he can drink as much as he wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.25,0:06:17.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼觉得他爸爸是个超人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny thinks his dad is like Superman.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.75,0:06:20.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可真相呢  他根本不值一提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The truth? He's a total flake.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.42,0:06:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  他唯一像超人的方面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In fact, the only way he's like Superman...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.71,0:06:25.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他们都是非法移民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is that they both landed in this country illegally.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.49,0:06:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么这么紧张呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe I'm so nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.81,0:06:31.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会喜欢我们的  我们就表现真我就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're gonna love us. Let's just be ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.97,0:06:34.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者稍微低调一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0r a slightly toned-down version of ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.60,0:06:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想这又变成"小卡秀"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just don't want this to become an episode of "The Cam Show."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.04,0:06:39.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天呐  大家都喜欢"小卡秀"  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 0h, my gosh. People love "The Cam Show." - Yes, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.83,0:06:41.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你也看"小卡秀"  -我确实看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You watch "The Cam Show." - I do watch it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.19,0:06:42.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是提前预约才能看到  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's appointment viewing. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.98,0:06:45.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -你们好  是参加亲子课的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi! - Hi! Are you here for Toddler Time?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.35,0:06:47.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我是米奇尔  这是卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. I-I'm Mitchell. This is Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.38,0:06:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有我们的女儿莉莉  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And this here is Lily. - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.08,0:06:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好  欢迎呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, well! Welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.82,0:06:54.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这儿轮流吹气球呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're all over here taking turns blowing bubbles.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.47,0:06:58.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多好玩啊  对小孩子而言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, how nice for... the babies.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.00,0:06:59.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕我会招架不住啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is gonna be really difficult.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.31,0:07:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才跟我保证  过了不到10分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ten minutes after making a promise to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.62,0:07:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就把车不上锁扔在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he leaves his bike unlocked.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.07,0:07:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在满脑子都是克莱尔的河东狮吼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All I can hear is Claire's voice in my head-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.88,0:07:24.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他不知道负责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"He's not responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.36,0:07:26.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不该给他买车"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never should have given him a bike."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.45,0:07:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我模仿克莱尔超像的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I do a pretty good Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.58,0:07:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我决定给他个教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I decided to teach him a lesson...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.41,0:07:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他以为自己的车被偷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and let him think his bike was stolen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.54,0:07:37.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这手段有点恶劣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I know that sounds kind of rough,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:40.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有时候做爹的就要狠一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but sometimes it's a dad's job to be the tough guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.00,0:07:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me! Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.75,0:07:44.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左边  我的左边  你右边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}On your left! My left. Your right!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.23,0:07:52.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  今天有个新家庭加入我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everyone, we have a new family joining us today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.24,0:07:55.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  我是米奇尔  一名律师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. I'm, uh, Mitchell, and I am a lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.62,0:07:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是卡梅隆  暂时待业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I'm Cameron, and I'm currently not working,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.37,0:08:03.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我有很多时间烹饪  打篮球  还有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which gives me more time to grill and shoot baskets and-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.70,0:08:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这是莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this is Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.61,0:08:07.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们以问候舞作为开场舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, we're gonna start with the Hello Dance,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.82,0:08:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后玩积木  手指画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we're gonna move on to blocks, then finger painting,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.45,0:08:12.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后跳"家庭之舞"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we're gonna do our Family Dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.95,0:08:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  谁想先开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Who wants to start us off?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.04,0:08:17.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,P.J小朋友先来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dance us in, P. J.!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.63,0:08:25.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她真可爱  -谢谢夸奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She's adorable. - Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.26,0:08:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-7个月大吗  -8个月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Seven months? - Uh, eight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.26,0:08:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  会抓东西了吗  会走路了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h! Is she grabbing or scooting yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.39,0:08:31.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  都会呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.87,0:08:34.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  她不是手在乱抓  就是脚在乱走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, when she's not grabbin', she is- she is scootin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.67,0:08:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰勒  进来跳吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dance us in, Tyler!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.58,0:08:40.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗  好的  来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you ready? Okay. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.69,0:08:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  莉莉还不会抓不会走呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, Lily is not grabbing or scooting yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.74,0:08:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还不会  以后会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she's not doing it yet, but she will eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.61,0:08:51.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你看  那么多小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, but, see, a lot of these other kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.01,0:08:52.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都在抓东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they're- they're grabbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是  给  拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I just- Here. Come-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.83,0:08:57.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  你看积木\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily. Look at the block, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.00,0:08:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把积木拿起来  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Grab the block, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.03,0:09:00.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抓着H  -该你上场了莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Grab the "H." - Dance us in, Lily!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.61,0:09:01.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  我来搞定  -小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. I got this. - Cam, just-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.84,0:09:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  要压抑我的天赋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I know. Tamp down my natural gifts
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.83,0:09:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后像个直男一样笨舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and dance like a straight guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.03,0:09:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许拍屁屁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No slapping your own butt.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.14,0:09:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不拍屁屁我怎么舞得起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's how I make my horsey go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.33,0:09:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢大家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.29,0:09:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.90,0:09:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很卑鄙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel dirty.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.07,0:09:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -嘿  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 0h, hey. - Hey! Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.53,0:09:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.88,0:09:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人难堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, this is really embarrassing,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.04,0:09:38.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把自己锁在外面了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I locked myself out of my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.95,0:09:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  我总做这种傻事  别不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h! Pssh! I do that all the time. Don't be embarrassed.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.31,0:09:45.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想  你能不能帮帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was- I was hoping you could help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.67,0:09:47.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有扇窗子开着  可我够不着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a window open, but I can't reach it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.93,0:09:49.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.87,0:09:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  没问题  -太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. Yeah. Sure. - Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.30,0:09:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  你知道有句俗话说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0f course. You know what they say-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.31,0:10:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"每当上帝关上一扇门  他就打开一扇窗"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Every time God closes a door, he opens a window."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.19,0:10:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过对你的话  是他每次都把你锁在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0r I guess in this case, every time he locks you out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.82,0:10:05.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, what do we got here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.04,0:10:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的魅力征服了她吗  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, am I attracted to her? Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.82,0:10:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会趁机发展一下吗  不  不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would I ever act on it? No. No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.28,0:10:13.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老婆还健在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not while my wife is still alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.96,0:10:15.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不想喝点什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you sure I can't get you something to drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.83,0:10:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  不用了  我很好  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. No, I'm- I'm fine. Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.24,0:10:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我知道会有帅哥爬我家卧室的窗户\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I knew a man was gonna climb into my bedroom window,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.57,0:10:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定会"清洗"一下的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would have cleaned up a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.01,0:10:23.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑吗  房里幽香怡人呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me? It smelled great in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.58,0:10:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有乳液精油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like lotions and oils...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.55,0:10:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  保湿用的  预防干裂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for... dry skin and, you know, calloused hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.10,0:10:31.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  是香烛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, it's a candle.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.07,0:10:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-完了  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh-oh. - What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.58,0:10:37.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-自行车没了  -哦不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The bike's gone. - Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.06,0:10:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我帮你找找吧  -不用了谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I help you find it? - That's all right. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.47,0:10:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  谢谢你哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0kay. Thank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.92,0:10:45.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了教育他  我藏起了他的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, to teach him a lesson, I took his bike,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.81,0:10:47.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  太离谱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then- crazy thing-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.06,0:10:50.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放下了两分钟  就被人卷走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I put it down for one minute, and someone swiped it from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.19,0:10:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许也是你爸想教育教育你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe that was your dad teaching you a lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.88,0:10:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够狠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Zinger.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.83,0:11:01.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  这一辆能打个折吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, any chance I could, uh, get a break on this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.68,0:11:03.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可以加个铃铛  -成交\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can throw in a bell. - Deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.53,0:11:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-五块一个  -那不要了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- For five dollars. - No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.79,0:11:07.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这次要买保险吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you wanna go for the insurance this time,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.48,0:11:08.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是继续给小偷做好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or is it still for suckers?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.23,0:11:11.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够狠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.34,0:11:14.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够狠啊大哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well played, milord.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.14,0:11:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次买保险  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will take some insurance. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.62,0:11:19.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在搞什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's going on in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.28,0:11:22.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-第四步不是那样  -不管它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's not step four. - Don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.39,0:11:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-上面说你应该...  -怎么还管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It says right here that you should- - That's worrying about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.06,0:11:27.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要喝点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you guys might need a drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.36,0:11:29.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太想太想了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, you have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.36,0:11:32.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼宝贝  我得去买点旅途要带的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, miamor, I have to go get some stuff for our trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.61,0:11:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟爸爸好好玩  好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay! But have some fun with your father, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.04,0:11:36.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周一见  亲亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'll see you Monday. Mwah!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.92,0:11:41.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到我的两个宝贝一起合作  好开心哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It makes me so happy to see my two boys working together.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.11,0:11:43.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰电到自己两次了  -好了曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Jay shocked himself twice. - 0kay, Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.45,0:11:46.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我警告过他了  -是啊  他真会帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, I warned him. - Yep, he's been a big help.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.46,0:11:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你们都有自己的小笑话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at you two with your private jokes already.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.54,0:11:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像高个子版的萨拉查和埃尔奥索\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're a regular Salazar and El Oso.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.17,0:11:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是哥伦比亚超有名的笑星搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a very big comedy team in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.26,0:11:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃尔奥索总打萨拉查的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}El Oso is always hitting Salazar in the head
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.42,0:11:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用梯子啊等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the ladder and things.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.94,0:12:01.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候他们还穿裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And sometimes they wear dresses. Hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.39,0:12:05.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不仅逗人笑  也让人深思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They make you laugh, but they also make you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.94,0:12:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞砸了  让我很没面子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You blew it. You made me look bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.36,0:12:12.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你让你妈和我都没面子  我们是个整体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you made your mother and I look bad. We are a team.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.07,0:12:15.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克你在吗  -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, you in there? - Hey, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.07,0:12:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Hey, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天很有意思吧  得到一辆新车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was, uh- That was pretty fun today, huh? Getting a new bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.74,0:12:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太赞了  -我走以后出什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, it was awesome. - So, uh, what happened after I took off?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.41,0:12:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有事想跟我说吗  -没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Anything you want to share with me? - Not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.12,0:12:30.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  我去车库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, if I, uh, went out to the garage,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.92,0:12:33.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍个照什么的  也不会有意外咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}took a picture for a scrapbook, there'd be no surprises?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.05,0:12:38.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不是故意的  我犯了个错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so sorry! I didn't mean it. I just made a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.73,0:12:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  大错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, a big mistake!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.74,0:12:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我很没面子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're making me look really bad here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.97,0:12:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还告诉你妈说你已经懂得负责任了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told Mom you were ready for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.10,0:12:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就刮花了一点点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just a scratch, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.96,0:12:46.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是重点  卢克  什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not the point, Luke! What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.93,0:12:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我骑上路的时候刮花了  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I scratched it on my way into the driveway. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.65,0:12:53.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  没丢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, it's not stolen?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.96,0:12:55.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啊  怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.69,0:12:57.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's good,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.74,0:13:01.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  有很多坏人喜欢偷车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause... there are bad people out there who would steal a bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.88,0:13:02.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小偷什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those are thieves.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.93,0:13:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐那儿反思一下为什么会刮花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You sit there and think about the scratch part.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.78,0:13:06.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刮花也不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not good either.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.08,0:13:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得修好这楼梯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gotta fix that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.24,0:13:09.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在的时候别再刮花东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So don't scratch anything while I'm gone,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.76,0:13:11.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Scratch一词多意：刮花/挠痒]
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.29,0:13:11.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痒的话可以挠挠  那个不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}unless it itches. That's different.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好消息是  卢克的车还在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The good news is, Luke has his bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.39,0:13:16.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更好的消息是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More good news-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.09,0:13:20.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷了个野孩子的车  给他上了一课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I taught some random kid a valuable lesson by stealing his bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.68,0:13:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的消息是  克莱尔什么都不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Best news- Claire knows nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.55,0:13:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  新车就丢在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I figure I'll just dump the new bike
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.71,0:13:28.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷车的地方好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where I stole the first bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.06,0:13:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  丢车的孩子拿到车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That way, random kid gets his back,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.06,0:13:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新车也不会引发很多尴尬的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and this new bike doesn't raise a lot of embarrassing questions...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.77,0:13:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如我为什么要多买一辆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like why I had it
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.25,0:13:36.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或谁爬进了谁的卧室窗户\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or who boosted who through a bedroom window.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.39,0:13:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样  皆大欢喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, everybody's happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.27,0:13:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗娘养...你给我的螺丝刀不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, son of a- You gave me the wrong screwdriver.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.42,0:13:48.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是你使用方法不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe you're just using it wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.37,0:13:49.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸什么工具都搞得定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dad's great with tools.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.91,0:13:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不用一分钟就能拆掉车轮子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He can get the wheels off a car in less than a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.17,0:13:54.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去酒庄散散心  去酒庄散散心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just get me to wine country. Just get me to wine country.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.81,0:13:56.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.75,0:13:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想我胳膊断了  -放松  没断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I think my arm is broken. - Relax. It's not broken.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.42,0:14:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道  你什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you know? You don't know anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.55,0:14:03.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点安全意识都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have no concern for safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.55,0:14:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-砸得又不重  -直接说不就得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Because it didn't hit you that hard. - Why don't you just say it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.26,0:14:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不想我在身边  -你猜怎么  你说对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You don't want me around. - You know what? Right now, I don't!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.35,0:14:12.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想跟你在一起  我要我爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't wanna be with you either. I'm gonna go wait for my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.15,0:14:15.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你走了  我怎么能完成呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, but- but if you leave, how will I ever finish?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.23,0:14:19.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我真希望你没娶我妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I wish you never married my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.31,0:14:22.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我讨厌住在这里  -你以为我喜欢这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I hate living here. - You think I like this arrangement?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.36,0:14:24.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有两辆跑车闲置在车道上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a two-seater parked in the driveway!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.44,0:14:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.51,0:14:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要背着我做这做那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you trying to sneak around and hide things from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.64,0:14:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得太搞了  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I actually think it's pretty funny. - You do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.55,0:14:38.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I do. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.69,0:14:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你偷了一个倒霉孩子的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, you steal a bike from some poor kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.61,0:14:43.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你又把车丢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then the bike gets stolen from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.41,0:14:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太搞笑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.80,0:14:47.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的风格  是不是  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Classic me, right? - Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.89,0:14:49.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那车丢的时候你在哪儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, where were you when it got stolen?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.91,0:14:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时在加油呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I was getting some gas.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.84,0:14:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你加油的时候竟然不在车旁边吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-huh. You don't stand near the car when you get gas?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.69,0:14:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在啊  可是  我进去拿了瓶汽水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yep, but, uh, I went inside to get a soda
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.85,0:14:58.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我渴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because I was thirsty,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.73,0:15:00.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我有汽水  我就不会口渴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and if I had a soda, I wouldn't be thirsty anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.32,0:15:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我买了一罐  就在那边喝完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I bought one, then I drank it all right there,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.34,0:15:03.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在手中才没有空瓶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is why I don't have the can.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.82,0:15:05.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  请你  慢慢回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, honey, please, let's try to remember
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.79,0:15:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你妻子  不是你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'm your wife, not your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.86,0:15:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后不用有事瞒着我  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So in the future, you don't need to hide things from me. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.28,0:15:12.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 0kay. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.80,0:15:16.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  -噢  太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 0kay. - Oh! Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.15,0:15:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再继续抱抱  没够呢  -菲尔你做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You get back here, you! - What are you doing, Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.09,0:15:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是太爱你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just love ya so darn much!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.93,0:15:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  我也爱你  你弄疼我了  -进去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know. I love you too, but that hurts. - Let's get you inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.89,0:15:26.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -我知道  好疼啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi. - I know. That's hurting a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.09,0:15:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-性感熊抱  -嗨  你们好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is a hot one. - Hello! Hi there!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.77,0:15:29.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-又见面了  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi again. - Oh, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.40,0:15:30.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到你的车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I, uh, found your bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.53,0:15:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, good! You-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.22,0:15:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是在加油站的吗  -不  在我家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- At the gas station? - No, at my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.60,0:15:38.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我邻居看到车倒在我门口  帮我放到车库了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One of my neighbors saw it and put it in my garage
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.68,0:15:40.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会儿你正在我卧室里  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when you were in my bedroom, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.57,0:15:45.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的典型风格?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Classic me?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.40,0:15:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点宝贝  拿起积木\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, honey. Grab the block.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.74,0:15:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  就像他那样  加油啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, like he did. You gotta do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.37,0:15:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-像他那样拿起来  -最近看电影了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You gotta grab it like him. - So, seen any movies lately?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.59,0:15:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.50,0:15:58.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫和我租了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, my husband and I just rented,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.78,0:16:01.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《妈妈咪呀》  我很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, Mamma Mia! Which I liked,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.58,0:16:04.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是觉得选梅丽尔·斯特里普做女主角不合适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I don't know that Meryl Streep was the right choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.27,0:16:06.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.44,0:16:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有搞错啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.02,0:16:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让梅丽尔·斯特里普去演蝙蝠侠都可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Meryl Streep could play Batman and be the right choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.91,0:16:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是完美的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's perfection...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.31,0:16:16.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论她有没有跟克莱默离婚  穿没穿普拉达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}whether she's divorcing Kramer, whether she's wearing Prada.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.67,0:16:19.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更不用说《苏菲的选择》了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't even get me started on Sophie's Choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.74,0:16:21.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想我都动情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I get emotional thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.08,0:16:25.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她根本无法原谅自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She couldn't forgive herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.06,0:16:32.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她还好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess she was okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.94,0:16:34.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Ooh.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.80,0:16:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿起积木  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Grab the blocks, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.21,0:16:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么都没兴趣  -亨利在堆积木吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're not even interested in it. - Is Henry stacking?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.90,0:16:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好啊亨利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good job, Henry!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.54,0:16:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good job!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.61,0:16:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Q  R  S  T  U  V\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Q-R-S T-U-V
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.76,0:16:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,W  X  Y  还有Z\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}W-X-Y and Z
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.59,0:16:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在知道我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I know my-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.81,0:17:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇噢  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa, Lily! Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.07,0:17:03.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要这么高啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not so high. Wow!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.73,0:17:06.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-人生重要一刻啊  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That is a big moment for her. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.69,0:17:08.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要份录像吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you like a videotape?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.65,0:17:09.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  不用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, you know, I don't-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.94,0:17:11.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道她还能不能再做一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know if I can actually get her to do it again, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.93,0:17:14.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的课都有录像的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we tape all of our classes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.05,0:17:16.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母自己带相机不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We don't like parents bringing cameras in.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.62,0:17:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样他们就不能一起参与了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It keeps them out of the moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.05,0:17:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课后我给你一份录像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll get you a copy after class.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.12,0:17:21.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  好的  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's super. Yeah. Great. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.62,0:17:24.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  小卡  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam. Cam, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.94,0:17:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what's happened to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.16,0:17:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我刚刚盗取了一个婴儿的知识产权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I just stole a baby's intellectual property.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.25,0:17:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -今晚的新闻会曝光我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - You'll see it tonight on the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.29,0:17:33.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别说了快走吧  -快看谁来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on. Let's just go. - Oh, look who's here!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.71,0:17:36.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-安东和斯科特  -抱歉我们晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Anton and Scott! - Sorry we're late!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.94,0:17:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的错  旁边这位爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't look at me. The eye candy here can't leave the house...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.13,0:17:41.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在镜子前打扮个20分钟是不会出门的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without spending 20 minutes in front of the mirror.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.58,0:17:43.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.13,0:17:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.67,0:17:48.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那对基神  我本可以在这里大放光彩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at those queens. I would have killed with this crowd.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.91,0:17:50.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你剪断了我翱翔的"基翅"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you had to clip my wings-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.34,0:17:52.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你曾是那翅膀下助力的风\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which you used to be the wind beneath.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.15,0:17:52.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  对不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I'm sor-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.83,0:17:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个班让我发疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This class has turned me into a complete monster.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.51,0:17:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我只是  我会补偿你的  走吧好不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm- I'm just- I'll make it up to you. Let's just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.66,0:18:00.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  亲子舞时间到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, it's time for Parents Dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.37,0:18:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都为自己的孩子起舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody dance for your baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.24,0:18:08.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跳  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna do it, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.78,0:18:10.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想好想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.32,0:18:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想为我的宝贝起舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanna dance for my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.34,0:18:15.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  上吧  去吧  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. Go on. Get in there. - You sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.25,0:18:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开足马力跳起来吧  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Make that horsey move. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.69,0:18:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.75,0:18:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}0h, I think I hurt myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.50,0:18:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  哈维尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello. Hey, Javier.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.15,0:19:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼在外面等你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's waiting for you outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.84,0:19:06.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  为什么来不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.71,0:19:08.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hold that thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.35,0:19:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他儿子坐在路边  等着去迪斯尼乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His son's sitting on a curb, waiting to go to Disneyland,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.41,0:19:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我们的超人爸爸沉浸于赌博不能自拔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Superman can't drag himself away from a craps table,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.69,0:19:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却说我是混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm the jerk.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.12,0:19:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Say, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.50,0:19:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.31,0:19:30.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很抱歉  我有坏消息  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sorry, but I got some bad news. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.28,0:19:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸来不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your dad couldn't make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.69,0:19:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.71,0:19:37.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞机票卖光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The plane was full,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.01,0:19:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个老奶奶回不了家  他把票让给了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and this old lady needed to get home, so he gave up his seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.84,0:19:42.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你瞎编的  是不是  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're making that up, aren't you? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.28,0:19:44.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是不愿意来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just didn't want to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.58,0:19:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  他很难过  他很想见你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me? He was very upset. He was dying to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.32,0:19:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看他送什么来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In fact, look what he sent.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.70,0:19:55.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-豪华轿车吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- A limo? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.73,0:19:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我和你妈妈带你去迪斯尼乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He wanted me and your mom to take you to Disneyland.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.23,0:20:01.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我跟你说我爸爸超赞的  -是啊  他是个王子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I told you he was an awesome dad. - Yeah, he's a prince.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.31,0:20:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  成为好父亲的秘诀是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. The key to being a good dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.26,0:20:10.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候事情会如你所愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes things work out just the way you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.80,0:20:11.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛谁先到路口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Race you to the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.68,0:20:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那主意可不妙  对你来说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is not a good idea... for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.77,0:20:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候则事与愿违\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes they don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.67,0:20:19.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要坚持\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You gotta hang in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.70,0:20:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为当一切尘埃落地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because when all is said and done,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.08,0:20:28.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个好父亲的大部分特征\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}90% of being a dad...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.42,0:20:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会自然出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is just showin' up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.42,0:20:45.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那是我的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey! That's my bike!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.18,0:20:47.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I don't, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.83,0:20:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.63,0:20:53.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你  -我是来还你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You- - I was giving it back!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.03,0:20:59.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她无法原谅自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She couldn't forgive herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.86,0:21:01.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.96,0:21:04.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她又不得不做出选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she had to choose.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.47,0:21:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[具体情节参见电影《苏菲的选择》]
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.46,0:21:06.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想因为现在我有了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think because now I have-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.07,0:21:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有了  我们有了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we have- we have-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.04,0:21:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有了莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we have Lily,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.23,0:21:13.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难想象那样的境地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's so hard to imagine being put in that position.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.77,0:21:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我要在莉莉和米奇尔中选一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I had to choose Lily or Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.89,0:21:18.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想  我会选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I would choose-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.00,0:21:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know! I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.80,0:21:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.38,0:21:29.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know!

