[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.09,0:02:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.09,0:02:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.09,0:02:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.28,0:00:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母对我说过最气人的话?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the most irritating thing my parents say to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.99,0:00:07.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你喷太多古龙水了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"That's too much cologne."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.41,0:00:10.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"女孩子就是那样丧命的"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"That's how girls end up dead."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.75,0:00:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"别给我黑嘴"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Don't talk black to me."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.90,0:00:15.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"那样不合适  因为她是你老师"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"It's inappropriate because she's your teacher."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.97,0:00:17.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫黑嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you even talk black?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.62,0:00:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每句话都加个"嘿"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}End words with "Izzle"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.28,0:00:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是"回嘴"  笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's "Talk back," You idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.32,0:00:26.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"有点大人样好不好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Act more like an adult."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.44,0:00:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫有点大人样  大人该是什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What does "Act more like an adult" even mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.04,0:00:33.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你  都湿透了  逊死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at you, you're soaked! That is so lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.61,0:00:35.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你先开始的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're the one who wanted to do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.66,0:00:37.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们父子俩干啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you two doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.41,0:00:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我捡了个水鼬鼠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I picked up one of those Water Weasels.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.12,0:00:40.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把它接到水管的一头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You hook it on the end
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.12,0:00:42.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会在空中乱飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of the hose and it flies around in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像鼬鼠一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just like a weasel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.80,0:00:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看有多酷  他湿透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Look at how awesome. He's so wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:47.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把鼬鼠放我裤子里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I put the weasel in my pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.79,0:00:49.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-绝对是真的  -傻蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He totally did. - Dork!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.79,0:00:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我的窗子都湿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there a reason why my window's wet?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.96,0:00:54.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很难说  -不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hmm. Very difficult to say. - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.17,0:00:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-击掌  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Up top- Ow! Ow! - What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.84,0:00:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小  -亲爱的  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Little- - Sweetie, you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.43,0:00:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小抽了一下  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Little twinge. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.71,0:01:00.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去打911\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll call 911.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许消防员会来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe the firemen will come.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.52,0:01:04.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要不要  -电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, no! No, no! - Give me it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.52,0:01:08.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们镇上的消防员出了名的性感火辣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The firemen in our town have a reputation for being hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.94,0:01:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不爽他们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do I resent that?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.73,0:01:11.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不会  他们都是我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course not. These guys are my friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.19,0:01:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他们一起打球  烤蛋糕给他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I play basketball with them. I bake for 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.19,0:01:15.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的问题是  什么叫火辣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My question is: What's hot?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.57,0:01:17.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.57,0:01:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.27,0:01:20.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  她是你老师所以不合适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, it's inappropriate because it's your teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.08,0:01:22.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the big deal anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.08,0:01:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个惊喜  你们会知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a surprise. You'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.69,0:01:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.16,0:01:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  不是吧你  -就是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay, Jay, you didn't? - Yes, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.95,0:01:30.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在那家新开的红花餐厅订上位了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got us into that new Benihana.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.52,0:01:31.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}红花餐厅为美国著名日式连锁餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.25,0:01:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那有个厨师可以把虾翻进自己的帽子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They got a chef there that can flip a shrimp into his own hat.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.25,0:01:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.13,0:01:37.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  -乖儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad! - There's my boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.30,0:01:41.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他来这干什么  -杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The hell is he doing here? - Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他昨天就该来接曼尼的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. He was supposed to pick up manny yesterday
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.69,0:01:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果又一如既往地让他失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and disappointed him again, as usual.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.72,0:01:47.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在又突然冒出来就可以了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now he just sails in here out of the blue?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.98,0:01:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢那家伙  理由嘛  当然有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't like the guy. Do I have reasons? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.17,0:01:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正当理由?  当然有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good reasons? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.25,0:01:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要理由吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How many reasons do I need?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.60,0:01:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要  我就是不喜欢那家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}None. I don't like the guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.33,0:02:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来要给你们打电话的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I would have called,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.36,0:02:12.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我帮朋友买船的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but while I was buying this boat for a friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.50,0:02:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被另外一艘船追出海去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got chased out to sea by another boat "Tiqui tiqui".
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.10,0:02:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是海盗吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Were they pirates?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.63,0:02:18.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没问  -其实很容易分辨的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I didn't stop to ask. - Well, it's not hard to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.80,0:02:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有没有拿着弯刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did they have curvy swords and
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.00,0:02:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唱着海盗生活真快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}sing songs about how fun it is to be a pirate?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.38,0:02:25.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  房子真漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay. Such a beautiful house, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.18,0:02:26.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正打算出去吃晚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, we were just headed out to dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.87,0:02:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我空手来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, you think I show up empty-handed?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.31,0:02:30.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带晚餐了  龙虾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I brought dinner- lobsters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.27,0:02:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是你亲手抓的吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you catch them with your bare hands? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.68,0:02:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是我亲手买的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I bought them with my bare hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.08,0:02:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还带了瓶好酒  给杰的一盒上等雪茄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I have some nice wine, a good Cuban cigar for Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.96,0:02:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  用你的新手机帮他照张相吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, why don't you take a picture of him with your new camera phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.57,0:02:46.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没有新手机  -你现在有了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't have a camera phone. - You do now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.66,0:02:47.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.70,0:02:50.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激一波接一波  我心脏都快受不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All of this excitement, my heart is just going.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.45,0:02:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.15,0:02:53.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年暑假你来看我的时候记得带上它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You bring that with you when you come visit me this summer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.72,0:02:55.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你去坐我朋友的赛车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll go in a race car with my friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.56,0:02:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后看场斗牛什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and after that, maybe a bullfight.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.84,0:02:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们我都熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know all these guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.97,0:03:01.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斗牛士  他们简直就是艺术家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The matadors, they're like artists.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.51,0:03:03.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己就跟个斗牛艺术家一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're quite the bullfight artist yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.72,0:03:06.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  带你父亲去厨房参观下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I, uh- Manny, why don't you show your father to the kitchen?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:09.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  天啊  来点音乐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Por favor. Dios mo. Someone put on some music.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.48,0:03:10.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我们要热舞一宿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tonight, we dance!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.82,0:03:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会热舞的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we're gonna dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.96,0:03:14.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  今晚我住这没问题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oye, mi amor, est bien que me quede aqu esta noche?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.77,0:03:16.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维尔  我不知道  我看看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, Javier, yo no s. Esprate para ver qu puedo hacer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.02,0:03:19.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说什么  是不是要龙虾钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did he say? Does he need money for the lobsters?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.86,0:03:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  友好点  -"友好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Jay, be nice. - "Be nice."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.18,0:03:22.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来应该坐在铁板烧旁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could be sitting grill-side,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.56,0:03:24.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着厨师堆洋葱山的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}watching a guy build an onion volcano.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.62,0:03:26.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却看着里克·苏艾文在我厨房瞎晃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Instead, I got Rico Suave in my kitchen,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.87,0:03:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}里克·苏艾文 著名波多黎各籍摔角手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.56,0:03:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车位上还停了艘偷来的船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I got a stolen boat in my driveway.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.63,0:03:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为我  早将他踹得一干二净了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If it was for me, he'd be out of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.42,0:03:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是曼尼需要他的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it's good for Manny to be with his father.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.84,0:03:36.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当初怎么就看上他那种货色了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just can't believe you ever fell for that act.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.91,0:03:39.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥伦比亚人有时很有说服力的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Colombians can be very persuasive.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.84,0:03:43.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候神不知鬼不觉你就答应他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They can make you agree to things before you even know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.05,0:03:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当时一定很傻很天真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You must have been pretty naive.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.80,0:03:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但我现在找到真命天子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. But now I'm with the right man, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.54,0:03:48.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.39,0:03:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维尔只住一晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Javier is only going to stay one night.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.95,0:03:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.93,0:03:53.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.94,0:04:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气  我只是起来帮她换个尿布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't be mad. I just got up to change her.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔想用费伯睡眠法训练宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Mitchell really wanted to Ferberize the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.93,0:04:07.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费伯睡眠法  就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ferberize. It is a method of
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.48,0:04:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让婴儿晚上...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}getting the baby to sleep through the night...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.03,0:04:12.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上是  自己哭睡着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by, yes, basically letting her cry herself to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.54,0:04:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,折磨啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Torture.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.90,0:04:15.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是折磨  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not torture, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.63,0:04:17.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对有些人来说是很难受的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just hard if you happen to be a person
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.34,0:04:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人就是见不得别人受罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who hates to hear another person suffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.26,0:04:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是两个人一起受罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or two people suffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.39,0:04:29.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  你每次起床安抚她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. You got up to comfort her,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.70,0:04:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都只会让她觉得  她一哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which only teaches her that every time she cries,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.68,0:04:34.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸就会过来抱她  给她看最喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}her daddy will come in and cuddle her and put on her favorite-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.14,0:04:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在看什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are we watching?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.65,0:04:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱恩·德·帕尔玛的争议大作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brian De Palma's controversial masterpiece
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.66,0:04:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《疤面煞星》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scarface.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.41,0:04:42.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给孩子看合适吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For the baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.65,0:04:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很喜欢呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She happens to like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.74,0:04:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道是因为色彩还是声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know if it's the colors or the sounds-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.99,0:04:47.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜店大屠杀要来了  她最爱这段了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, here comes the nightclub massacre. She loves it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.74,0:04:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看她的小眼皮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Watch her little eyelids.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.81,0:04:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快睁不开了  真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's so cute. They get so heavy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.70,0:04:53.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.70,0:04:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  -我没事  真没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, honey. - I'm fine. No, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:58.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是  好吧  是癌症\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just- Okay, that's cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.38,0:04:59.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许只是颗肾结石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe it's just a kidney stone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"只是"  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Just," Claire?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.17,0:05:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's going on, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.48,0:05:03.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  回去睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's nothing. Go back to bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.76,0:05:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  爸爸  -别碰我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, but Dad... - Don't touch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.22,0:05:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢肯定只是颗肾结石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bet it's just a kidney stone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.66,0:05:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又说"只是"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Just" Again.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.94,0:05:09.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们谁下去给你妈倒杯水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Someone get your mom a glass of water...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.05,0:05:13.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再从车道上捡颗石子  看她觉得滋味如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and a piece of gravel from the driveway and see how she likes it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.01,0:05:13.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家在吵什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is everybody yelling?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.96,0:05:15.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸有点不对劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Something's wrong with Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.70,0:05:17.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吓着他了  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't frighten him. Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.81,0:05:20.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死了  死神要过来索命了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's gotta be death! Death is coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.01,0:05:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你得去医院  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, you need to go to the hospital. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.77,0:05:23.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用不用  吃药就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. I just need a pill.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.26,0:05:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我找片最大的药来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give me the biggest one you can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.36,0:05:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  深呼吸  深呼吸就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, breathe. Just-Just breathe.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.70,0:05:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生孩子的时候我也是这么跟你说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what I told you when youwere in labor
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.26,0:05:31.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果你把奶昔扔我脸上了  药呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you threw my smoothie at me. Pill!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.95,0:05:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去打电话  -真不用  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, I'm calling. - No, no, it's fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.08,0:05:36.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  过去了  疼痛已经过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's actually- It's fine. It's passing. It's passing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.75,0:05:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉吓着大家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am sorry to alarm everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.73,0:05:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该只是我反应过度了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I was probably just overreacting,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.54,0:05:41.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我体内住着个外星人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because there's an alien inside of me!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.68,0:05:42.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.34,0:05:44.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快停下  -我去打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, close it down. - I am definitely gonna call.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.26,0:05:47.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,系统全面衰竭  系统全面衰竭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All systems down. All systems down.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.00,0:05:55.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-混蛋  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Son of a bitch. - What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.84,0:05:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说呢  他在玩我的台球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's playing on my pool table, that's what.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.48,0:05:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概还给自己倒了杯好酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Probably got himself a nice drink too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.76,0:06:01.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where you going, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.23,0:06:03.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我就出去看看  -算了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just to check things out, okay? - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.52,0:06:06.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见没  他又开始乱动我的遥控器了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You hear that? Now he's messing around with my remote control.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.36,0:06:08.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么远你怎么听得见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't hear that from here!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.12,0:06:12.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.94,0:06:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  对不起  吵醒你了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay. Listen, I'm sorry. Did I wake you up?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.04,0:06:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我本来睡得就浅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, I'm a light sleeper.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.62,0:06:20.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-年纪大了就这样  -你才不老呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's what happens when you get older. - Oh, you're not old.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.30,0:06:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说我老\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't say I was old.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.05,0:06:23.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来也不怎么睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never sleep much anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.67,0:06:27.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凌晨两点以后  生活才精彩得多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Life is just more interesting after 2:00 A.M.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.17,0:06:28.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美酒更香醇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, the liquor tastes better,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.97,0:06:30.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人更美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the, uh, women are more beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.80,0:06:31.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么说来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is it they say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.41,0:06:35.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜晚是属于诗人与疯子的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That the night belongs to the poets and the madmen.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.68,0:06:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是哪个  -也许两个都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Which are you? - Perhaps both.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.27,0:06:40.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉你也一样  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I think maybe you too, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.46,0:06:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到那边你骑着摩托车的照片了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see a picture over here of you on a motorcycle.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.11,0:06:46.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你喜欢骑摩托车吗  -曾经\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You ride? - I used to.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.23,0:06:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经  曾经\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Used to? Used to?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.94,0:06:49.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.41,0:06:53.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全世界语言中最伤感的词莫过于此了  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the saddest words in any language, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.24,0:06:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你给我说说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, help me out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.58,0:06:57.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都觉得你很了不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody sees you as this great guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.16,0:06:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过着到处冒险的精彩生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you live this life of adventure.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.37,0:07:01.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么一个字都不信呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How come I don't buy a word of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.38,0:07:04.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见的只是个爽约的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All I see is a dad who doesn't show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.14,0:07:06.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼了解我  我是活在当下的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Manny knows me. I live in the now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.75,0:07:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的当下就是昨天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I was living in the yesterday
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.99,0:07:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼坐在门口哭泣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when Manny was crying outside that door...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.13,0:07:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你第十次爽约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}cause you didn't show up for the 10th time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.88,0:07:14.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我没来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And when I don't come, you think,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.49,0:07:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我在别处花天酒地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh- what, I'm just off chasing a good time, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.52,0:07:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有想过  我来这里也很不好受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You ever think it might be hard for me, coming here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.98,0:07:23.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  因为歌洛莉亚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? Because of Gloria?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.48,0:07:25.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.16,0:07:36.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.62,0:07:40.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  他们马上就来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, they're on their way.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.00,0:07:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  围过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, kids, gather around.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.42,0:07:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像拥抱我的样子  但别碰我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like you're hugging me, but don't touch me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.71,0:07:49.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now look, I'm gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We know, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.85,0:07:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.53,0:07:52.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能站起来就是个奇迹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a miracle I'm standing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.34,0:07:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  万一天有不测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But look, in case anything happens-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.24,0:08:00.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你们明白  如果我有时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you to know that if I'd had time,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.05,0:08:01.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定早把楼梯修好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would have fixed that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.27,0:08:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸  谢谢你  -我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks, Dad. - I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.33,0:08:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  别哭  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't cry, Luke. I'm okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.98,0:08:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把茶几打碎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I broke the coffee table!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.98,0:08:09.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.87,0:08:10.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.82,0:08:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打碎玻璃茶几的是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I broke the glass coffee table.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.48,0:08:14.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你当时发誓不是你干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The one you swore you didn't break,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.45,0:08:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们因此怪罪艾斯贝兰斯  把她开除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we blamed Esperanza and fired her...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.87,0:08:19.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害的她在感恩节偷了只火鸡给家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she stole a turkey at Thanksgiving for her family
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.23,0:08:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果被驱逐出境了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and got deported?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.54,0:08:21.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.00,0:08:24.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很抱歉  -你会受到惩罚的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm sorry. - You will be sorry!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.39,0:08:26.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们到了  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They're here!  - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.47,0:08:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.63,0:08:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克打碎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke broke the-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.13,0:08:34.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你换衣服了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you changed your clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.49,0:08:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不换衣服怎么见人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I had- I had to get dressed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.43,0:08:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换了件这么性感紧身的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Into that sexy, clingy-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.02,0:08:40.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  是给那些消防员看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. It's the firemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.14,0:08:40.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.89,0:08:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还擦了口红\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And lipstick!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.53,0:08:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在剧烈疼痛中煎熬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm out here convulsing in agony
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.38,0:08:45.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有心思找漂亮衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you're looking for cute tops to wear?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.11,0:08:47.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就随手拿了一件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just threw on the first thing I could find.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.00,0:08:49.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有时间  如果你还想换条紧身裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We got a minute, if you wanna try on some tighter jeans-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.73,0:08:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Phil, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.66,0:08:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不管怎么说  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. By all means, Claire,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.04,0:08:54.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然得以最性感火辣的面貌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we want you looking your sexiest...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.74,0:08:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来迎接那些健壮基情的消防员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when the hunky, gay firemen get here!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.91,0:08:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么样  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How we doing? - We're great.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.49,0:09:00.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是说我  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He meant me! - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.62,0:09:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.60,0:09:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  杰  你是个强劲的对手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, listen, Jay. You're a tough guy to compete with.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.86,0:09:10.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你拥有的这一切吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, look at all you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.00,0:09:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你因此只好让曼尼伤心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So Manny has to suffer?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.38,0:09:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.17,0:09:15.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以后会更加努力的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I'm going to try harder.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.88,0:09:18.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许他同时有我们两个父亲是好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But maybe it's a good thing that he has the two of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.93,0:09:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你身上他可以学到沉稳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From you, he learns stability.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.07,0:09:23.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而从我身上  他可以学到随性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From me, he learns how to be spontaneous,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.27,0:09:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掐住命运的咽喉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}grab life by the throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.89,0:09:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有时候也会有掐住别人喉咙的冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we do a little throat grabbing ourselves around here, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.51,0:09:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前正打算去红花餐厅  结果你突然出现了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were on our way to Benihana when you showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.63,0:09:32.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我儿子能追逐他的梦想就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, as long as my boy follows his passion.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.36,0:09:33.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这辈子做的最烂的职业决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The worst career decision I ever made
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.75,0:09:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是去打棒球  但我无时无刻不在享受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was playing baseball, but I loved every minute of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.61,0:09:39.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打过棒球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You played baseball?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.49,0:09:41.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看家本事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I lived baseball.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.32,0:09:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只打进了三A联盟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I only made it to Triple-A,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.79,0:09:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}三A联盟是美国职棒最高等级的小联盟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.25,0:09:46.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我跟索萨  麦圭尔他们都一起打过球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I played with all those guys- Sosa, McGwire.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.29,0:09:47.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来也打过的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You look like you played some.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.28,0:09:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高中的时候打过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I played in high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.58,0:09:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打得还行  但从来没击中过曲线球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was all right. Never hit a curve ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.75,0:09:53.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以那就是你的梦想吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So that's a dream of yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.92,0:09:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击中曲线球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To- To hit a curve?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.95,0:09:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Used to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.59,0:09:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是"曾经"  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Used to be." Por favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.95,0:09:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又说了一次是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said that again, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.34,0:10:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, please. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.15,0:10:01.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我不该总这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're right, I shouldn't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.68,0:10:02.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们干什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you guys doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.98,0:10:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  吵醒你了吗  真抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, did we wake you up? I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.02,0:10:07.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我在做科学课的额外学分作业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I was doing my science extra credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不用想也知道  -我也能玩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Of course you were. - So, can I play?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.40,0:10:11.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你爸爸决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's up to your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.82,0:10:15.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们桌球玩的差不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I think we're done with pool for right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.15,0:10:18.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个更好的主意  走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a better idea for the three of us. Vamos.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:22.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么认识那家伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, how do you know this guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.14,0:10:23.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他欠我个小人情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He owes me a little favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.50,0:10:32.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚简直酷毙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is the coolest night ever!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.29,0:10:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来试试曲线球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, let's see about that curve ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.97,0:10:41.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-出去  -我还以为你在床上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Out. - I thought you were-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.34,0:10:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是枕头堆的  出去  快出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those were pillows. Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.22,0:10:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  你意识到你有多气人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, do you realize how infuriating this is?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.06,0:10:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"费伯睡眠法"的精髓就在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The whole point of Ferberizing...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.81,0:10:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们家闺女自己入睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is to teach her to put herself to sleep,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.45,0:10:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却一直捣乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you keep ruining it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.73,0:10:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我情难自禁  我就像一头小母熊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't help it. I'm like a mother bear.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.88,0:10:58.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊宝宝一哭  我就得赶去抱抱她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I hear my cub crying, I have to run to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.37,0:11:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可不是头熊  快回屋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Except you're not a bear. Get in our room.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.20,0:11:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回  小卡  回屋  回屋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get- Cam, get in there. Get in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.99,0:11:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别闹了  -快点  回屋去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cut it out. - All the way- Our room.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.79,0:11:08.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去  快进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get! Get in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.66,0:11:10.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  快走  进去  进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Come on. Get in there. Get!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.63,0:11:14.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不公平  为什么不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's so unfair. Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.79,0:11:16.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为女孩子就是那样丧命的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because that's how girls end up dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.08,0:11:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  -大伙儿都来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, honey. - Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.36,0:11:19.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就想看看你怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We just wanted to see how you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.93,0:11:20.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没妨碍到你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is this a bad time?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:23.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  只是在手术前给他注射一点镇定剂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we're just giving him something to relax before the procedure.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.65,0:11:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手术肯定会顺利的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which is gonna go just fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.76,0:11:27.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们知道  -鬼知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, we know. - We don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.77,0:11:28.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你爹下不了手术台\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In case it doesn't,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.75,0:11:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应我  跟你们的消防员后爸好好相处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}promise me you'll be nice to your new fireman daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.52,0:11:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯了吧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Unbelievable.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.25,0:11:34.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老婆昨晚居然为了消防员梳妆打扮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My wife got dressed up for the firemen last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.73,0:11:37.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有为消防员打扮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't get dressed up for the firemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.01,0:11:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高跟鞋啊  勾死人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those heels were really hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.69,0:11:40.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还穿高跟  -话题结束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You put on heels? - Let's drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.90,0:11:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要对你做什么啊老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are they doing to you, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.91,0:11:44.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身体里有颗烦人的石头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a little scratchy rock inside of me
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.84,0:11:47.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大夫们会用根管子把它吸出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they're sliding in a tube and sucking it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.87,0:11:49.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该不害怕吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not scared, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.58,0:11:52.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老爸我什么时候害怕过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When was the last time you saw your old man scared?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.50,0:11:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次你缠到蜘蛛网\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When you walked through the spiderweb.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.50,0:11:55.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有次我们玩灵应牌时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When we were playing with the Ouija board
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.61,0:11:57.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一阵风把门给关上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the wind blew the door shut.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.10,0:12:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不是风  伙计  是我们招来的灵物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There was no wind, buddy. We brought something forth.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.34,0:12:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟  镇定剂起作用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. This stuff's really hitting me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.68,0:12:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五脏六腑都麻醉酥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My insides feel like velvet.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.85,0:12:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在外面等我一下好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you guys wait out in the hallway, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.10,0:12:11.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  快好起来  -会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Feel better, Dad. - I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.10,0:12:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你  老爸  -我也爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Love you, Dad. - Love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.02,0:12:16.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爱你  -卢克  老弟  等会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Love you. - Luke, buddy, hold back a sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.94,0:12:19.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会死的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is not gonna happen, okay,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.65,0:12:20.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过万一遭遇不测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but there is a scenario
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.51,0:12:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成了一家之主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where you could be the man of the house...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.15,0:12:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得知道家里所有的识别码和密码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you need to know all the PIN numbers and passwords.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.28,0:12:26.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-741  -我才不要做家里的男主人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- 741 - I don't wanna be the man of the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.66,0:12:27.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是"黑"嘴的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, don't talk black to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.69,0:12:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝儿  你爸会好起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, your dad's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.43,0:12:31.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去外面等我吧  他会没事的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you wait out in the hall. He'll be fine, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.63,0:12:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我得赶紧送他们上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I'm just gonna run them to school.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.15,0:12:36.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送完就过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be back right after.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.25,0:12:38.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-恩  克莱尔  -我在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Claire? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.25,0:12:41.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实打扮了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You did get dressed up, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.42,0:12:44.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我随手拿了一件衣服穿的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I pulled on the first thing I saw, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.54,0:12:47.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  不提了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I'll drop it
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.15,0:12:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,药起效了  好困\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause this stuff is making me fall asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:52.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我长眠于世  你对我说的最后一句\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if I never wake up, I'd hate
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.09,0:12:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谎话的话  我做鬼也会记恨你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for the last thing you ever said to me to be a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.32,0:13:10.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我真的小小地打扮了一下下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I might have gotten dressed up just a tiny bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.54,0:13:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我就知道  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I knew it. - Oh, damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.26,0:13:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  上学要迟到了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, we're gonna be late for school.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.26,0:13:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天怎么这么累啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you so tired today?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.60,0:13:33.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何不让我送他去呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Any reason I can't take him?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.60,0:13:35.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然起床了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm surprised you're up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.40,0:13:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可知道你昨晚几点回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know what time you went back to bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.97,0:13:39.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没大碍  我们就出去打了会儿球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, it was nothing. We just went out, we hit a few balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.86,0:13:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对猜不到我们去哪儿打了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you'll never guess where.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.84,0:13:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜哈维尔上面有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess Javier knew a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.16,0:13:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.28,0:13:44.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他可跟你认识了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now that he knows you,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.47,0:13:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后他要是有困难  你就成他上面的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the next time he needs something, you are the guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:51.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈咪呀  你是不是也带他去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, Dios mo. Did you took him with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.22,0:13:52.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍到学校再打瞌睡会死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You couldn't wait to get to school to do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.82,0:13:55.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  跟我去上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, vamonos para el colegio.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.26,0:13:57.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  今天迟大发了  快去学校\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go. We're gonna be so late. Vamonos.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.46,0:13:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得迟到了  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Vamos a llegar tardsimo, Manny,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.77,0:14:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,磨叽什么呢  快上车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}qu te pasa? Get in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.54,0:14:04.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得你说过  要我好好跟哈维尔相处的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you said you wanted me to bond with Javier.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.51,0:14:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说让你友好点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said be nice, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.17,0:14:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没说让你们带着曼尼刷夜打球啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't say take Manny up all night and play games.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.76,0:14:12.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们还吃了热狗哦  -给老娘睡觉去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Then we got hot dogs. - Ay. Go to sleep!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.55,0:14:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是想要一个疯狂的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I wanted to be married to a wild man,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.41,0:14:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会离开哈维尔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would have stayed with Javier.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.94,0:14:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Qu pasa?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.69,0:14:21.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  -我的天呐  不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad! - Por dios, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.27,0:14:22.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.91,0:14:26.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.38,0:14:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们该不是要走了吧  -我得去上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're not leaving, are you? - I've got school.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.74,0:14:30.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么上学  -是的  上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? School? - Yes, school.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.61,0:14:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们去学校是要学知识的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's where people go to learn things,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.54,0:14:34.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说别带着小孩子刷夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like not to keep children up all night.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.41,0:14:36.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他招了吗  -他弱爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He told her? - He's weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.04,0:14:39.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你说你曾经喜欢骑摩托车  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, listen, you said you used to like riding motorcycles, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.78,0:14:40.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我给你带了一辆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I brought you one.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.66,0:14:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  但我得工作  -工作毛啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know. But I kind of got work. - Work.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.63,0:14:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-上吧  杰  -对啊  上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go, Jay. - Yeah, go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.99,0:14:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  杰  把曼尼也带上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, go, Jay, and take Manny with you too!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.10,0:14:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.92,0:14:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  曼尼尔·阿尔伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Manuel Alberto!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.81,0:14:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车  不然老娘把你塞到后备箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In the car or I put you in the trunk!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.10,0:14:55.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我不跟你争了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, I'm not gonna argue anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.14,0:14:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不多嘴了  你随意吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna say anything else. Do whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.02,0:15:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但别让老娘再听到你抱怨哥伦比亚人疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I don't wanna hear you any more saying that Colombians are crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.47,0:15:03.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为跟你比起来我们弱爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause you're the one that is acting crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.42,0:15:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然说你是被他带疯的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}even though he's the one that is making you act crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.44,0:15:08.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道自己在说神马  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I don't know what the hell I'm talking about! Manny!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.53,0:15:17.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没必要在她午睡时回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You didn't need to come home during nap time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.69,0:15:20.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚的事证明我十分有必要回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think we proved last night that I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.46,0:15:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  她就在后面  你走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she's back there now, so why don't you go,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.73,0:15:23.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心老板找你麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so you don't get in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.79,0:15:24.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  我跟大家说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's okay. I told everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.56,0:15:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找了个不可靠的伴侣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I have an unreliable partner,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.42,0:15:28.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  他们表示理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and, uh, they understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.43,0:15:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道不  我才不要在这里被冷嘲热讽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I don't need to sit here and be condescended to.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.14,0:15:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去弄杯冰红茶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna make myself an ice tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.99,0:15:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信不信我抽你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will bring you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.47,0:15:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你  别逗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't bring me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.92,0:15:38.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会扫堂腿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll sweep your legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.04,0:15:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不是正常人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's something wrong with you...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.19,0:15:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家闺女如此痛苦抑郁地哭喊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that the sound of our child in such distress
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.63,0:15:44.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然扰不了你半根神经\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}doesn't bother you more.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.45,0:15:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才不抑郁呢  而且\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's not in distress,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.49,0:15:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此事恰恰证明  你比她更需要费伯睡眠法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and this just proves that you need this more than she does.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.07,0:15:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得用此法锻炼两个宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm Ferberizing two babies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.66,0:15:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几天有浣熊溜进劳森家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Raccoons slipped into the lawsons' home
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.53,0:15:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷了一长条面包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and stole a loaf of bread.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.12,0:15:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your point?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.78,0:15:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想想  莉莉房间窗户开了道缝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That we left Lily's window open a crack,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.41,0:15:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浣熊要找些小菜做个三明治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and those raccoons need something to put between that bread,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.49,0:16:00.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后莉莉就哭着喊救命了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that is Lily's "Help me" Cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.04,0:16:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-熊妈妈来救你了  莉莉  -你敢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm coming for you, Lily. - No, you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.17,0:16:03.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不准去  卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are not coming, Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.98,0:16:06.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我去  嘿  你撒手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me go! Hey, stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.50,0:16:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我  下来  你干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let go! Get off me! What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.84,0:16:10.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-停下  -我不停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Stop! - I will not stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.88,0:16:13.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别淘气了  宝宝我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop being such a baby. I'm coming for you!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.60,0:16:18.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-咋了  -脚崴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Oh, my ankle.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.60,0:16:20.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚崴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My ankle.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.56,0:16:30.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会从摩托车上摔死呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay! I guess you didn't kill yourself in the motorcycle today.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.28,0:16:32.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你恨不得亲手杀了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I figured you were looking forward to killing me,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.19,0:16:33.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么能驾车归西  让你愿望落空呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I'm not gonna take that away from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.13,0:16:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  哈维尔打给你了没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, did Javier call you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.64,0:16:37.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啊  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, why?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.69,0:16:40.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要拉我去酒吧会会他的老球友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's dragging me to this bar with some of his old baseball pals.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.45,0:16:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说好5点这边见的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was supposed to be here at 5:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.58,0:16:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他拉着你啊  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ah, he's dragging you, huh? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.74,0:16:44.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得没什么不妥的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figured it would be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.79,0:16:46.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见识过当中一半的人打比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've seen half these guys play.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.96,0:16:49.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维尔说没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Javier says it's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.67,0:16:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你笑什么  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? What's the joke? - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.59,0:16:54.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好笑  你之前还笑话我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just funny to me... that you make fun of me
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.84,0:16:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会被他那样的人勾去了魂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because I was seduced by him,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.30,0:16:57.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你现在...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but here you are-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.35,0:16:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有被他勾去了魂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No one is getting seduced.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.81,0:17:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么做都是为了曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm doing this for Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.89,0:17:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦  你们俩去山上浪漫地野餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, it's very important for Manny
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.75,0:17:06.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对曼尼来说是多么滴重要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you two go and have a nice picnic in the mountains.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.81,0:17:08.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  那不叫野餐  就喝了杯咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}First of all, it wasn't a picnic. We stopped for coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.86,0:17:11.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧那儿有卖煎饼果子的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They just happened to be selling crepes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.48,0:17:14.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  他打来知会我一声  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen. Let me know when he calls, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.11,0:17:16.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  眨眼就6点了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, it's almost 6:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.99,0:17:20.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们都盼着你回家呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The kids are so excited for you to come home.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.99,0:17:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.88,0:17:23.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  卢克还给你做了个标语呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, Luke made you a sign.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.79,0:17:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他最贴心了  -你看上去气色挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, he's a sweetie. - Yeah. You seem great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.38,0:17:30.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-确实感觉不错  -那就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I am great. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.54,0:17:32.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了消防员那事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Except for that fireman thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.25,0:17:33.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还记着呢  -必须的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You remember it? - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.26,0:17:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  对不起  -没事啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, okay. Look, I am sorry. I'm so sorry. - Ah, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.84,0:17:39.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的错  没有借口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's no excuse for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.68,0:17:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一家庭妇女  每天邋里邋遢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I just spend so much time in dowdy mom clothes,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.56,0:17:46.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上都是面粉和花生酱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm covered in paste and peanut butter,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.18,0:17:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想偶尔能散发点魅力  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I just- I wanted to feel attractive for a second, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.11,0:17:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I really-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.11,0:17:56.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  再给我点时间释怀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, I just need a little bit of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.61,0:17:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我会没事的  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gonna be fine. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.16,0:18:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-恩  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.16,0:18:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就想开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was already fine with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:03.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥在下一盘很大的棋  克莱尔搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's the deal: Claire messed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.13,0:18:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她欠我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She owed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.21,0:18:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千年难得一遇的好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This never happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.33,0:18:10.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老菲尔金牌在手啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Old Phil has a golden ticket.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.75,0:18:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  我可以立刻兑换些小恩惠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, I could have cashed that in right away for something small-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.57,0:18:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用打扫车库  去参加一周马戏团夏令营之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}get out of cleaning the garage, a week at circus camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.59,0:18:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-记忆犹新  -知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Still fresh. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.76,0:18:23.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是拖得越久  她愧疚感越多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But the longer you hold on to it, the more the guilt builds,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.51,0:18:25.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥得到的也就越多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the more you get.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.43,0:18:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖五年  和弟兄们去巴黎旅行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Five years: Trip to Paris with my buddies.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.98,0:18:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖十年  漂亮的敞篷车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ten years: Sweet little convertible.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.11,0:18:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖二十年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Twenty years:
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.11,0:18:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  语言表达清晰  全功能的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, fully articulating, five-function robot...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.32,0:18:43.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能读懂我的思想  有自主感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that can read my mind and has feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.28,0:18:47.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你不是打算不辞而别吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, you're not leaving without saying good-bye, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.45,0:18:48.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  伊莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Elaine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.31,0:18:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是你老公吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is this your husband? - Uh-huh.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.50,0:18:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见了  巴黎  -我来探望我姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Good-bye, Paris. - I'm visiting my sister...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.70,0:18:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一下午就在那玩魔术牌逗我们开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he was entertaining us all afternoon with his card tricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.70,0:19:00.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔来啦  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is that Phil? - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.64,0:19:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  菲尔这就走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mom, Phil's leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.97,0:19:07.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不跟我抱抱吗  -一波又一波啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Without a hug? - Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.60,0:19:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  语言表达清晰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good-bye, fully articulating,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.10,0:19:13.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全功能的  会说"再见"的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}five-function robot with the ability to- Good-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.65,0:19:15.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布兰妮  快点宝贝儿  菲尔走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brittany, hurry, honey. Phil's leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.53,0:19:18.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.86,0:19:23.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-脚踝还疼吗  -拔凉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How's your ankle? - It's cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.74,0:19:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起害你受伤  -别  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm sorry I hurt you. - No. No, don't be. I-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.70,0:19:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可能轻易伤到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could have just as easily hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.37,0:19:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你倒是挺大言不惭的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's cute that you think that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.71,0:19:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  小卡  我不想一直唱白脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, Cam, I- I can't always be the bad cop here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.38,0:19:38.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道自己很严格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I know it's my issue,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.70,0:19:40.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不希望她成长的过程中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but she can't grow up with
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.62,0:19:42.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直是那个胸襟宽广  温暖可人的爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}one huggy, happy, cuddly dad...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.51,0:19:46.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却是那个死板严肃  满嘴教条的爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and one frowny, lesson-teachy dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.18,0:19:47.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because guess which one
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.86,0:19:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她最后会选谁陪她走婚礼红毯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she's gonna ask to walk her down the aisle.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.56,0:19:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh- Y- Okay, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.86,0:19:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以适时唱唱白脸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can be the bad cop sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.25,0:20:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她吃蔬菜的任务就交给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll always make her eat her vegetables.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.11,0:20:03.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行  看牙医也交给你  -成交\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Dentist. - Deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.57,0:20:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -只要你逼她练小提琴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Good. - As long as you make her practice her violin.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.53,0:20:08.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  小提琴  我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. The violin. I like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.12,0:20:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  到时候我们一起伴着她走红毯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we're both walking her down the aisle.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.58,0:20:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你到时候还能走路的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Assuming you can walk by then.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.58,0:20:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去医院看看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you need to go to the hospital for that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.46,0:20:19.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  妈呀  不了  没那么严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, God. No, no. It's not that bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.80,0:20:21.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是打911吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you meant call 911, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.51,0:20:22.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感消防员哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Firemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.70,0:20:25.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快打电话  我换件衣服去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, you call, and I'm gonna change my shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.00,0:20:29.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  如果要我有点大人样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, if I'm supposed to act like an adult,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.68,0:20:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是让我像世上正常的大人那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is that act like adults I see in the world-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.62,0:20:36.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是像家里的这些大人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or the adults in my family?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.82,0:20:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要我像家里的大人一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause if it's the ones in my family-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.82,0:20:47.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走吧  回去吧  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on. Let's go. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.24,0:20:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.74,0:20:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没什么难的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how hard could that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.63,0:20:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在医院里玩的纸牌魔术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doing the card tricks at the hospital
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.95,0:21:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重燃了我的魔术之火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}really got me fired up about my magic again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.55,0:21:04.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你刚刚那张牌吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is this your card?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.05,0:21:07.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你真牛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Oh, my gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.80,0:21:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  并不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's- It's not, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.51,0:21:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  真不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, uh, no. It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.68,0:21:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最虐心的就是对方自己都忘了是哪张牌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The hardest part is when people forget their card,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.99,0:21:15.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那样就显得我像个傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because then I look like the idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.73,0:21:17.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  再玩一次  -我们真得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right. Let's do it again. - We really have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.90,0:21:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你以为我喜欢这样吗  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You think I like this? - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  哥教你一招好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. I'm gonna teach you one, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.61,0:21:23.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数到三你就抓住这个  准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}On the count of three, just grab this. You ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.61,0:21:25.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把手伸出来  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Put your hand out. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.61,0:21:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二  三  走你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One, two, three. There it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  这整哪出啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. What was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.91,0:21:31.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢配合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.87,0:21:33.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿我当猴耍呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me?

