[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.05,0:00:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  薄饼闻起来不错哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those pancakes smell great.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.50,0:00:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿那些是要上哪儿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing with those?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.66,0:00:07.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克和我准备开车去收旧东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke and I are doing a recycling drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.24,0:00:08.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能收到够多的瓶子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If we collect enough bottles
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.50,0:00:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以在非洲建一所学校了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they build a school in Africa.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.02,0:00:11.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能读一所\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wouldn't that be so cool
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.21,0:00:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用瓶子堆起来的学校就太给力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to go to a school made out of bottles?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.98,0:00:16.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[特殊学校指专为残障人开设的学校]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.98,0:00:16.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那铁定是所特殊学校\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That would certainly be a special school.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.86,0:00:17.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有听到我说什么没  爹妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you hear what I said, parents?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.86,0:00:19.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"特殊学校"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Special school"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.94,0:00:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  大家先别太大反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, nobody make a big deal about it,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.07,0:00:23.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和迪兰分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I just broke up with Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.20,0:00:25.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别啊  -老天  你没事吧  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No  - Oh, my gosh. Are you okay, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.87,0:00:27.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没事  我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I'm fine. I just
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.87,0:00:29.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得找个聪明灵活点的男朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need to date someone who has a clue,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.91,0:00:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而迪兰就是个傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}instead of an idiot
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.13,0:00:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次把车骑出车库时都要撞到头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who bangs his head every time he rides his bike out of his garage
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.19,0:00:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every time!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.29,0:00:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真为你难过  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.37,0:00:39.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你俩感到难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry for both of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.67,0:00:41.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会儿发短信安慰一下他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll have to text him later.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.59,0:00:43.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我得去洗澡了  要迟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm. I gotta jump in the shower. I'm gonna be late.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.68,0:00:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪儿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.83,0:00:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去见我的好朋友  瓦莱丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm going to meet my friend Valerie.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.27,0:00:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们15年没见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I haven't seen her in 15 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.48,0:00:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前是同事来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We used to work together.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.26,0:00:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你上过班?  -嗯哼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-You worked? -Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.75,0:00:51.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不出来你上班是什么样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can't imagine you working.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.29,0:00:52.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  我跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, let me tell you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.58,0:00:54.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样对女性说话很不礼貌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is very offensive to women.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.40,0:00:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老妈工作时很卖力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your mom works very hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.99,0:00:58.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是她现在选择照顾我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just now she works for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.53,0:01:02.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你们说  当年我可是前途大好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will have you know that I had quite the little career going.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.15,0:01:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时可是星冠酒店的客户经理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was an account manager at Starcrest Hotels.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.70,0:01:06.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有自己的小单间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had a little cubicle,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.19,0:01:07.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先穿运动鞋去上班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and I wore my tennis shoes to work...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.95,0:01:09.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后换成工作装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and changed into my work pumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.45,0:01:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟电影《上班女郎》一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was very Working Girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.04,0:01:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那部电影真赞  -嗯哼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That movie's so clutch  - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.04,0:01:15.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说  我当年那叫一个宏图大展啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't mind saying I was making quite a splash.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.54,0:01:16.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么不干了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then, why'd you quit?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.88,0:01:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  你可以说我守旧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Haley, call me old-fashioned,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.67,0:01:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想全心顾家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I wanted to focus on raising a family.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.63,0:01:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我嫁给了你老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I married your dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.76,0:01:25.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了五个月以后  我们就  就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Five months later, we... were...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.34,0:01:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又过了四个月  有了这个小美人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}four months away from having this little bundle of joy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.72,0:01:29.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.64,0:01:34.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家大律师驾到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's my lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.85,0:01:36.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚出了场小车祸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria got into a little car accident,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.85,0:01:38.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸让我帮她处理下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so my dad asked me to help her out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.86,0:01:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是第一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, uh, this is the first
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.22,0:01:42.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸向我请求法律援助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}time that my dad's asked me for legal advice,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.65,0:01:44.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it's-it's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.33,0:01:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那让我觉得他还是很尊重我的工作的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's nice to know that he respects me in that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.48,0:01:49.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔是个超棒的律师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Mitchell is an amazing lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.24,0:01:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦想他能进最高法院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My dream for him is that one day he'll be on the Supreme Court.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.95,0:01:54.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why, Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.50,0:01:55.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样参加派对时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So at parties
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就可以向大家卖弄我男友"法力高强"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can tell everyone my partner is one of the Supremes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.84,0:02:02.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧  精壮如钢铁的灰发老朽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There he is-the steely, grizzled veteran...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.05,0:02:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和勇猛小胖星大干一场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}ready to do battle with the plucky upstart.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.22,0:02:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速度对战优雅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Speed versus grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.90,0:02:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-野性战...  -直接办正事儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Brute force versus  -Let's just do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.89,0:02:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰和我都喜欢健身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay and I are both gym rats.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.55,0:02:12.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱桑拿那种干热的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love the sauna. That's the dry heat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.56,0:02:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有湿热的蒸汽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the steam, wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.18,0:02:17.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也超迷手球式墙球的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, of course, I am just a kook for racquetball.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.10,0:02:19.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连续两年拿俱乐部冠军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Club champ two years in a row,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.13,0:02:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在密苏里州通加诺克西的健康中心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tonganoxie, Missouri Rec Center.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.36,0:02:25.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以杰和我这几个月都在计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, naturally, Jay and I have been trying for months...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.19,0:02:28.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去打一场球赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to get together to bang the old hollow rubber ball around.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.64,0:02:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是竭尽全力在躲那场比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have been avoiding this day like the plague.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.58,0:02:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去健身  一方面是冲着那种气氛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, part of going to the gym is the lockerroom atmosphere.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.04,0:02:37.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果身边有一个基佬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if I'm there with a gay guy,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.43,0:02:39.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气氛就完全毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's-it's just not gonna be the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.82,0:02:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说  更衣室就是更衣室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, for me, it's a locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.67,0:02:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对他  就是脱衣舞厅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For him, it's a showroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.34,0:02:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She doesn't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.14,0:02:59.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*开着我的小车呀*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Driving in my car*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.03,0:03:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*给你看我的伤疤*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*I'll let you see my scar*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:06.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞毛啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.91,0:03:13.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人说我是销售员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some people call me a salesman.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.76,0:03:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得自己是"销售之友"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I call myself a sales friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.37,0:03:17.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  我需要陌生人能够信任我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So obviously, I need strangers to trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.45,0:03:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我觉得很不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't take kindly to it
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.52,0:03:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有人给我画上汤姆·希莱克斯那样的胡子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when someone Tom Sellecks my bus bench.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.70,0:03:22.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[汤姆·希莱克斯  著名演员\N在播美剧《警察世家》中弗兰克的扮演者]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.58,0:03:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是菲尔·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.52,0:03:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  我是芭芭拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, it's Barbara.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.59,0:03:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕特森一家不想买了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The Pattersons wanna back out of the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.38,0:03:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.50,0:03:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他家老婆犹豫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The wife's getting cold feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.07,0:03:29.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我让她打给你了  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I told her to call you. -Okay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.97,0:03:32.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来处理吧  我绝不能丢掉这一单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll handle it. I'm not losing this sale.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.02,0:03:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-另外  -我可是花了大量心血啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-By the way  -I've spent way too much time on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.06,0:03:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你上班经过榆树街吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, do you take Elm when you come to work?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.53,0:03:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见了  芭芭拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I saw it, Barbara.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.82,0:03:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健身房不错嘛  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a terrific gym, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.82,0:03:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛巾随便用  我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Very liberal with the towels. I love that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.83,0:03:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淋浴室单间的  先告诉你一声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Showers are private, in case you wondered.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.00,0:03:53.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想那个  不过谢谢你的提醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wasn't, but thanks for the heads-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.83,0:03:57.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是惊奇呀  宽松平角裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, that's a surprise. Boxers.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.40,0:03:58.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有必要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that necessary?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.25,0:04:00.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是一直想象  你应该是穿紧身白色内裤的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just always pictured you as a tighty-whitey guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.05,0:04:02.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你了  下次你想象时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, do me a favor. The next time you picture me,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.72,0:04:03.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想我的内裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}leave the underwear out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.93,0:04:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我想象也只是会想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, don't you worry. The only thing I'm picturing...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.37,0:04:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是拿你拖地  那会拖得多干净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is how clean the floor's gonna be when I'm done mopping it with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.82,0:04:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就这点水平吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that the best you can do?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.43,0:04:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为光这种不痛不痒的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause it's gonna take a little more than some
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.53,0:04:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点没感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}lame trash talk to get me out of my-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.77,0:04:16.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠  你搞毛啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gaah! What the hell was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.73,0:04:18.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的屁屁亲上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our butts pressed against each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.44,0:04:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有亲上  只是隔空对望了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They didn't press. It was glancing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.89,0:04:20.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop talking about it!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.77,0:04:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了  你又不是头一次来更衣室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh come on. All the time you've spent in a locker room,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.48,0:04:23.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不是第一次"屁屁碰"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this can't be your first moon landing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.07,0:04:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还专门起了个名儿  -很平常啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-You got a name for it? -It's very common.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.03,0:04:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太不淡定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got off easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.78,0:04:28.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少不是沐浴之后亲到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At least it didn't happen after a shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.58,0:04:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-够了  -我们把那叫做"湿身吻"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Enough. -We call that a splashdown.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.24,0:04:33.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  我去外面换  借过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it. I'm changing in the stall. Excuse me!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.20,0:04:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见那照片了  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I saw the picture, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.21,0:04:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手揽着她呢  表情还很猥亵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You had your arm around her with that humpy look you get.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.50,0:04:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚  你平时才不是那表情  我们吹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, that's not always how you look. We're over!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.34,0:04:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的想和你谈谈  帕特森夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I'd really like to talk to you, Mrs. Patterson,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.80,0:04:48.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看事情还有没有转机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}see if we can't turn this thing around.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.63,0:04:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有我电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, you've got my number.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.18,0:04:51.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.31,0:04:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了我俩没戏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said we are over.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.10,0:04:55.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以骑车出去转转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you go out for a nice bike ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.58,0:04:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是迪兰吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan again, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.02,0:05:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的男生就是笨得慌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some guys just do not know how to play it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.52,0:05:02.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  你干啥呢  -噢  对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Dad, what are you doing? -Oh, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.65,0:05:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是试试我的"滤汤器"[胡子]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just, uh, test-driving my new soup strainer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.24,0:05:06.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从万圣节杂物里翻出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I dug it out of the Halloween stuff
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.68,0:05:07.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看大家反应如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to see what people think.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.65,0:05:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们如果想做房地产咨询\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do people want their real estate advice...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.94,0:05:17.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是找"先锋派"还是"跟屁虫"呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from someone who leads or from someone who follows?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.95,0:05:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赌这胡子会再掀流行热潮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm betting these babies are coming back in a big way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.24,0:05:21.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低买  高卖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buy low, sell high.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.99,0:05:24.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家肯定都会说  他可是"高"人[嗑药过量]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People are gonna see this and say, "That guy's high."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.50,0:05:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry to bother you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.65,0:05:30.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在隔壁干活儿  弄破了主水管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're doing work next door and nicked a main,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.50,0:05:31.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以得把你家水停了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so we're gonna have to shut down your water.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.91,0:05:33.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Okay. No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.66,0:05:35.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会太久  如果你要方便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It shouldn't be too long. If you happen to need it,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.40,0:05:36.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外边有个流动厕所\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}there's a porta-potty out front.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.61,0:05:37.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢了  那个  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Thanks. Hey. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.47,0:05:40.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡子挺不错啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice mustache.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.47,0:05:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  你的也挺好  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, man. You too, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.66,0:05:46.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的也挺好  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"You too, brother."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.96,0:05:53.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  她是长女  15岁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley-She's the oldest. Fifteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.26,0:05:55.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是艾丽克斯  13岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then Alex is 13.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.28,0:05:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是我的小儿子  卢克  才11岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's my baby, Luke. He's 11.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.89,0:05:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不敢相信吧  -哇  他们真水灵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Can you believe it? -Oh, my God, they're gorgeous.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.40,0:06:02.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对啊  -和快乐男菲尔处得如何啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Yeah. -And things are still good with Phil the Thrill?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.24,0:06:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  很棒  他好我也好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Things are great. Great with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.49,0:06:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真为你开心  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so happy for you. Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.14,0:06:08.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真  我很开心你过得那么幸福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so-I'm so happy that you're happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.45,0:06:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Well, and you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.95,0:06:13.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的人生真是  -别别  接着说你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I mean, your life is -No, no, no-Let's talk about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.96,0:06:16.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -因为你是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Okay. -Because, you know, you're
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.84,0:06:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选择了当妈  你成了一位母亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You chose the mother. You're the mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.63,0:06:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感辣妈  妈妈  充满母爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The yummy mommy, mama, person
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.84,0:06:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都快把我的戒指压进我的肉里去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're kinda squeezing the ring right into my finger.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.00,0:06:27.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was I?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.26,0:06:29.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有点  -不好意思啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-A little. -I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.26,0:06:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我突然意识到  她在嫉妒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And just then, it hit me. She was jealous of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.81,0:06:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们之间一直存在竞争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, there'd always been a little bit of a competition between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.48,0:06:37.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次可是重大比拼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was more serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.94,0:06:40.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得我的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She was looking at my life as something...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.65,0:06:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她一直想要  却没得到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that she'd always wanted, but never had.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.82,0:06:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈谈你的职场生活啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So how's life in the trenches?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.32,0:06:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,23楼的那些混账老板\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You still got the bastards on the 23rd floor...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.79,0:06:50.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让所有员工都生不如死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}making life miserable for all the people actually doing the work.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.08,0:06:53.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是老样子呗  -有一点不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Same as ever, right? -One-one difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.01,0:06:55.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -我现在也是混账老板之一了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Mm-hmm? -I'm one of them bastards now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.28,0:06:58.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等下  你混上23楼啦  -是24楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Wait. You're on the 23rd floor? -I'm on the 24th floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.18,0:07:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哇  真牛啊  -也没啥啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Wow. That's insane. It's -It's no big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.14,0:07:04.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你没离职  上去的也许会是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, if you hadn't left, it probably would have been you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在路上开车啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was driving along this street.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.93,0:07:13.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些车就像这样停在路边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The cars were parked just like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.15,0:07:15.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  嘭的一下  他就突然撞到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And boom, out of nowhere, he hits me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.07,0:07:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以是他撞的你  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Okay, so, he-he cut you off? -Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.20,0:07:20.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦  -疯司机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Right. -A crazy driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.20,0:07:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我以前也像那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I used to be a little bit like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.29,0:07:23.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也许是因为莉莉吧  我也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know, maybe it's because of Lily,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.81,0:07:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开车会更加小心  顾及他人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I've definitely become more considerate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.54,0:07:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前都不让别人"插"在我前面  现在会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like, I used to never let people in, and now I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.97,0:07:32.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于懂那个隐喻[插]的意思了  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just now getting that metaphor. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.34,0:07:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有何高见  -有目击证人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-So, what do you think? -Were there any witnesses?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.90,0:07:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  只有曼尼  他当时在后座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, just Manny. He was in the back seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.24,0:07:39.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦  -发生得太突然了  眨眼间啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Okay. -It all happened so fast--Just like they say.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.99,0:07:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  行  接下来我们这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. All right. Well, this is what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.26,0:07:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先拍几张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll take a few pictures,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.26,0:07:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后坐下来起草一份声明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then we'll sit down and write a statement.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.05,0:07:46.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好  我去占个桌子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perfect. I'll go and get us a table.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.96,0:07:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行  -曼尼  你也来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-All right. -Manny, come.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.97,0:07:51.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-稍等  老妈  我鞋带散了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Uh, just a minute, Mom. I need to tie my shoe. -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.72,0:07:52.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Mitchell. -Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.79,0:07:55.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说话  听就好  责任在她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't talk. Listen. It was her fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.34,0:07:57.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  我没听清  -别看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I'm sorry. What? -Don't look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:59.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别傻愣着  照相啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do something. Take pictures.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.09,0:08:02.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你想要什么味道的蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny! What kind of cupcake do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.85,0:08:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  我不饿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, that's okay. I'm not hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.72,0:08:08.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失误了  她现在肯定起疑心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was a mistake. Now she'II know something's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.60,0:08:11.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Are you okay? -I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.73,0:08:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她撞的那个司机  她驾驶技术超烂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She cut that guy off. She's a terrible driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.02,0:08:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她是马路杀手  -慢点慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-She's a danger to us all. -Okay, wait. Now stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.90,0:08:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是说她的车是停着的  他撞了她吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought she said he was parked and then he cut her off.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.74,0:08:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时速100英里  你看所有的车都是停着的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody looks parked when you're going a hundred miles an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.16,0:08:24.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你之前为什么不说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, why didn't you speak up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.58,0:08:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她受不了别人批评她的驾驶技术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She can't take criticism about her driving.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.04,0:08:29.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有次一个老太太在十字路口冲她嚷嚷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Once an old lady yelled at her at a crosswalk.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.12,0:08:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就一直鸣喇叭  最后喇叭都不响了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She honked so long, the horn ran out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.27,0:08:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.04,0:08:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经透露得太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've said too much already.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.84,0:08:40.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you hearing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.31,0:08:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我靠  -得分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Aw, that's  - Point.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.89,0:08:48.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妨碍[术语]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hinder!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.41,0:08:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走狗屎运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lucky shot!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.60,0:08:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏结束  胜负分晓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is game and, I believe, match.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.36,0:08:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧好吧  你赢了  但也难怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, fine, you won. But, you know, what do you expect?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.61,0:08:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上半场的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For the first half of the game,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.81,0:09:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的更衣室事件  让我有些分心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was distracted by what happened in the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.11,0:09:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定不是因为我打得很赞吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you're sure it's not because I'm a fabulous racquetball player?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.95,0:09:07.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就一般水平  我心里一直纠结你碰了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're average. But I was a little thrown by you touching me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.26,0:09:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很让人反感  但你肯定不觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which is unnatural. Not to you, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.91,0:09:11.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定觉得很爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, to you it's like rocket fuel.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.30,0:09:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  是啊  基佬就"喜欢"到处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sure. When you're gay you just walk around
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.08,0:09:14.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用屁股碰别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}giving butt bumps to everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.04,0:09:16.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像"击掌"一样  不过是"亲臀"罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like a high five. It's a low two.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.05,0:09:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说  我要证明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I'm gonna prove
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.20,0:09:20.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输掉是因为分心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you won only because I was distracted.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.48,0:09:22.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在再打一场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna have a rematch right here, right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.84,0:09:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以你想再和我"大干一场"吗  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-So you want to go up against me again? -Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.85,0:09:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.89,0:09:28.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.68,0:09:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你知道那车祸责任在歌洛莉亚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Dad. Uh, did you know that the accident was Gloria's fault?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.60,0:09:33.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我虽然当时不在场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. I mean, I wasn't there,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.29,0:09:34.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但歌洛莉亚是个烂司机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but she's a horrible driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.27,0:09:35.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要撞了10辆车  我也不吃惊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If she hit 10 cars, I wouldn't be surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.98,0:09:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你既然知道是她的责任  为什么把我扯进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you knew it was her fault, why did you get me involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.15,0:09:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为总得有人告诉她她错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because someone has to tell her she's in the wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.15,0:09:41.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说总比我说好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and better you than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.06,0:09:42.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊  我还天真地以为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's great. Here I am thinking
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.72,0:09:44.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸开始尊重我律师的职业了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that my dad actually respects me as a lawyer,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.51,0:09:46.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你只是把我往火坑里推\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and really you're just throwing me to the wolves.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.41,0:09:47.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不能两种心思都有吗  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Can't it be both? -Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.63,0:09:49.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你就一点没觉得悲哀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, it doesn't bother you in the least...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.70,0:09:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的同性恋儿子是唯一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that your gay son is the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.15,0:09:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢直面你老婆的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}tough enough to stand up to your wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.54,0:09:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油搞定吧伙计  回见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go get 'em, Rocky. See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.54,0:09:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老爸和我在更衣室"屁屁碰"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your father and I had a moon landing in the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.14,0:09:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有病啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.42,0:10:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  有没有在处对象啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What about you? Do you ever get serious with anyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.26,0:10:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  目前没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure. Oh, no. Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.13,0:10:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你会有的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey, you will.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.99,0:10:08.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不希望有  现在很好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, I hope not. It's-It's fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.75,0:10:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我在等电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I'm just-I'm waiting for some news.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.75,0:10:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么电话  -我去应聘了一个法国的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-What news? -I'm-I'm up for the Paris job.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.09,0:10:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国际分公司的头头吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The-The head of the international division?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.80,0:10:18.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那也太牛了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's-That's-That's crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.80,0:10:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没啦  我应该聘不上的  聘上当然好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, no. I mean, I'll never get it, but it'd be great...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.01,0:10:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我情夫之一在巴黎呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause one of my lovers lives in Paris.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.36,0:10:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  我都不知道那句话中哪个词更震撼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. I-I don't know what jumps out of that sentence more-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.77,0:10:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是"情夫"又是"之一"的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, "Lovers" Or "One of."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.81,0:10:31.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我单身嘛  就是要这样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm single. I mean, it's kinda what you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.69,0:10:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯哼  -有个在巴黎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Uh-huh. -I have one in Paris.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.07,0:10:38.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴黎  纽约  迈阿密各有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I have Paris, New York, Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.90,0:10:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实还有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a fourth one.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.95,0:10:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我都忘了我的情夫了  真要命  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I'm forgetting one lover. I'm forgetting one lover. -Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.38,0:10:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我把冰箱下面的散热器打扫了下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Last night I vacuumed the radiator thingy under the fridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.75,0:10:47.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太沾灰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, it collects the dust.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.47,0:10:49.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时就该清理的  我也忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cause you should, and I don't. So-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.54,0:10:52.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  为我祈祷吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hey, hold on. Cross your fingers.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.64,0:10:54.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.72,0:10:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到瓦莱丽会得到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The thought of Valerie getting the one job
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.09,0:10:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份大家都想要的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in the whole company that everyone coveted
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.52,0:11:00.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心里可不怎么"情"愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}well, I wasn't a "Lover" Of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.02,0:11:01.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  嗯  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Okay, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.99,0:11:04.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.38,0:11:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还没定呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, they haven't made a decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.99,0:11:09.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说回头再告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're-they're gonna tell me later on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.50,0:11:12.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们不是这么说的吧 -是啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's not what they said, is it? - Uh, yeah, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.10,0:11:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  瓦莱丽  我不是外人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Valerie, come on. It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.29,0:11:15.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友就该相互支持\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are friends for,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.32,0:11:17.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再坏的事情都可以跟我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if not to be there for you when you get bad news?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.50,0:11:20.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我聘上了 -天呐  啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I got it. -Oh, my God. Aaah!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.54,0:11:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是欧洲的头儿啦  -酒店头儿啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm the head of Europe. - Well, you know, for the hotel-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.47,0:11:27.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是整个欧洲  -差不多啦  差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Not the continent. - Kind of though. Kind of.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.79,0:11:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一开始为什么不告诉我呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why didn't you tell me when you first heard?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.67,0:11:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  因为  那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, 'cause, you know
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.35,0:11:35.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我才恍然大悟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's when it really hit me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.98,0:11:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦莱丽才不嫉妒我  她可怜我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Valerie wasn't jealous of me. She pitied me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.73,0:11:41.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时有点想把她带回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And part of me wanted to take her back to the house...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.33,0:11:43.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她看看我有而她没有的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and show her everything she was missing...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.07,0:11:47.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真悲哀  没有孩子  没有老公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in her sad, childless, husbandless life.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.49,0:11:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道"高风亮节"四个字儿咋写\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But there's a little thing called "Taking the high road."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.37,0:11:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下你到我家喝杯茶呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you come by and meet everybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.39,0:11:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  那挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sure. That'd be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.75,0:11:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  艾丽克斯就是个小天才啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I mean, Alex is just a genius,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.92,0:12:00.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉真是女大十八变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Haley is turning into this beautiful young woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.13,0:12:03.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她让我懂得了做母亲... -旧金山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-and it makes me realize that motherhood is -San Francisco.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.97,0:12:06.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-最重要的是  -我第四个情人  在旧金山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The most important  - That was my fourth lover. San Francisco.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.47,0:12:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想不起来我今晚肯定睡不着  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It would have kept me up all night. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.57,0:12:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  快看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, look.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.45,0:12:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会儿  小家伙  我去上趟厕所\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just a sec, buddy. I'm on my way out to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.01,0:12:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  昨晚奥布里一家开了个巨型派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Check it out. The Aubreys had this huge party last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.84,0:12:18.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓶子都归我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we got all these bottles to recycle.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.58,0:12:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-恭喜  -野格酒是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Great. -What's Jegermeister?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.79,0:12:25.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...在童话故事里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you know how in a fairy tale...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.00,0:12:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会有种让公主睡着的药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}there's always a potion that makes the princess fall asleep,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.91,0:12:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后男生们就去亲她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then the guys start kissing her?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.41,0:12:33.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野格酒也差不多  不同的是你醒来不是在城堡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, this is like that, except you don't wake up in a castle,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.09,0:12:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是在兄弟会的房子  然后从此臭名远扬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you wake up in a frat house with a bad reputation.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.43,0:12:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.82,0:13:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  都洒出来了啦  -擦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, you're spilling it! - Aw, crud.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.36,0:13:04.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}God
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.49,0:13:06.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耗子  好恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gross! A rat!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.53,0:13:07.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.31,0:13:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着  来了来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hang on. I'm coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.85,0:13:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿了我的一样东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I believe you have something that belongs to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.94,0:13:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.94,0:13:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在网上说了让你滚远点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought I I.M.'ed you to stay away.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.07,0:13:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗷  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.70,0:13:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  迪兰  迪迪仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello? Dylan? D-Money?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.37,0:13:33.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老兄  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy! Hey, buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.71,0:13:36.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  左邻右舍们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, friendly neighbors!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.54,0:13:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求帮忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Little help?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.80,0:13:40.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.04,0:13:41.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前怎么没想到你爱我啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you should have thought about that...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.26,0:13:43.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然带莎伦·妮可利那个小婊子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}before you took that skank Sharon Nicolini
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.29,0:13:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看安妮·海瑟薇的电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to an Anne Hathaway movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.97,0:13:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没带她去  只是碰巧遇到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't take her. She was just there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.59,0:13:50.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就一个人去看安妮·海瑟薇的电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you were just there by yourself at an Anne Hathaway movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.43,0:13:51.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忽悠我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think so!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.65,0:13:54.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我很喜欢她的电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yeah. I like her movies.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.31,0:13:57.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个出色的女人  求求你  别闹了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's every woman. Come on. Let's not fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.27,0:14:01.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下来  像两个不成熟的成年人那样谈谈吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's just discuss this like two un-immature adults.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.70,0:14:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  帕特森太太\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello? Mrs. Patterson.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.28,0:14:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  我正等你电话呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. I've been waiting for your call.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.37,0:14:13.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我们可不可以再仔细谈一谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Uh, is there any chance that maybe we could talk a little bit-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.58,0:14:16.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没没没  挺好的  真挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no. Now's perfect. That's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.12,0:14:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我这边吵  等我把办公室门关上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I couldn't hear you. Let me just close my office door.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.71,0:14:22.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  能听清了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There we go. Much, much better.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.17,0:14:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再来回顾一下车祸的情形吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Maybe, uh, we should go over the accident one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.30,0:14:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一丝不"狗"地分析  你真是个好律师啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Put the dogs on a row. You're such a good lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.54,0:14:33.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[习语Put the ducks in a row有条不紊  一丝不苟\NGloria使用错误]
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.93,0:14:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想确保\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, I just wanna make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.27,0:14:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要搞清楚真实的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we're 100% clear on exactly what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.52,0:14:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经很清楚了啊  我跟你说了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we're clear. I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.51,0:14:40.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你不信我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? You don't believe me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.32,0:14:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  没  我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.32,0:14:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道  有时候会漏掉一些细节嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, sometimes you can forget tiny details.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.95,0:14:50.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  有没有可能  是你开太快了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like, is it possible, maybe, uh, you were driving too fast?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.00,0:14:52.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁说我开太快了 -对  谁说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Who said I was driving fast? -Yeah, who?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.16,0:14:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着街上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just-I'm looking at the street,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.04,0:14:57.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想  如果你开得很快的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm thinking if you were driving a little fast,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.42,0:14:58.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's possible that maybe you
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.18,0:15:01.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没看见那车  -你也跟他们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- didn't see the car - You're like everyone else, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.00,0:15:02.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是我们拉丁人的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You blame the Latino driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.98,0:15:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们老家  总是把错都推给拉丁司机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where I come from, they always blame the Latino driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.64,0:15:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们老家不是所有司机都是拉丁司机吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where you come from, isn't everybody a Latino driver?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.20,0:15:11.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼  你跟他说 -没法说啊  我吃蛋糕呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Manny, tell him. - I can't 'cause I have a cupcake in my mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.67,0:15:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  别拿蛋糕当挡箭牌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on. Don't blame your cupcake.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.84,0:15:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你也觉得是我的错吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? You think I'm guilty too?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.88,0:15:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没啦  -得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.88,0:15:20.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要你做我的律师了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't need you as a lawyer anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.43,0:15:23.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩不是觉得我是个烂司机吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if you two think I'm such a bad driver,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.18,0:15:25.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们走回家好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're safer walking home.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.18,0:15:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Chao.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.02,0:15:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就这儿了 -真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Here it is. - It's really cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.69,0:15:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我们都很以此为豪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. We're pretty proud of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:35.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的烂CD  拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's your stupid CDs...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.02,0:15:38.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的烂衣服  还有狗屎诗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and your clothes and your poems!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.36,0:15:40.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你敢扔试试  -我就敢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't you do it! - Oh, I'm doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.90,0:15:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  停手  你在干啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, stop it. What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.88,0:15:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,折磨我的心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tearing out my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.45,0:15:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你去让莎伦·妮可利给你个吻痕啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, why don't you go get a hickey from Sharon Nicolini?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.62,0:15:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我吉他带子勒的  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's from my guitar strap, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.25,0:15:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-噢  谢谢你提醒我扔吉他  -那是我女儿海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Oh, thanks for reminding me. -That's my daughter Haley
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.67,0:15:56.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她男朋友  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And her boyfriend, Dylan, um
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.55,0:15:58.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉刷的颜色真漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a nice color.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.61,0:16:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩  是这样的  我家平时不这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Um, listen. This is not normal,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.67,0:16:04.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这么  靠  是酒的气味吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with all that, nor-nor is that liquor smell.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.55,0:16:07.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  宝贝  天  卢克  这是咋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, honey? Oh, my God. Luke, what is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.72,0:16:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野格酒  老爸说它可以让女生更容易亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jegermeister. Dad says it makes girls easier to kiss.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.13,0:16:13.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那地毯是怎么回事 -出了点小意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What happened to the rug? - I had an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.77,0:16:15.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  艾丽克斯  你又在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Alex, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.35,0:16:17.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在追杀一只耗子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm trying to kill a rat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.53,0:16:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.06,0:16:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎伦在帮我给你挑生日礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sharon was helping me buy you a birthday present.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.23,0:16:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不明白吗  我爱的是你的屁股蛋蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you get it? I love your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.32,0:16:27.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...我  我快迟了  得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-You know, I-I-I'm late and I should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.01,0:16:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  我知道  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-I know. I know. -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.57,0:16:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的确是有点乱糟糟的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it seems like things have gotten a little wonky around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.24,0:16:33.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道菲尔上哪儿了  他肯定...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know where Phil is. He's definitely-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.83,0:16:37.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Alex
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.87,0:16:39.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.27,0:16:40.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他去外面上厕所了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He went outside to go to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.09,0:16:46.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时真不这样的  靠  刺瞎我的眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's... not usually like this. Oh, gross.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.05,0:16:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们结婚吧  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let's just get married. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.60,0:16:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会后悔的  帕特森太太\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You will not regret this decision, Mrs. Patterson.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.64,0:16:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'll tell you what.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.39,0:16:56.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请你到我家来庆祝下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna have you over to our little house to celebrate.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.73,0:16:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吗  嗯  拜拜  -有空再来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay? Okay, bye-bye. - You should come back again-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.52,0:17:01.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有空就来  -克莱尔  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- sometime, when you get a break - Claire! Claire!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.53,0:17:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你  你干啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, what are you-what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.15,0:17:06.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忙着谈业务呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just concluding a little business.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.05,0:17:07.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便补一句  很顺利噢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Very successfully, I might add.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.86,0:17:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-宝贝  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Honey - Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.53,0:17:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -你不是瓦莱丽嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi. - Is that Valerie?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.82,0:17:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯  -哇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Wow!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.78,0:17:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真漂亮  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You look fantastic. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.41,0:17:16.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来来  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come here. Get over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.62,0:17:18.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.71,0:17:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们多久没见了  -很久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How long has it been? - A long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.88,0:17:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my goodness.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.62,0:17:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没办法触到你  -是有点难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, I can't touch you. Okay. - A little bit difficult.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.82,0:17:25.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔车相望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gulf divides us, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.38,0:17:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-见到你真好  -可不是嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So nice to see you. - It's great to see you though
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.34,0:17:28.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.59,0:17:30.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走了啊  -有空来坐坐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, then. - Thanks for coming by.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.47,0:17:31.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢招待  -拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's such a pleasure. - Bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.89,0:17:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有空常来啊  -你家真漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks for stopping by. - You have a beautiful family.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.72,0:17:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她真漂亮  是吧  -你脸上是什么玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She looks great, doesn't she? - What is on your face?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.36,0:17:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次  哪怕一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time! Once!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.44,0:17:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带个客人回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time I bring somebody home...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.48,0:17:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想刺激一下别人  结果呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who I want to impress, and what do I find?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.86,0:17:51.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个全身酒味的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A bunch of booze-drenched hill people...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.82,0:17:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着内裤到处走  一个追耗子的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just sitting around in their underwear and-and chasing rats...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.53,0:17:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个在楼梯口就搞起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and fornicating in the stairwell.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.70,0:17:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能插句话吗  -不准插  超级玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I say something? - No. No, you can't, Mario.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.79,0:18:01.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不用说了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There is nothing left to say but thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.32,0:18:03.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you all.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.60,0:18:17.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早说了你打不过我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told you I'd win.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.35,0:18:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没话可说了吧  神球手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not talking so much now, are you, hotshot?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.56,0:18:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你洗澡洗个爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hope you enjoy that nice, hot shower,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.44,0:18:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但15比7的耻辱你是洗不掉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's not gonna wash away the shame of that 15-7 beatdown.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.07,0:18:30.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真该看看你当时的表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should have seen the look on your face...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.11,0:18:32.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球和墙亲密接触那瞬间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when that drop shot just kissed the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.11,0:18:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  湿身吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah. Okay, splashdown.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.45,0:18:36.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又弄到我了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got me again. Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.99,0:18:38.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我这传统直男情何以堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Make the uptight straight guy all embarrassed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.08,0:18:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我还就真无所谓了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Except for one thing -doesn't even bother me anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.37,0:18:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以一直这样碰  来  再碰一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could do this all day. Here, another one for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.54,0:18:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多来几次啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe a couple of 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.75,0:18:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我发现后面有个桑拿哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, I just noticed a sauna back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.42,0:18:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们要冲进去吗  -像赶着投胎那样冲进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-How big of a hurry are we in? -Biggest hurry of your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.59,0:18:54.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借过  借过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Scuse me. 'Scuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.84,0:18:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果注定了要被困住[进退两难]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if you're going to be stranded,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.85,0:18:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如就被困在蛋糕店吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}might as well be in a place full of cupcakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.89,0:19:00.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你吃得差不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think you need any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.77,0:19:04.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. I'm sorry, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.69,0:19:08.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  我喜欢为自己抗辩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's true. I am a defensive driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.15,0:19:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是说你喜欢抗辩...  -我知道自己什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-You mean you're defensive about -I know what I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.41,0:19:16.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我不喜欢大家凭空就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just that I don't like when people just assume
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.40,0:19:18.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我是个烂司机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'm a bad driver.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.43,0:19:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我是要  负那么一点点责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe it was just, like, a little bit my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.27,0:19:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能承认  挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm glad you can admit that, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.78,0:19:26.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是想让你当我的律师  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm still gonna need you as my lawyer, Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.51,0:19:28.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么  -因为眼前的惨剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Why?  -Because this one
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.58,0:19:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不关我的事  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was not my fault, I promise you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.47,0:19:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来那巨响是这个啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what that sound was.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.88,0:19:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是这蛋糕招牌的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was the big cupcake.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.86,0:19:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直难以置信  老妈疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was unreal. Mom was crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.80,0:19:41.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好怕怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.95,0:19:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我了解你妈这个人  她没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look. I know your mom pretty well. She's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.87,0:19:48.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜她现在在努力控制情绪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd be willing to bet she's just composing herself,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.39,0:19:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在公园里静静散步呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}taking a nice, long, peaceful walk in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.59,0:20:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.55,0:20:07.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会儿我只想回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At that moment all I wanted was to be with my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.43,0:20:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但回去肯定要想办法道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But of course, that meant finding a way to apologize...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.02,0:20:13.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说话太重  伤了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to the people that I had belittled and rejected.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.10,0:20:16.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你乱说啥呢  那歌多好听啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you are so crazy. That song totally rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.23,0:20:18.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  你才乱说呢  -明明很有道理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Daddy, you're crazy. -Crazy right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.69,0:20:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  宝贝  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Hey, honey. -Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.03,0:20:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老妈  来坐啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mom. Come on. Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.61,0:20:22.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  老爸  烂透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, seriously, Dad. It's lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.85,0:20:24.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  卢克  不烂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, Luke. It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.86,0:20:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸上有芥末还是什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got some mustard or something on your face.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.91,0:20:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于音乐我还是懂点的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I know a little bit about music.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.55,0:20:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读大学时我还当过DJ呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was a DJ in college.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.70,0:20:32.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有一档在黄金时间播放的节目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had my own show in the coveted time slot.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.33,0:20:34.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《与邓菲一起等待黎明》  -真的假的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Daybreak with Dunphy. -Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.47,0:20:37.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗你干啥  我播瑞克·艾斯里的歌哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm not kidding you. And I played Rick Astley.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.19,0:20:39.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  你囧死我了  -绝不放弃  卢克  跟着唱啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Dad, that's embarrassing. -Never gonna give, Sing it, Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.90,0:20:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们原本大可以记恨我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They could have been petty.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.90,0:20:44.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们大可以为难我  但他们没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They really could have made me pay, but they didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.94,0:20:46.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱死他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Never loved 'em more.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.94,0:20:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为毛瓦莱丽就看不到他们的这一面呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why the hell couldn't Valerie have seen them like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.27,0:21:02.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.93,0:21:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  邓菲先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mr. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.23,0:21:05.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.02,0:21:08.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉又跟我闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Haley and I got into another fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.06,0:21:17.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Say Anything直译为"随便说点什么吧"\N也是一部电影名《情到深处》\N剧中男主角高举收音机在喜欢的女孩窗前等候]
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.60,0:21:12.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《情到深处》的场景呀[说点什么吧]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Say Anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.31,0:21:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, good morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.73,0:21:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  情到深处[随便说点什么]  -报纸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-No. Say Anything. -Newspaper.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.32,0:21:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  迪兰  《情到深处》  经典电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Dylan. Say Anything. Clutch movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.86,0:21:23.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经典电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Clutch movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.16,0:21:26.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她应该要过几个小时才醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She probably won't be up for a couple hours still.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.49,0:21:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  手机没多重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's okay. It's not that heavy.

