[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.54,0:03:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.54,0:03:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.54,0:03:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季 第十三集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.40,0:00:03.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人会变吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can people change?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.44,0:00:05.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  这是个很难回答的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's a- that is a tough one,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.36,0:00:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我认为  是的  人会变的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I would say yes. People can change.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.66,0:00:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坚信这点  至死不变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what I believe anyway, and I will till the day I die.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.83,0:00:15.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你自相矛盾了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You do realize you're proving the exact opposite of your point?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.46,0:00:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  她就变了  她以前从不反驳我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? She's changed. She used to be very supportive of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:21.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.57,0:00:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.58,0:00:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么这么大声  -我耳朵快被吵爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ow! Ow! Why is it so loud? - My ears are bleeding!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.03,0:00:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么这么大声  -不知道  快关掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why is it so loud? - I don't know! Make it stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.84,0:00:35.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚在客厅装了一套超棒的家庭影院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just installed a sweet home theater system in the family room.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.85,0:00:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是克莱尔对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The, um- the trouble is Claire struggles...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.68,0:00:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何高科技产品都一窍不通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with technology of any kind.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.19,0:00:45.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是遥控器  手机  电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, remotes, cell phones, computers.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.70,0:00:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  你看到我那件蓝色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, have you seen my blue-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.90,0:00:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  邓菲太太  -你好  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Mrs. Dunphy. - Oh, hey, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.53,0:00:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我能看见你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know I can see you, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.30,0:00:57.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我还真不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I did not know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.70,0:01:01.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉在浴室  她一会儿就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley's just in the bathroom. She'll be back in just a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.12,0:01:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.08,0:01:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你刚才把遥控器对着哪  -对着电视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where were you pointing it? - At the TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.38,0:01:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.00,0:01:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  不  我不是在笑你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey- Uh, no. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.56,0:01:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这是  这是家庭影院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's-It's a home theater.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.42,0:01:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢  我看电视的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, so I can't point it at the TV
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.34,0:01:13.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不应该把遥控器对着电视吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I want to watch the TV?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.81,0:01:15.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你应该对着接收器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You point it at the receiver.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.66,0:01:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是接收器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's a receiver?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.93,0:01:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧  你把家庭影院想象成人的身体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, imagine our home theater system is a human body.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.02,0:01:23.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接收器就相当于大脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So then the receiver is the brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.98,0:01:26.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-电视就是人脸  -我知道你是哪部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The TV is the face. - I know what part you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.15,0:01:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他对他妻子说  你不再爱我了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So he says to his wife, "you don't love me anymore?"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.49,0:01:32.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的心脏受到了重创\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His heart- boom!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.36,0:01:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心脏搭桥手术白做了  瓣膜撕裂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Quadruple bypass. Blown a valve.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.63,0:01:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  看看这是谁  -嗨  是你啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey! Look who it is. - Hey. There he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.71,0:01:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好巧哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What a coinkydink.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.81,0:01:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在给歌洛莉亚买花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just getting some flowers for Gloria
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.41,0:01:40.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢她临时照顾莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for babysitting Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.42,0:01:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我帮忙带给她吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want me to take 'em to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.37,0:01:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  但是我给她准备的爆笑卡片在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would, but I have the most hilarious card for her at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.35,0:01:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面是一个像安东尼奥·班德拉斯那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's- It's a hunky Antonio Banderas type
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.93,0:01:48.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着平角短裤的性感熟男\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in silk boxers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.12,0:01:51.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面写着  谢谢昨夜春宵一场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And on the inside, it says, "thank you for last noche,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.36,0:01:54.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是裤子寻不着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I can't find my pantalones."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.52,0:01:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我说的不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not doing it justice, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.56,0:02:00.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好  我是卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. I'm Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.45,0:02:02.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  抱歉  各位  这是卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, geez. I'm sorry. Guys, this is Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.51,0:02:07.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是  他是我儿子的朋友  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's a... friend of my son's. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.00,0:02:10.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  斯科特  达尔  雨果和小短\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is, uh, Scotty, Dale, Hugo and Shorty.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.10,0:02:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到你们很高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's nice to meet you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:13.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们现在这样看上去像泽西男孩里的一幕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys look like a scene out of Jersey Boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.16,0:02:21.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哎呀你看上去真帅  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay! So handsome! - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.38,0:02:24.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  你涂了须后水吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, are you wearing aftershave?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.92,0:02:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  为了我的约会对象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, for my date.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.60,0:02:29.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这将是她第一次闻到我的雄性气息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This will be the first time she will ever smell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.37,0:02:30.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫惠特妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Her name is Whitney.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.72,0:02:33.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在网上读书俱乐部认识她的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I met her in an online book club.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.21,0:02:35.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都喜欢和吸血鬼有关的小说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We both like vampire fiction...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.21,0:02:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是他们永生的浪漫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the romance of eternal life.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.25,0:02:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼有约会对象这件事实在是太可爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think it's adorable that Manny has a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.00,0:02:42.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他甚至选好了午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He even picked out the lunch menu-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.17,0:02:44.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤起司三明治和番茄浓汤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}grilled-cheese sandwich and tomato soup.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.38,0:02:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选番茄浓汤是因为  它看上去像血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tomato soup because, you know, the tomato soup is like the blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.39,0:02:49.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而吸血鬼喜欢吸血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the vampires like to eat the blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.72,0:02:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他希望我带他们出去吃冰激凌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then he wants me to take them out for ice cream,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.31,0:02:54.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为曼尼喜欢吃冰激凌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}well, because Manny likes ice cream.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.74,0:02:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是她来了  如果约会进行顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that must be her. If this goes well,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.41,0:02:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以提前撤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you don't need to stick around.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.73,0:03:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是惠特妮  我是来见曼尼的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. I'm Whitney. I'm here for Manny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.58,0:03:25.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧这玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See how that works?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.48,0:03:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了小甜心  久等了他爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, sweetie. Sorry, Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.03,0:03:28.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.65,0:03:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和莉莉刚刚在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were just- me and Lily were just using the time...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.53,0:03:32.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研究这个车的声控系统怎么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to figure out how to use the car's voice-command thingy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.67,0:03:34.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  瞧好了  你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Here. Check it out. Watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.74,0:03:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CD播放器  下一首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}CD player. Next track.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.34,0:03:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请讲指令  -不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Say a command. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.34,0:03:44.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CD播放器  下一首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}CD player. Next track.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.79,0:03:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空调已开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Air conditioner on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.84,0:03:47.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.26,0:03:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比你姐还不擅长用这些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're worse than your sister with this kind of stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.46,0:03:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好莉莉没有弹射座椅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a good thing Lily doesn't have an ejector seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.60,0:03:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了你知道吗  我碰到你爸和他朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, guess what. I ran into your dad and some of his friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.27,0:03:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -是的  而且\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, really? - Yeah. And get this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.82,0:04:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他介绍我的时候  说我是你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He, uh- He referred to me as "a friend of my son."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.70,0:04:03.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Seriously? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.67,0:04:05.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样有点不尊重你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's a little disrespectful to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.89,0:04:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没有觉得自己被冒犯了  -但我有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I wasn't offended by it. - Well- I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.40,0:04:12.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会说菲尔是克莱尔的朋友吗  不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, would he refer to Phil as "a friend of Claire's"? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.98,0:04:14.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听过他说菲尔一些更不好听的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've heard him call Phil a lot worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.62,0:04:16.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想这件事了  就当我没说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just let it pass. I should have never said anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.98,0:04:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能就这么算了  他得知道这样不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not letting it pass. He needs to know that's not okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.99,0:04:21.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他不喜欢这样  他以后就别出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if he doesn't like it, he knows where he can go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.12,0:04:23.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-输入目的地  -去死[地狱]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Enter destination. - Hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.61,0:04:26.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-墨西哥菜  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mexican food. - Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.26,0:04:29.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是25岁左右出柜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I came out of the closet in my mid-20s.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.76,0:04:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我爸说了三次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had to actually come out to my dad three times...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.22,0:04:34.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才终于接受了这个事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}before he finally acknowledged it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.56,0:04:36.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定他是不是希望他听错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not sure if maybe he was hoping he heard it wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.89,0:04:41.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如他希望我说的是  爸  我是"童心恋"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like I had said, "Dad, I'm gray."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.36,0:04:43.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我的父母  他们一直都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And my parents, they always just knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.23,0:04:45.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈说她生我的时候用了36个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My mother says labor with me took 36 hours...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.36,0:04:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为从她肚子出来时我就像这样  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because I came out of the womb like this- "Hello!"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.45,0:04:50.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不该再吃煎饼卷了  -嗨  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I gotta lay off these cannolis. - Hey, dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.67,0:04:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  你们认识我儿子吧  米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell. Hey, you guys know my son, Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.58,0:04:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨米奇  最近好吗  -嗨米奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Mitch, how they hangin'? - Hey, Mitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.70,0:04:56.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  哟  这件大衣不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey, hey. That's a great coat.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:04:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在哪儿买的  -不知道  别人送的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where'd you get that? - I don't know. It was a gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.93,0:05:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  面料是小山羊皮还是仿麂皮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? What is it- suede, microsuede?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.68,0:05:05.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是某种小羊皮吧  摸上去很软\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some kind of lambskin? It's very soft, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.78,0:05:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.73,0:05:12.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那个  我能和你谈谈吗  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, can I talk to you for a second? - Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.15,0:05:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  见到你很高兴  -很快回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks. Good seeing you. - Be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.91,0:05:16.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.03,0:05:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介绍小卡的时候  说他是我的朋友吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, "a friend of my son"? That's how you introduce Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.12,0:05:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里就是为了说这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why you came here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.32,0:05:22.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你也太侮辱人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, it's just more than a little insulting.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡和我在一起5年了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam and I have been together for five years.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.42,0:05:25.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有一个女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We- We have a daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.42,0:05:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at these guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.50,0:05:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们看上去好像来自十九世纪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They look like they came out of the 1800s.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.54,0:05:30.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到雨果了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You see Hugo over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.73,0:05:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&} [桑卡是世界上最早的去咖啡因咖啡之一]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.73,0:05:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完午餐后  他点了一杯桑卡咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}After lunch, he ordered a Sanka.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.05,0:05:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是他们无法接受同性恋  是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, they're not the ones that are uncomfortable with this. You are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.74,0:05:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从未真正接受过我是同性恋这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've never been completely accepting of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.76,0:05:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我都有家庭了  再说什么都迟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And now that I have a family, it's getting a little old.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.88,0:05:42.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人无法理解同性恋这码事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These guys don't understand the gay thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.81,0:05:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要把气氛搞僵呢  我这么想而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why create an awkward situation? That's all I'm saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.81,0:05:46.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's weird,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.45,0:05:49.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你朋友小短就是"基味十足"的同性恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because your friend Shorty there- gay as they come.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.98,0:05:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在开玩笑吧  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You gotta be kiddin'.  - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.99,0:05:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的"基达"从没出过错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My gaydar is never wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.39,0:05:57.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它现在正叮铃作响  就像在澡堂一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it is pinging like we're at a bathhouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.69,0:05:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你在说什么吗  他以前结过婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about- gay? The guy used to be married.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.53,0:06:01.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  难道那就...艾尔顿·约翰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that makes- So did Elton John,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.21,0:06:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[均为隐瞒自己同性恋身份的名人]
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.37,0:06:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅尔夫·格里芬和科尔·波特也结过婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Merv Griffin, Cole Porter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.16,0:06:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你肯定搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? Listen. You couldn't be more wrong about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.32,0:06:09.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  爸爸  你才搞错过很多事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Dad. You could not be more wrong- about a lot of things.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.25,0:06:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-见到你们很高兴  -慢走  小伙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Good seeing you guys. - You take care, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.67,0:06:13.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那件大衣很不错  -好  回见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's a great coat. - Yeah, later.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.21,0:06:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叮铃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ping!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.67,0:06:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔·邓菲  -嗨  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil Dunphy. - Hey, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.52,0:06:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -听着  我这儿有很多妈妈们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. - Listen, I've got a bunch of moms over here...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.77,0:06:30.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们都想看选秀比赛的DVD\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who wanna watch the talent show DVD,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.82,0:06:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我调不出声音来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I can't get the sound to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.32,0:06:35.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有图像吗  -有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is there a picture? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.40,0:06:38.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  你是不是像每次受挫的时候那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Be honest. Did you do that thing where you get frustrated...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.16,0:06:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始狂按各种按键了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you start pressing all the buttons?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.16,0:06:41.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.20,0:06:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得菲尔在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a theory that Phil installs...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.25,0:06:44.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装那些操作复杂的要死的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}overly complicated things in the house...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是希望把我当小孩训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just so he has an excuse to talk to me like a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.33,0:06:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个月是自动调温器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Last month, it was the thermostat.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.13,0:06:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪花按键降降温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The snowflake button makes it cold, cold, cold
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.61,0:06:58.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温度设置恒恒温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Set temperature" makes it hold, hold, hold
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.33,0:07:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小火苗按键升升温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The little flame makes it hot
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.49,0:07:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太丢人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is so humiliating.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.25,0:07:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I am sorry. - It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.09,0:07:10.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在网上给人感觉很成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just seemed so mature online.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.09,0:07:14.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我怎么会这么傻  -你不傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How could I be so stupid? - You're not stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.59,0:07:17.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不跟着感觉抓住恋爱的机会才叫傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Stupid" is not following your heart and taking a chance on love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.81,0:07:21.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  哪个11岁小孩能说出这样的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, what kind of 11-year-old talks like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.35,0:07:22.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼内心很成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's an old soul.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.06,0:07:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  手帕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Use my handkerchief.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.81,0:07:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白我的意思了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You see what I mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.82,0:07:30.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会孤老终死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll just be alone for the rest of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.03,0:07:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不过没关系了  -不要这样说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And that's okay. - No, don't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.99,0:07:36.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们国家  有一句谚语是这么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In my country, there's a saying that means...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.91,0:07:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱就在"转角"处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Love is just around the corner."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.66,0:07:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老家附近有很多妓女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I come from a neighborhood with a lot of prostitutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.21,0:07:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许对你来说是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.05,0:07:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都会有很多男人围着你转吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, men must throw themselves at you every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.04,0:07:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以的  只要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They'II do the same for you if you just-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.59,0:07:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要怎样  献身吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just what? Put out?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.27,0:07:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  只要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Just-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.39,0:07:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涂点唇彩  弄弄头发  穿上托文胸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like, the lipstick, the hair, push-up bra. You know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.53,0:08:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有用吗  我永远不会变得和你一样漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's it matter? I'm never gonna be as pretty as you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.22,0:08:03.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我也是下了一番功夫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, believe me, this takes a lot of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.43,0:08:05.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是需要找到你的内在美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just need to find your inner beauty.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.52,0:08:08.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的内在美被你的不安全感掩盖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's hiding beneath a mask of insecurity.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.94,0:08:10.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有点吓到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, he's starting to freak me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.98,0:08:12.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  自己去玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, go play.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.99,0:08:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  这花看上去怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, how do these look to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.08,0:08:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看上去像是快要谢了  -对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Like they're dying. - I know. Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.24,0:08:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是这么对那个花商说的  他说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said something to the florist. He said,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.69,0:08:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要担心  它们会变好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Don't worry about it. They're gonna come back."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.42,0:08:26.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们没有变好  它们更蔫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're not coming back. They've crossed to the other side.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.59,0:08:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你蛮搞笑的  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You are a funny man. - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.63,0:08:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能被这些花搞得心烦气躁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're completely bothered by the flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.63,0:08:33.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我爸爸说你是我的朋友的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But when my father introduces you as "a friend of my son,"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.47,0:08:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一点儿也没有觉得困扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}doesn't faze you in the least.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.04,0:08:36.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那个花商把我当成了一个傻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because the florist played me for a fool.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.57,0:08:39.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸没有刻意伤害我  他就是那样的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your dad didn't mean any harm. He's just being who he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.26,0:08:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我在东部的法学院上学的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I was back East in law school,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.74,0:08:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸曾经每周六下午六点都打电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my dad used to call me every Saturday at 6:00 p.M.,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.75,0:08:46.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大家都准备出去玩之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}before people would go out,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.19,0:08:48.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了查查勤  了解一下近况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just to, you know, check in, catch up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.36,0:08:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  应该是第二年的圣诞节吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then, I think, the Christmas of my second year,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于鼓起勇气向他出柜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I finally got up the courage to tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.78,0:09:02.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  我  我基本上只和我妈说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}After that, I-I... pretty much just talked to my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.75,0:09:04.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.21,0:09:05.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没在哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.37,0:09:09.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我回家了  -我们在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm home! - We're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.42,0:09:12.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是惠特妮  我们在打扮她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is Whitney. We're giving her a makeover.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.17,0:09:14.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  你的家人都很善良\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. You have such a nice family...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.84,0:09:17.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的房子也很漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and a really beautiful house.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.02,0:09:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你们怎么认识的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks. You two know each other how?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.86,0:09:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我的约会对象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's my date.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.22,0:09:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她当然是  我去里面歇着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course she is. I'll be in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.89,0:09:24.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很快就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  这个约会和你预想的不太一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry this didn't turn out like you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.19,0:09:29.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.50,0:09:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许和你预想的也不太一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Probably didn't turn out how you wanted it either.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.32,0:09:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll tell you what.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.68,0:09:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果十年以后我们还都是单身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If neither of us is with anybody in 10 years,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.31,0:09:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩试试行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how about you and me give it a shot?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.55,0:09:42.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着好诡异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's disturbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.38,0:09:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过可以试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.49,0:09:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们的午餐吃的怎么样  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How was your lunch with the boys? - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.36,0:09:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还碰到了米奇尔和小卡  -不错嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ran into Mitchell and Cam. - Ay, nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.66,0:09:48.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定不会相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not gonna believe this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.72,0:09:51.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔说小短是同性恋  -小短吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell says Shorty's gay. - Shorty?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.37,0:09:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我相信他是  -不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, I believe it. - Oh, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.42,0:09:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  他穿着很讲究  跳舞也很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, he's a great dresser, a great dancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.55,0:09:58.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些不能证明什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That doesn't prove anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.42,0:10:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是你朋友中唯一一个没有勾搭过我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's the only one of your friends that never hits on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.63,0:10:01.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友勾搭过你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My friends hit on you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.59,0:10:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  经常的事儿  不过不用担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, all the time, but don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.39,0:10:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是老男人  造成不了什么威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're a bunch of harmless old men.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.39,0:10:06.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们和我一样年纪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're my age.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.84,0:10:10.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小短要保守这个秘密一定很难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure it's very hard on Shorty to keep a secret like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  我觉得你该跟他聊聊  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Jay, I think you should talk to him. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.18,0:10:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你有一个同性恋儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're the only one with a gay son.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.60,0:10:16.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定会愿意跟你倾诉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure he'll appreciate opening up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.68,0:10:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是男人  男人不倾诉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're guys. We don't open up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.68,0:10:21.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们聊运动  聊车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We talk about sports and cars,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.12,0:10:22.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有半夜爬起来尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}getting up in the middle of the night to pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.44,0:10:26.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信米奇出柜的时候  你帮了他不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure you made it very easy for Mitch to come out of the closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.86,0:10:30.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是  -好吧  我去继续帮人打扮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Okay. I'm gonna finish my makeover.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.03,0:10:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我关心别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I care about people.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.20,0:10:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想帮别人改变他们的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I want to help them change their lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.79,0:10:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  我在暗示你应该打电话给你朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, I'm hinting that you should call your friend, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.99,0:10:42.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  我懂了  -好  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. I'm getting that. - Okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.27,0:10:47.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈喽  爸爸回到自己的领地了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey! Daddy in the hizzouse!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.07,0:10:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要这么对一个又新又贵的遥控器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would you do that to a brand-new, very expensive remote?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.11,0:11:01.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我发火了  它又不听话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I lost my temper, and it didn't work.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:02.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  它对我来说没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Therefore, it's useless.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.70,0:11:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  只要碰上电子产品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, honey, when it comes to anything electronic,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.24,0:11:07.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不是个好学生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're not exactly the best student.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.16,0:11:08.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很聪明的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am very smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.14,0:11:11.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大学绩点4.0  你多少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had a 4.0 in college. How about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.04,0:11:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也差不多  尽管我花了很多时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was almost that despite my substantial time
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.51,0:11:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在啦啦队上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}commitment to cheerleading.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.48,0:11:16.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是说好不提啦啦队这档事的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought we agreed not to bring up the cheerleading.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.23,0:11:19.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的大学  啦啦队员可是名流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cheerleading in my college was cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.90,0:11:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橄榄球队的羡慕嫉妒恨到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The football players were so jealous,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.13,0:11:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不让我和几个兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they wouldn't even let me and my buddies
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.57,0:11:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特雷弗  斯科特还有林参加他们的派对呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trevor, Scotty and Ling- go to their parties.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.03,0:11:29.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, Claire,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.16,0:11:31.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砸烂了遥控器  你总得给我道声歉吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you owe me an apology for breaking that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.16,0:11:32.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Phil,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.48,0:11:35.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉砸烂了世上最差劲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I apologize for breaking the world's worst remote...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.58,0:11:37.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一时糊涂而买的遥控器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you bought... stupidly.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.90,0:11:38.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.46,0:11:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它可是被科技咨询网的专家评为最佳遥控器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but the experts at CNET.Com rated it the best remote.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.16,0:11:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了三个半鼠标呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They gave it three and a half mice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.17,0:11:47.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个好主意  我们把科技网的砖家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. I have an idea. Let's invite the gang from CNET over...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.41,0:11:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你那些啦啦队同仁们请来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and your old buddies from cheerleading,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.05,0:11:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个书呆子派对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we can have a nerd party.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.09,0:11:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林才不是书呆子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ling is not a nerd.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.14,0:11:53.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他自己造了架直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He built his own helicopter.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.67,0:11:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他现在还健在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if he was alive today-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.56,0:11:55.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我们不说林了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweet pea, let's not talk about Ling.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.74,0:11:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一提到他你就难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It upsets you too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.06,0:12:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-知道我要干什么吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know what I'm gonna do? - Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.96,0:12:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去买个一模一样的遥控器回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna buy a new remote- the same remote.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.29,0:12:05.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了证明你错的有多离谱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And just to prove how wrong you are,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.72,0:12:06.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要在20分钟内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna teach our dumbest kid
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.89,0:12:09.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教会我们最傻的孩子怎么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how to use it in 20 minutes or less.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.09,0:12:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们最傻的孩子是谁  -卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who's our dumbest kid? - Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.47,0:12:14.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  不行  卢克很懂电器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke? No, Luke understands electronics.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.64,0:12:15.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.73,0:12:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -没错  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Yeah, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.02,0:12:19.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教会海莉怎么用  我就道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Teach Haley to use the remote, and then I'll apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.98,0:12:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海莉  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Haley? - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.73,0:12:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.32,0:12:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小短  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Shorty, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.36,0:12:26.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算去高尔夫球场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was thinking of heading over to the driving range
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.81,0:12:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挥几杆子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and hitting a few balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.62,0:12:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to join me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.68,0:12:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意  杰  我该穿什么好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's great, Jay. What should I wear?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.71,0:12:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道  想穿什么穿什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. Wear- Wear whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.76,0:12:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.39,0:12:38.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -那束花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - The flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.39,0:12:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来好多了  真是人间惨剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They look so much better! This is a disaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.77,0:12:42.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道"惨剧"是什么意思吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You do know what "Disaster" means, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.31,0:12:45.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂  我要求他们过来换一束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't understand. I demanded that they come exchange them.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.94,0:12:47.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还对那花店狂发了顿飚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got all medieval on the florist.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.94,0:12:50.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  我听见你讲电话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, I heard you on the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.32,0:12:52.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是说你不满意  那怎么算发飙呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You said you were displeased, but that's hardly going medieval.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.44,0:12:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我说的是"非常不满意"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me. I said "Very displeased."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.39,0:12:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用的还是我的牛仔音  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I used my cowboy voice, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.98,0:12:57.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.87,0:13:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我微波一下  花就蔫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm microwaving them so they look bad again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.28,0:13:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走火入魔了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that seems a little crazy, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.53,0:13:06.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  是花店的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no! That's the florist.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.03,0:13:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定  把花拿出来  我去应门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Relax. Just take them out. I'll get the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.54,0:13:09.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看不出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He'll never know the difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.70,0:13:13.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  我是花店的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi. Florist.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.71,0:13:16.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请进  花在他那儿呢  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. Come on in. He's over there with the flowers. - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.67,0:13:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.95,0:13:19.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些花看起来蔫头耷脑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They just, uh, somehow lost their vigor.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们一到家就这样了  -小卡  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They were like this when we came home. - Cam. Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.26,0:13:24.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.30,0:13:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的神啊  老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Oh! Oh! Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}God, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.22,0:13:31.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧  我的脸也羞愧得跟火烧过一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at that. Two things flaming at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.43,0:13:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.01,0:13:41.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道你问题在哪吗  -在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know what the problem is. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.12,0:13:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有灵活运用臀部  太僵硬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not moving your hips. They're frozen.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.87,0:13:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臀部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hips?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.42,0:13:45.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  你的臀部  太僵硬了  我教你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, your hips. They're frozen. Here, let me show you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.80,0:13:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别麻烦了  -别跟我争了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No, it's okay.  - No, no. - Don't fight me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.59,0:13:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小短\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, Shorty.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.64,0:13:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向后挥杆  来  这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just bring the club back. Go ahead. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.55,0:13:53.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后屁股转过来  没错  放松就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now turn those hips. That's it. You just gotta relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.39,0:13:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两腿站开点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You gotta open up the stance a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.95,0:13:55.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开  打开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Spread 'em. Spread 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.89,0:13:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  如果不放松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it. If you don't relax,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.21,0:13:59.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那一杆永远挥不得劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're never gonna get that shaft where it belongs.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.91,0:14:01.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们去喝杯咖啡休息下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you know what? How about a coffee?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.63,0:14:03.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走  喝咖啡去  -行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let's get a coffee. - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.26,0:14:05.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按下"功能"键\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now press the button labeled "Activities."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.80,0:14:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在哪呢  -就在右侧  右侧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where is that? - It's just to the right. - To the right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.94,0:14:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后选择"观看DVD"  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And now choose "Watch DVD." - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.80,0:14:13.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  专心点  我们只有20分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, you gotta focus. We've only got 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.01,0:14:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假装  假装商场要关门了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pretend- Pretend the mall's closing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.94,0:14:15.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  这也太傻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, this is stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.97,0:14:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都是用电脑看电视的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I watch TV on my computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.41,0:14:18.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干嘛要学这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do I have to learn this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.69,0:14:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你妈觉得你学不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because your mom doesn't think you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.63,0:14:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁来也学不会啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nobody can.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.93,0:14:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.19,0:14:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.45,0:14:26.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道听起来似乎不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know this seems impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.51,0:14:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是想想有多少次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But this is for all those times
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.92,0:14:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈告诉你她是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that Mom told you she was right...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.29,0:14:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你心里很清楚她是错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you knew she was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.09,0:14:39.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我会尽全力  -乖女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'll do it. - That's my girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.20,0:14:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那男的杆挥的不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, that guy's got a beautiful stroke.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.25,0:14:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧那裤子  一点褶都没有  我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at his pants- no pleats. I like pants like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.24,0:14:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我撑得起来那样的裤子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think I can get away with something like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.80,0:14:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么撑不起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sure. Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.90,0:14:51.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小短  我们是老交情了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, Shorty, uh, we know each other a long time, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.20,0:14:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有30年了吧  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What, 30 years? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.33,0:14:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉你心里藏了个秘密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, um, I sense that you got a secret...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:00.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个秘密让你痛苦不堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's maybe causing you a lot of anguish.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.54,0:15:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听说了什么  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You heard something, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.91,0:15:07.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子米奇尔也曾经这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I had the same situation with my son, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.97,0:15:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.73,0:15:11.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  而我处理得不是很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and I didn't handle it too well either.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.34,0:15:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, uh, I just want you to know
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.61,0:15:16.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以随时对我敞开心扉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you can open up to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.47,0:15:18.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会不余遗力地帮助你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I'm gonna do all I can to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.10,0:15:24.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I mean I-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.19,0:15:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没对任何人说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never said this out loud before to anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.11,0:15:29.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得  要说也只能是对你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I guess, if I did, it would be you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.90,0:15:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  杰  其实  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just that, Jay, you see, I'm, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.12,0:15:36.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.12,0:15:38.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来吧  说出来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go ahead. Yeah. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.12,0:15:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我欠债了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm in debt. - Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.46,0:15:44.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向赌场庄家借了两万  他是个狠角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I owe a bookie 20 G's, and he's a serious guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.67,0:15:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有你雪中送炭  真是太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you offering to give me the dough- This is beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.13,0:15:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等会  你不是同性恋  -同性恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Wait a minute. You're not gay? - Gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.04,0:15:53.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呢  什么同性恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talkin' about- gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.21,0:15:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是呢  你从哪看出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gay. Where'd you get gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.96,0:15:56.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  瞧瞧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. I mean, you're always
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.01,0:15:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天到晚不停地说衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}talking about clothes and everything, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.95,0:16:00.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲是个裁缝  我喜欢服饰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My father was a tailor. I like clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.27,0:16:00.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.01,0:16:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在说我父亲是同性恋吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you calling my father gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.52,0:16:03.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.01,0:16:04.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果当年没有我父亲登陆诺曼底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My father landed on Normandy
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.86,0:16:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不知道在哪混呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to save your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.96,0:16:07.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是看在你借我两万块的份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, if you weren't lending me 20 G's,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.93,0:16:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在肯定揍得你满地找牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd knock you out right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.77,0:16:15.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,支票行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take a check?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.77,0:16:17.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现金更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cash would be better.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:21.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley. You ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.07,0:16:24.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.11,0:16:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开电视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turn on the TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.09,0:16:29.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-安琪拉说他给她染完后  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Angela says, after he colored her hair- - Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.90,0:16:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-头发变灰然后又变绿了  -静音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It turned gray and then green. - Mute it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.88,0:16:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消禁音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Un-mute it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.66,0:16:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六十五块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sixty-five dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.87,0:16:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-播放DVD  -理发师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Put on a DVD. - Hairdresser
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.31,0:16:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗雷德里克·朗迈尔不承认过失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Frederick Longmire denies he's responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.96,0:16:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快进  -我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Skip forward. - Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  回到电视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Back to TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.78,0:16:53.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}...better than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.98,0:16:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霸气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Face!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.30,0:16:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别高兴得太早  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't get all cocky, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.55,0:16:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我这样的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's see what happens to little Haley...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.65,0:17:01.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小海莉要怎么办呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when I do... this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.82,0:17:04.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霸气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ho, ho, ho. Ho! Face.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.57,0:17:06.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, wh- What do I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.95,0:17:09.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别慌  我们练过这个的  好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't panic. We went through this. Just- Just think.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.70,0:17:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃吧  承认你们失败了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give up. Give up. Admit defeat.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.83,0:17:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海莉  -我想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Haley. -Okay. - Uh, let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.87,0:17:18.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先把遥控器转回电视模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You put the remote on to TV mode...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.87,0:17:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后按"输入"键\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then press "Input"...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.13,0:17:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到HDMI1出现  然后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}till you get HDMI 1 and-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.09,0:17:30.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我成功了  -她成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I did it! - She did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.72,0:17:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. You proved your point.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.73,0:17:38.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家里所有人都比我聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody in this house is smarter than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.81,0:17:40.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  亲爱的  不是这意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, honey, you're missing the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.81,0:17:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在20分钟内就教会了海莉用遥控器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I taught Haley how to use the remote in 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.36,0:17:45.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定比她快多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So think how fast you can learn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.40,0:17:47.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那话什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.19,0:17:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See what I'm saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.17,0:17:51.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, it's me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.09,0:17:55.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  老爸  -嗨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Dad. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.09,0:17:57.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来是想告诉你  你的基达坏掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm here to let you know your gaydar is broken.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.14,0:17:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小短不是同性恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shorty is not gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.99,0:18:01.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I, uh- I knew that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.75,0:18:04.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那样对小卡我一时气不过才那样说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made that up to mess with you for dissing Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.87,0:18:07.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你让我花了两万块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? That cost me 20,000 bucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.84,0:18:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.38,0:18:10.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他说是同性恋也没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I reached out to him to let him know it's okay to be gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.08,0:18:14.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真这样做了  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Y ou did? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.53,0:18:16.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我人生最诡异的高尔夫球课之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right after one of the stranger golf lessons of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.96,0:18:19.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他只是个赌技很烂的赌徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turns out what he is is a lousy gambler,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.53,0:18:21.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在我得为他买单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and now I'm the one on the hook for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.85,0:18:25.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太抱歉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.10,0:18:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你笑什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then why are you smiling?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.07,0:18:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真为你骄傲  爸  你成长了不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm- I'm proud of you, Dad. And you're growing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.05,0:18:31.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just-Just stop it. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.46,0:18:32.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道这对我来说多艰难吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you see how hard this is for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.93,0:18:35.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前就跟他们一样  看看我现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, I used to be just like one of those guys. Now look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.04,0:18:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家就跟哥伦比亚村一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a house looks like Little Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.09,0:18:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子是同性恋  我还有个中国孙女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a gay son and a Chinese granddaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.32,0:18:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是越南\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Vietnamese.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.50,0:18:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也只有你才知道区别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Only you would know the difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.75,0:18:44.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别急  老爸  你也没长进多少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry, Dad. Not growing too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.28,0:18:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a little nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.89,0:18:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别紧张  -你肯定美极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't be. - I'm sure you look beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.01,0:18:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.03,0:18:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.01,0:18:59.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.07,0:19:02.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人会围着你转的  赶都赶不走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna be fighting men off with a stick.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.36,0:19:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.90,0:19:08.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡梅隆  -抱歉没打个招呼就来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cameron! - Hi. Sorry for the pop over,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.61,0:19:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想过来送你这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I just wanted to bring you these...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.55,0:19:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢你昨晚帮我照顾莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to thank you for babysitting Lily again last night. -Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.37,0:19:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  跟我客气啥啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gracias! You didn't need to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.78,0:19:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱莉莉  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know I love Lily. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.53,0:19:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来  打个招呼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come in. Say hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.30,0:19:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  来认识一下我的新朋友惠特妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cameron, this is my new friend, Whitney.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.89,0:19:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惠特妮  这是卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whitney, this is Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.34,0:19:27.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  认识你很高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello. It's nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.31,0:19:29.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的裙子真是惊艳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is a spectacular dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.16,0:19:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这老旧玩意?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This old thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.22,0:19:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看看她发型  -天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What about her hair? - Oh, my gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.99,0:19:36.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟芭芭拉·史翠珊在《往日情怀》里一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like Barbra Streisand in The Way We Were.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.08,0:19:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的最爱之一  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- One of my favorites. - Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.75,0:19:42.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  是谁在读永恒系列\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, who is reading The Forevers?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.42,0:19:43.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.84,0:19:47.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近完全迷上吸血鬼小说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so obsessed with this whole vampire thing right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.17,0:19:48.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.22,0:19:51.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚认识了个超棒的男人  他叫卡梅隆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just met the sweetest guy named Cameron.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.88,0:19:54.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他可能是我的真命天子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think he might be the one.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.34,0:19:56.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人会改变吗  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can people change? I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.92,0:20:01.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们总是本性难移  加减个15%吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People are who they are- give or take, yeah, 15%.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.01,0:20:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真的想改变的话最多也就15%\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's how much people can change if they really want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.43,0:20:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那有机会再见了  再见  -恩 谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, I'll see you when I see you. - Yeah, thanks for-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.65,0:20:19.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  甜心  醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, sweetie, wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.27,0:20:23.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干嘛  -教教我怎么用电视吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - I need you to teach me to use the TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.12,0:20:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  为什么不找爸爸教你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now? Why can't Dad teach you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.22,0:20:28.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是夫妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because we're married.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.08,0:20:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是为自己还是为了所爱的人改变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whether it's for themselves or for the people they love-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.92,0:20:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That way. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.71,0:20:37.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后按  -我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And then press- - Mmm! I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.76,0:20:41.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩  15%\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yeah, 15%.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.26,0:20:44.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是  -我成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But you know what? - I did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.85,0:20:48.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有时候这样就足够了  -我成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sometimes that's just enough. - I did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.60,0:20:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  我们下星期见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, I'll see you guys next week, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.72,0:20:55.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay. Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.48,0:20:58.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, I wanna thank you for,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.86,0:21:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我解了围\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, helping me out with that jam.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.78,0:21:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was nothin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.71,0:21:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  我想送你个小礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. And I got you a little present.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.70,0:21:05.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不必这样  -不  我已经买了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You didn't have to do that. - No, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.45,0:21:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦克·布雷演唱会的两张门票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two tickets to see the great Michael Bubly.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.84,0:21:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙简直是天籁之音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The guy sings like an angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.77,0:21:12.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会在露天剧场外面演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna be outside at one of the amphitheaters.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.84,0:21:14.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚肯定爱死这个了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria's gonna love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.69,0:21:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我是说我们俩去  -你和我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. I'm talkin' about you and me. - Oh, you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.82,0:21:18.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  -这会不会有点...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - Well, that's a little-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.42,0:21:21.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是在野外  我们可以顺便野餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought maybe we could have a little picnic since it's outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.32,0:21:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会带瓶好酒  带点奶酪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know? I'll get some nice bottle of wine, a little cheese.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.41,0:21:26.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-铺张毯子  行吗  -行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Lay on a nice blanket. All right? - Yeah, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.86,0:21:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你的发型  谁帮你剪的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yo, hey. I like your hair. Who does your hair? Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.93,0:21:33.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  帅哥  谁帮你剪的头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yo, handsome. Who does your hair?

