[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:36.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:36.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:36.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第二十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.95,0:00:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了问了  当时疼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I forgot to ask- Did it hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.32,0:00:09.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么疼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.29,0:00:11.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从天堂坠落凡间  接触地面的那一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When you fell from heaven and landed on earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.62,0:00:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没从天堂...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't fall from- Ah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.73,0:00:16.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我像个天使\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I'm an angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.24,0:00:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘴巴怎么这么甜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you so sweet?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.74,0:00:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许只是因为我心情太好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe just 'cause I'm so damn happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.07,0:00:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是杰的生日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Today's Ja y's birthday,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.92,0:00:25.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要带他去夏威夷呆上一整个星期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I'm taking him to Hawaii for a whole week.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.90,0:00:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茂伊岛的豪华套房  两人的私密空间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Big suite in Maui. Just the two of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.71,0:00:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把曼尼拴在后院  留一大碗狗食给他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got Manny tied up in the backyard. Big bowl of kibble.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.67,0:00:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑  交给克莱尔和菲尔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding. He's staying with Claire and Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.48,0:00:36.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次旅行他完全不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This whole thing was a big surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.38,0:00:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一手包办  订机票  订酒店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did it all myself- the flight, the hotels.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.29,0:00:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说花了我不少钱  不过绝对值\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cost me a fortune, but it was worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.80,0:00:45.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\pos(134,204)\u1}花了我不少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.53,0:00:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管说了千万遍  不过还是要再说一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In case I forget to say it a few hundred times this week,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.53,0:00:51.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.38,0:00:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy birthday!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.02,0:00:56.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wh- What the heck?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.72,0:00:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-惊喜  爸爸  -全家都会跟我们一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Surprise, Dad. - The whole family's coming with us!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.45,0:01:01.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They are? - Uh-huh.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.15,0:01:03.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  米奇尔  卡梅隆和莉莉也来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, and Mitch and Cameron and Lily too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.25,0:01:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  菲尔正在托运行李呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and Phil- he's just checking the bags. Wow!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.55,0:01:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可真是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's, uh- Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.56,0:01:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是歌洛莉亚的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was all Gloria's idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.70,0:01:10.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把我们机票什么的都包了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She bought all of our tickets and everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.03,0:01:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  所有人的  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? Everyone's? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.39,0:01:13.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你过生日嘛  该花就得花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's your birthday. I didn't spare any expense.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.78,0:01:16.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  谢谢你了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, gee! Thank you, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.90,0:01:19.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他们  都跟我们一起坐头等舱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are they, uh, all gonna be up with us in first class?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.47,0:01:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻啊老公  经济舱啦  你当我是摇钱树啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, no, silly. Coach. You think I'm made of money?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.16,0:01:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.92,0:01:42.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要吃夏威夷野猪宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna go to a luau,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.68,0:01:44.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟迈阿密海豚一起游泳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}swim with the Miami Dolphins,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.80,0:01:46.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐着那啥啥环游\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}take a tour in one of those, the-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.38,0:01:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-直升飞机  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Helicopter. Helicopter. - Mm-hmm. Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.03,0:01:52.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不爱参加活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't like activities.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.37,0:01:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想跟歌洛莉亚到处转转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanted to hang out with Gloria
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.02,0:01:55.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读一读罗伯特·勒德拉姆的小说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and read my Robert Ludlum novels.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.63,0:01:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这电子书里存了整整八本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got eight of 'em loaded up on my book reader thing here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.65,0:02:00.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别误会  我爱我的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I love my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.02,0:02:02.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共进晚餐啦  吃吃烧烤啦都不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love 'em at dinners, I love 'em at barbecues,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.18,0:02:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但干嘛非要到夏威夷去啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but do I have to love 'em in Hawaii?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.37,0:02:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.55,0:02:07.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道自己行李[心理]负担不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I got a lot of baggage,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.78,0:02:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过别担心  我在看心理医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but don't worry, I'm seeing a therapist.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.66,0:02:11.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just kidding. I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.45,0:02:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  我认识这帮人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Daryl, I know these guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.93,0:02:18.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帽子能借我演个戏吗  肯定会很搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I borrow your hat? This will be hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.57,0:02:19.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不行  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.93,0:02:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  菲尔姑父\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aloha, Uncle Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.28,0:02:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去旅行了激动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys excited about the trip?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.67,0:02:26.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激动死了  你知道吗  这是我的第一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we're so excited. You know, this is my first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.75,0:02:28.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -是啊  我知道很不可思议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? Yeah, I know it's surprising.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.45,0:02:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家总说我弥漫着"夏威夷"的气息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People always say I scream "Hawaii."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.55,0:02:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who says that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.38,0:02:33.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一些人  -哪些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- People. - What people?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.39,0:02:34.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了你也不认识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't know them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.64,0:02:39.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  莉莉  嗨 -噢不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Lily! Hi. - Oh, no! Oh, n-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘带钱包了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I forgot my wallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.62,0:02:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我有现金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's all right. I have cash.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.95,0:02:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我没带身份证不能登机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no. I can't get on the plane without my I.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.69,0:02:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多亏了你  小卡  -怎么能赖我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks a lot, Cam. - How is this my fault?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.80,0:02:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为早上你要是按我说的做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because if you had done what I asked you to do this morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.78,0:02:49.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会忙得团团转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then I wouldn't have been overwhelmed
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.84,0:02:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会把钱包落家里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I would have remembered my wallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.40,0:02:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(186,216)\fs26\fn方正粗圆_GBK\b1}四  小  时  前
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.98,0:02:56.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  还得把莉莉的玩具打包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. We still need to pack Lily's toys,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.86,0:02:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打印登机牌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}print the boarding passes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.05,0:03:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂停报纸的递送\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, stop the newspaper.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.60,0:03:02.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你在做什么  我刚打包好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. What are you doing? I just packed those.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.35,0:03:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她穿这身衣裳太可爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She just looks so cute in this outfit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:05.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要她以最佳状态去见贾斯珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want her looking her best for Jasper.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.49,0:03:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说的我一句听不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing you just said made any sense to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.15,0:03:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贾斯珀和他妈妈要来跟莉莉玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jasper and his mother are coming over for a playdate.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.84,0:03:10.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们几周前定好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We scheduled it weeks ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.03,0:03:12.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们要去机场了  -还有一小时呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We're about to leave for the airport. - Not for an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.37,0:03:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贾斯珀只有这时候有空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this is the only time Jasper could do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.04,0:03:15.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贾斯珀是有多忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How full is Jasper's calendar?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.59,0:03:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此乃妙计  只要跟贾斯珀套上近乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a coup. When you get in with Jasper,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.41,0:03:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万事都轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}doors open.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.12,0:03:20.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可是快乐时光幼儿园里的大明星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a legacy at Happy Time Preschool.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.01,0:03:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们连10个月大小孩的马屁都要拍吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're kissing up to a 10-month-old?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.48,0:03:23.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是希望留个好印象嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just want him to like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.86,0:03:25.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  他们来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.01,0:03:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来坐会儿就得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But just in and out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.95,0:03:27.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一堆事要忙活呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We still have a million things to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.45,0:03:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能放松点吗  你总爱瞎操心  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you relax? You always worry. It always gets done.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.33,0:03:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  记住  我们是循道宗信徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, and we're Methodists, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.33,0:03:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[基督教新教主要宗派之一]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.05,0:03:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗谁呢我  这肯定是赶不上飞机了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, who am I kidding? I'm not making this flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.12,0:03:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开车送你回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-uh. I can get you home
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.80,0:03:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后飞机起飞前赶回来  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and back before the plane takes off. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.07,0:03:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  想个法子让飞机晚点起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Daryl- See if you can stall the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.45,0:03:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个...我待会儿再付给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's- I will get to you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.37,0:03:49.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真觉得  真觉得肯定赶不上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really- I really don't think there's enough time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.91,0:03:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  在登机口见  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go. I'll meet you at the gate. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.75,0:03:54.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不会丢我一人自己去玩吧  -这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But you won't get on the plane without me, right? - Oh. Well-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.73,0:03:56.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的  你打算自己去吗  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously? You were gonna get on the plane? Cam!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.85,0:03:58.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just go!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.49,0:04:00.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  后面也得关上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nope. Gotta get that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.61,0:04:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我关不上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I can't-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.19,0:04:04.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-噢  真是慢得要死  -赶紧开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh! That's as fast as she goes. - Just drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.81,0:04:07.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-赶紧开  -行李交给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Just drive. - I'll get the luggage!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.50,0:04:10.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快瞧瞧那帅哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, check out that cute guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.62,0:04:13.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟你可不是一路人  他在读书呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's out of your league. He's reading a book.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.15,0:04:15.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.16,0:04:21.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是今天  奔赴茂伊  -看见菲尔没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Here today, gone to Maui! - Hey. You seen Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.74,0:04:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他载米奇尔回家去拿钱包了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, he drove Mitchell back to get his wallet. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.35,0:04:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  他说一定能及时赶回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. He said he's gonna make it back in time,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.16,0:04:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我看悬啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I think it's gonna be close.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.21,0:04:29.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就把我扔这儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So he left me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.15,0:04:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(186,216)\fs26\fn方正粗圆_GBK\b1}四  小  时  前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.93,0:04:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉还没起来  卢克人也不知道哪儿去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley is still asleep, and I have no idea where Luke is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.69,0:04:35.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底准备好了没啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And are you even ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.56,0:04:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的包都放在客厅了  一切都会没事的啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My bag's in the living room. Everything's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.21,0:04:40.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  抱歉  我有点小紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Fine. I'm sorry. I'm a little tense.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.58,0:04:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你还喝咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coffee'll help that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.48,0:04:43.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.55,0:04:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是聊过了嘛  航空旅行非常安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've been over this. Air travel is incredibly safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.46,0:04:48.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道的  不过话说回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I know. But at the end of the day,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.14,0:04:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就是天空中的一座建筑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it is still a building on its side
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.58,0:04:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,横着被扔过来扔过去呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}being thrown from one place to another.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.28,0:04:52.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有电影看  -顶屁用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- With a movie. - Not helping.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.23,0:04:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要来点什么药  帮助你缓缓神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna take something, maybe calm your nerves?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.76,0:04:59.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  孩子们还指着我呢  我要清醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No. I wanna be alert if the kids need me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.02,0:05:03.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好伟大的母亲  有时我都希望你能是我母亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What a mom. Sometimes I wish you were my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.73,0:05:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  菲尔  我已经有点想吐了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God, Phil. I'm already feeling a little queasy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.24,0:05:10.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌这种感觉  特讨厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate this feeling. I hate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.41,0:05:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是快上飞机这感觉就会越强烈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it's just gonna get worse and worse until the flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.70,0:05:15.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.30,0:05:17.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有菲尔大叔在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uncle Phil's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.38,0:05:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的  老弟  第一个准备好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great job, buddy! First one ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.48,0:05:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  艾丽克斯  要走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley and Alex, let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.66,0:05:25.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bless you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.66,0:05:25.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(294,238)\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK}听到别人打喷嚏的安慰语
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.73,0:05:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-来了  -好的快跟上  姑娘们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Coming. - All right. Come on, girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.15,0:05:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练兵千日  用兵一时啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. This is why we practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.86,0:05:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就来了  就来了  -十五秒的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on through. Come through. - Fifteen seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.60,0:05:34.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-准备好了吗  -准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are we ready? - I think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.45,0:05:35.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's go time.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.89,0:05:39.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直奔小车  欲速则不达  慢慢来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Straight to the car. Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.21,0:05:41.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走  走  走  欲速则不达  慢慢来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go, go, go, go, go. Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.54,0:05:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -很好  快走  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Very nice!  -Alright. Let's go. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.99,0:05:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好像还多余几秒呢  -不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I think we got an extra couple of seconds. - No,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.61,0:05:47.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  -老爸  赶紧的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- we don't. - Dad, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.76,0:05:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想这么抱你一整天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will never get tired of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.79,0:05:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me neither.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.51,0:05:58.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈知道怎么样才最酷吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what would be cool, Mum?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.06,0:05:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.81,0:06:00.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是飞机直插入暴风雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If the plane flew into a storm
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.69,0:06:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后像《迷失》里那样坠毁在一座岛上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and crash-landed onto an island like in Lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.46,0:06:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里不对劲吗  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Something wrong there, Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.53,0:06:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新买的登山鞋磨得我脚生疼啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm just breaking in a new pair of hiking shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.05,0:06:18.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一向如此  我们家的男人脚踝都比较粗壮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This always happens. All the men in my family have wide ankles.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.83,0:06:21.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个叔叔只能穿喇叭裤  对天发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have an uncle that can only wear bell bottoms. Hand to God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.43,0:06:22.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wasn't doubtin' ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.43,0:06:24.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是纳闷儿你为什么要穿个登山鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just why are you wearing the hiking shoes?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.74,0:06:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-惊喜吧  -什么  又来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Surprise! - What, again?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.11,0:06:30.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早上整个一家子都要去登山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every morning the whole family's gonna go hiking.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.44,0:06:31.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一星期下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then at the end of the week,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.71,0:06:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就都能爬到火山顶了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we all gonna make it to the top of the volcano.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.45,0:06:35.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早上是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every morning, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.41,0:06:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  当时小卡一提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. When Cam suggested it,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.80,0:06:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道这主意你肯定喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew you were gonna love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.75,0:06:41.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-原来是你的鬼主意啊  -生日快乐  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, so this was your idea? - Happy birthday, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.23,0:06:43.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啊  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, thanks, buddy. Ow.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.92,0:06:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小甜心好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, sweetheart!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.29,0:06:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要去登山啦  -她在笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm going hiking! - She's smiling!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.62,0:06:55.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.50,0:06:58.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  老妈  我怀孕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, Mom, I'm pregnant.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.04,0:06:59.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  不过你还是得吃晕海宁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. You still gotta take your Dramamine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.56,0:07:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿谁会晕机吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, does somebody get a little motion sickness?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.85,0:07:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能从头吐到尾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I throw up all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:05.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你得赶紧吃点晕海宁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well, then Dramamine's the way to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.98,0:07:08.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是想干什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.35,0:07:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不能让她睡着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'm just trying to keep her awake
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.66,0:07:11.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样上了飞机她就能睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so she'll sleep on the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.36,0:07:13.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会喜欢乘飞机碰上个大哭的婴儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nobody likes a crying baby on a flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.14,0:07:14.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦人得很\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's-It's very stressful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.47,0:07:16.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年我从纽约飞回来的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, last year I flew back from New York...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.68,0:07:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边就有个婴儿吵了一整路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}next to a baby who was very upset the entire flight,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.43,0:07:20.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,备受煎熬啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it was hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.62,0:07:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是跟你一班飞机嘛  我怎么不记得...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was on that flight with you, and I don't recall-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.20,0:07:24.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  你指的是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I get it. You're talking about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.94,0:07:25.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好笑哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's very funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.74,0:07:27.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没能买到《舞出我天地》的票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, we couldn't get tickets to Billy Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.72,0:07:31.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就只想能够跳上舞  说的是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All he wanted to do was dance, and that's my story.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.00,0:07:32.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叨逼叨了五个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Five hours of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.32,0:07:34.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我就想能跳上芭蕾"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&} I just want to dance at the ballet!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.91,0:07:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晕海宁  上次坐飞机之前我吃点这个就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dramamine. Oh, I wish I had that the last time I flew.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.31,0:07:45.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说那飞机可是  忽上忽下  忽左忽右\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tell you, the plane was rocking up and down, back and forth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.75,0:07:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我真以为机翼给折断了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought the wings were gonna snap off, honestly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.71,0:07:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己拆吧  用牙咬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you do it yourself. Use your teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.24,0:07:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最快的路线吗  怎么不上高速\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-Is this the best way to go? What about the freeway?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.83,0:07:57.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放轻松  交给我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Relax, punkin. I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.10,0:07:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键在于要熟悉路线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's all about knowing the route.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.50,0:08:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你面前的可是靠蹬三轮车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're talking to a guy who made his way
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.82,0:08:02.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挣学费念完大学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}through college by driving a pedicab.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.89,0:08:04.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-知道三轮车是什么吗  -知道知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know what one of those is? - Yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.83,0:08:06.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是刚刚超过我们的那辆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just saw one pass us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.62,0:08:09.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抢答  《邪恶女人》是谁唱的  -啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Quick- Who sang "Evil Woman"? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.56,0:08:11.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ELO组合[音同Hello]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}ELO!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.00,0:08:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你死哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, where the hell are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.34,0:08:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看  靠  转弯口我给错过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, let's see. Oh, shoot! I just missed my turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.22,0:08:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这会儿理应呆在这陪着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're supposed to be here with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.27,0:08:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉过你的  越是接近起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I told you, I get more and more freaked out
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.92,0:08:21.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会变得越抓狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}as we get closer to the flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.01,0:08:22.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  不过米奇...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I know, but Mitch- Okay, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.42,0:08:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来还指望你能陪陪我  真是谢谢你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was counting on you to be here, so thanks a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.37,0:08:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她紧张得要疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's pretty tightly wound.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.82,0:08:35.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人就是天性使然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some people are just built that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.97,0:08:37.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢开得再慢一点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honestly, could you drive any slower?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.71,0:08:42.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜世界最大的风力发电机在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess where the world's largest wind generator is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.27,0:08:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是我身后这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it right behind me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.48,0:08:46.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错  在瓦胡岛上[夏威夷群岛之主岛]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nope. It's on the island of Oahu.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.68,0:08:49.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我考虑把它加进我的夏威夷之歌里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm thinking about using it in my song about Hawaii.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:49.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What song?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.92,0:08:52.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老妈没告诉你吗  -惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Didn't Mom tell you? - Surprise!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.43,0:08:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大家子准备给你的生日弄个汇演助兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The whole family's putting on a show for you for your birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.70,0:08:59.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都要上台表演  菲尔都把木偶拿来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody's performing. Even Phil brought his dummy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.20,0:09:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很棒啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Isn't that great?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.37,0:09:03.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Jay? - Oh, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.27,0:09:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在想如果我一不小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was just thinking how tragic it would be
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.16,0:09:06.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉进火山可就悲剧了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I fell into that volcano.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.64,0:09:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  别说胡话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, papi, don't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.64,0:09:12.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿睡  宝贝  待会儿睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not yet, sweetie. Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.20,0:09:17.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  真是完美无缺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? He's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.61,0:09:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他连买咖啡都不加巧克力的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at him getting coffee and not putting chocolate in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.81,0:09:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's so mature.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.09,0:09:22.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那迪兰怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What about Dylan?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.20,0:09:24.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰可比不上他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan's no that guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.11,0:09:27.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(186,216)\fs26\fn方正粗圆_GBK\b1}四  小  时  前
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.58,0:09:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  赶紧的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.85,0:09:29.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有两分钟就要出发了  起床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're leaving in two minutes! Get up!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.59,0:09:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天啊  -不会吧  已经是第二天了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God! - Oh, no. Is it tomorrow?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.10,0:09:36.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  你在这儿干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan! What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.87,0:09:39.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想走的  但是见你入睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was gonna go, but then you fell asleep,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.50,0:09:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想到你要离开一个星期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and since you're leaving for a week,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.84,0:09:42.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就寻思着能多看几眼就多看几眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to stare at you as long as I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.47,0:09:44.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧走吧  要不然我爸妈会以为我们做过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to go. My parents are gonna think we did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.14,0:09:46.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还想呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As if.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.41,0:09:49.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快出去  千万别让别人发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get out of the house and make sure that nobody sees you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.26,0:09:52.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会想你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'II miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.46,0:09:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这一走  我就像一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When you're gone, it's like I'm
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.68,0:09:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困在寂寞小岛上的囚犯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this prisoner trapped in a cell of loneliness.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.53,0:09:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得真好  不过你真得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's beautiful, but you have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.03,0:09:58.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.23,0:10:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌这种感觉  特讨厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate this feeling. I hate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.49,0:10:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是快上飞机这感觉就会越强烈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it's just gonna get worse and worse until the flight. - Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.70,0:10:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.80,0:10:16.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有菲尔大叔在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uncle Phil's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.82,0:10:19.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好样的伙计  第一个准备好的  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Great job, buddy! First one ready. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.88,0:10:21.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  艾丽克斯  要走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley and Alex, let's go! Coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.41,0:10:23.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bless you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.41,0:10:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(294,238)\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK}听到别人打喷嚏的安慰语
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.79,0:10:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-来了  -好的快跟上  姑娘们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Coming. - All right. Come on, girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.34,0:10:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.47,0:10:29.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-练兵千日  用兵一时  -就来  就来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is why we practice. - Come on through. Come through.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.72,0:10:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-十五秒的时间  准备好了吗  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Fifteen seconds. Are we ready? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.33,0:10:33.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's go time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.56,0:10:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直奔小车  欲速则不达  慢慢来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Straight to the car. Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.20,0:10:39.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欲速则不达  慢慢来  直接走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast. Straight through.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.37,0:10:42.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -赶紧走  赶紧走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Very nice! - All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.50,0:10:44.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好像还多余几秒钟呢  -不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I think we got an extra couple of seconds. - No,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.25,0:10:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  -老爸  赶紧的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- we don't. - Dad, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.53,0:11:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.84,0:11:07.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My keys!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.10,0:11:12.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑住啊  宝贝  别睡着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stay awake, sweetie. Stay awake.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.29,0:11:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  噢不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whee! Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.80,0:11:18.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房产经纪人培训就是用来对付这个的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is where your Realtor training comes in handy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.94,0:11:22.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着像是标准的波特森D型顶锁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Looks like a standard Porter and Sons D-Model top lock.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.98,0:11:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速刷一下应该就能打开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One quick swipe oughta pop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.85,0:11:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All aboard.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.85,0:11:29.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -走起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.20,0:11:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice and easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.60,0:11:34.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你夹痛我了  夹痛我了  -不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, you're pinching. You're pinching. - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.64,0:11:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经手千万房屋  习得百般技艺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you show enough houses, you learn all the tricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.48,0:11:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个房产经纪人可都是深藏不露的大师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Every Realtor is just a ninja in a blazer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.90,0:11:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般的小毛贼入室行窃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The average burglar breaks in
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.70,0:11:45.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会留下各种蛛丝马迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and leaves clues everywhere,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.31,0:11:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.27,0:11:48.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥来无影  去无踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm completely clueless.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.94,0:11:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么重你还吃得消吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're sure I'm not too heavy?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.24,0:11:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  我打彩弹枪穿的护具都比你重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please, you weigh less than my paintball gear.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.16,0:11:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  -好嘞  进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Yup. - There we go. We are in.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.30,0:11:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下来吧  压到脖子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Off-load. On we go. Squeezing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.58,0:12:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-缓一会儿  -你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm going for a ride. - You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.38,0:12:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yup. I'm good. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.17,0:12:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.99,0:12:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提防着下次再有人想破窗而入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just making it a little tougher on the next guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.96,0:12:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明人总是先别人一步  我靠...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got to get up pretty early- Son of a-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.25,0:12:12.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you all right? - Yes, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.24,0:12:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点被你们家的救火车搞死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just, uh, almost killed myself on your fire truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.63,0:12:17.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我们家的  是贾斯珀的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not ours. That's Jasper's.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.02,0:12:18.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们认识贾斯珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know Jasper?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.07,0:12:19.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他爸妈从我这买过一栋房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I sold a house to his parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.54,0:12:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是怎么约到他来家里玩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did you ever get a playdate with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.80,0:12:23.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧走吧  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go! Please, can- yeah. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.82,0:12:27.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞅瞅  他在素描哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at him. He's sketching.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.27,0:12:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像泰坦尼克号里的莱昂纳多一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's like Leonardo DiCaprio in Titanic.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.85,0:12:32.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打赌他一定是艺术院校的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bet he goes to art school.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.69,0:12:34.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说他是不是在画我俩呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think he's sketching us?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.81,0:12:37.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我"俩"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. "Us."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.93,0:12:41.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于5点30分飞波士顿的航班现在开始登机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Check-in for the 5:30 flight to Boston may board at this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.84,0:12:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对上眼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.81,0:12:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:52.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我被困住了"  哎呦喂  真能折腾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I'm trapped." Yeah, yeah, yeah. What a drama queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.13,0:12:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去"浣赏"鲸鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We will go whale washing,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.09,0:13:00.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探索热带雨林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}explore the tropical forest,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.56,0:13:02.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回归大自然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}get back into the nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.32,0:13:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来不错啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That sounds fun. Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.16,0:13:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -不谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.37,0:13:07.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your attention, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.58,0:13:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请曼尼·迪尔加多到22A登机口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Will Manny Delgado please report to Gate 22-A?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.74,0:13:13.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼·迪尔加多到22A登机口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny Delgado to Gate 22-A.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.17,0:13:16.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  外公  晕海宁起作用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Check it out, Grandpa. The Dramamine's working.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.90,0:13:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都不晕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not dizzy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.19,0:13:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心饮料  小鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Oh, watch the drink, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.10,0:13:22.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  我的小说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh! Ooh, my Ludlums!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.78,0:13:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起  外公  -没事  别紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm sorry, Grandpa. - All right. Relax, relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.60,0:13:25.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能没什么大碍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We might be okay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.28,0:13:34.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上天待我不公  上天待我不公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not fair. It's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.72,0:13:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉女士  他是曼尼·迪尔加多吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me, ma'am. Is this Manny Delgado?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.11,0:13:41.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -你儿子的名字在禁飞名单里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. - Your son's name is on a no-fly list.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.30,0:13:43.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  安检那会儿就跟我们核实过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, please, we've been through this at the check-in.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.25,0:13:44.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是名单里的那个曼尼·迪尔加多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not the same Manny Delgado.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.88,0:13:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个想重现旅行格调的男孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just a boy trying to bring style back to travel.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.36,0:13:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们只想核实几个问题  -这是个误会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We just have a few questions to ask. - No, this is a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.66,0:13:51.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我老公人呢  杰  -这边请  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where is my husband? Wait. Jay! - Step this way, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.87,0:13:53.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士  请这边走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ma'am, step this way, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.28,0:13:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-孩子  这边走  -杰  别推我  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Son, step this way. - Jay! No pushing. Jay!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.12,0:14:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我双份的量吧  我一家老小一起旅行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You make it a double? I'm traveling with my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.19,0:14:02.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.69,0:14:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟个男人一起生活肯定简单多了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Must be a lot easier just living with a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.95,0:14:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是同性恋  生活肯定简单得多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, life would be simpler if I was gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.07,0:14:14.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能挤进快车道啊[适应这种生活]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think you could get in the fast lane?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.80,0:14:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我当然能适应了  -我指的是路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, I could totally get in the fast lane. - I mean the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.06,0:14:20.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了条短信  说的什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'm getting a text. What does it say?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦没啥事  是报警器公司\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um- Oh, G- Well, it's nothing. It's the alarm company.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.28,0:14:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说你家有人闯入  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It says your house was broken into. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.52,0:14:28.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啥事  他们会处理的  你开你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's nothing. They'll take care of it. Just drive!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.48,0:14:29.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.89,0:14:37.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩个有趣的机场游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, fun airport game.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.44,0:14:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便挑一个旅客  虚构他们的整个人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You pick out a traveler, you come up with their entire story.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.18,0:14:41.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如这个男人  他叫亨利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. This guy, his name's Henry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.54,0:14:43.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他准备去凤凰城看他的祖母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's on his way to Phoenix to visit his grandmother,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.79,0:14:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母名叫...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}whose name is, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.00,0:14:47.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.56,0:14:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太难了  你来  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Too hard. Your turn. - Okay. Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.18,0:14:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见一个女人  她惊恐万分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see a woman, uh, wracked with fear,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.32,0:14:52.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还被她老公给抛弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}whose husband has abandoned her.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.48,0:14:54.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪里  说谁呢  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where? Where? Who is she? - Me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.44,0:14:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟菲尔说的清清楚楚要他在这陪着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made it perfectly clear to Phil that I needed him here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.60,0:14:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样  米奇尔也在生我的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. It's going around. Mitchell's mad at me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.61,0:15:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得就是因为早上我没帮他整理行李\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He thinks because I didn't help him pack this morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.23,0:15:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才让他忘带钱包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he forgot his wallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.65,0:15:04.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我有一点烦躁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm-I'm sorry. I'm sorry to be snippy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.86,0:15:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在生小卡的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just... I'm a little upset with Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.82,0:15:10.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上打包要他的帮忙  结果他却让我失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I needed his help this morning, and he let me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.43,0:15:12.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我印象中的小卡不是这样的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That doesn't sound like him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.63,0:15:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你请他帮忙他却不闻不问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You asked him to do something and he didn't do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.90,0:15:17.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没见他开口说啊  他就在那一直说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But he never asked! I mean, all he said was,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.77,0:15:19.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"莉莉的东西要装好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Lily's bag needs to be packed
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.33,0:15:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报纸要暂停寄送"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the newspaper needs to be canceled."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.10,0:15:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听着就像是在向你求助啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That sounds to me like he was asking for help.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.51,0:15:25.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听着你简直就是想让他能通灵啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sounds to me like you expected him to read your mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.58,0:15:29.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当我有超能力啊  -不是说让你有超能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What am I, a psychic? - No! It's not about reading minds.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.72,0:15:31.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说要了解另一半的需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's about knowing what your partner needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.59,0:15:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如这样  直接说"帮我个忙"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's an idea: Just say "Help me."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.61,0:15:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我"都可以省了  "帮个忙"就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't even have to say "Me," Just "Help."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.56,0:15:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样他就明白你到底要什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then he'll know exactly what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不至于憋一肚子气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You won't have to get all mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.89,0:15:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒没憋一肚子气  只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not mad. It's just-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.24,0:15:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是希望能和一个人心有灵犀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You wanna believe you're on the same wavelength as someone,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.37,0:15:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可到头来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then it's just-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.21,0:15:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现其实没那么默契时  总有点沮丧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's a little disheartening when you find out you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.94,0:15:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:53.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最难受的是我明明愿意为他付出所有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's frustrating is I would do anything for Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.97,0:15:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他却看不出来  说实话我有点伤心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-and frankly, it's a little hurtful that he doesn't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.90,0:16:02.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机场可真吵杂啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, airports, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.19,0:16:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.16,0:16:06.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在画什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you drawing something there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.49,0:16:09.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩  画得一般般啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. It's no good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.31,0:16:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内心纠结的艺术家  妙极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tortured artist. Classic.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.48,0:16:13.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.46,0:16:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是个机器人  -可不是嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's a robot. - Oh, yeah. Sure is.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.75,0:16:21.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-背后那个是什么  -一只恐龙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's behind him? - A dinosaur.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.56,0:16:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校的作业  让我们画连环画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's for school. We're supposed to make a comic strip.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.12,0:16:26.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也要做哎  就八年级那会儿...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We had to do that too, back in the eighth-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.41,0:16:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才14岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was 14 years old.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.14,0:16:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.75,0:16:35.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他是我的灵魂伴侣"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"He's my soul mate."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.55,0:16:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I d-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.19,0:16:45.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以下是最后一遍登机通告...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is the final boarding announcement for-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.45,0:16:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在喝什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What you drinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.28,0:16:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad. Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.17,0:16:58.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分是汤力水  要谢谢这位大哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mostly tonic actually, thanks to my new sponsor here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.31,0:17:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一想到坐飞机就心里发憷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a little jittery about flying.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.74,0:17:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢  你乘过很多次飞机了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you talking about? You fly all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.23,0:17:06.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  也就这几年开始的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I know. This started just in the last couple years.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.95,0:17:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  之所以会紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I'm just- I'm nervous
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.83,0:17:10.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是因为现在有很多东西放不下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause I've got so much to lose now, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.35,0:17:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.21,0:17:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来喘口气  不用想着度假的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm taking a break from my vacation.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.34,0:17:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,度假可还没开始呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We haven't even started yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.69,0:17:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是觉得吧  真到那个时候我就没个清静了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I gotta figure, I might not have a lot of time for myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.23,0:17:20.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿烤猪宴  一会儿爬山  一会儿表演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, what with the luaus, the hiking, the talent shows.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.83,0:17:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一大家陪你来  你不开心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you not happy that we're coming with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.55,0:17:24.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是跟我的初衷有些不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just not what I expected.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.22,0:17:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过老爸  我们这样你难道不感动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, Dad, doesn't it feel good to know...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.26,0:17:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一家人都甘愿抛下一切来陪你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that your whole family is willing to drop everything to be with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.49,0:17:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还必须坐那铁棺材横跨大洋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to fly across the ocean in a steel coffin?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.55,0:17:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那杯剩下的也给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna finish that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.47,0:17:39.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你们无关  我爱全家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not you guys. I love the family.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.48,0:17:43.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是感觉歌洛莉亚在想方设法地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It just kinda feels like Gloria's going out of her way...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.73,0:17:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,避免跟我单独相处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not to spend time with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.48,0:17:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是认真的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't believe that, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.58,0:17:51.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on, Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.72,0:17:54.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是太傻太可爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is so crazy and so adorable.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.76,0:17:57.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女人是爱你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That woman loves you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.54,0:18:01.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又没说我不招人爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I didn't say I wasn't lovable.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.98,0:18:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是每个做老婆的都愿意花钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not every wife that would spend the money
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.09,0:18:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让全家去夏威夷旅游的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to fly a family to Hawaii.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.27,0:18:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们以为歌洛莉亚的钱哪里来的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Where does everybody think Gloria's money comes from?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.03,0:18:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前在日本从事什么活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what kind of business did you have in Japan?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.65,0:18:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我压根就没去过日本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've never been to Japan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.04,0:18:19.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在2003年的11月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You didn't go to Osaka
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.41,0:18:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有去大阪参加电子贸易展\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}November 2003 to attend an electronics trade show?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.35,0:18:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时我才4岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was four.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.36,0:18:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  你怎么不去门口随便抓个人来盘问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Enough. Why don't you question the other people on the gate, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.49,0:18:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那个拄着拐杖的老妇人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you see the old lady with the cane?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.21,0:18:29.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那拐杖里说不定藏了个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if she has a ceramic knife
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.67,0:18:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属探测器查不出来的陶瓷刀呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in there that can go through the metal detector?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.52,0:18:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却在这里把时间浪费在骚扰小孩子上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And yet you waste your time harassing a little kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.39,0:18:36.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士  你似乎非常了解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ma'am, you seem to know an awful lot about
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.70,0:18:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何偷带违禁品上飞机啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}sneaking contraband on to a plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.66,0:18:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  姐可是哥伦比亚人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I'm Colombian.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.55,0:18:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有没有去过日本呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Have you ever been to Japan?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.77,0:18:44.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想先打一通电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would like to make a phone call.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.62,0:18:47.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们先生们  飞往茂伊岛的航班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ladies and gentlemen, preboarding for our flight to Maui...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.06,0:18:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上开始办理登机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}will begin in the next few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.00,0:18:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  快别转了  -对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, please stop spinning. - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.47,0:18:54.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能让机场也别再转了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now make the airport stop spinning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.55,0:18:56.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做到啦  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We made it! Claire!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.46,0:18:58.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地  你终于来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Thank God you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.70,0:19:00.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.87,0:19:02.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是对不起  -都是我不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I am so sorry. - It was my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.97,0:19:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是你的错  -我应该想到你要什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It wasn't your fault. - I should have known what you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:08.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是不是喝高了  -有点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you drunk? - Kinda.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.51,0:19:11.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有次我去墨西哥的坎昆玩了一周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And once I spent a week in Cancún,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.64,0:19:14.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我说  远远没有传说得那么好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which, by the way, did not live up to the hype.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.55,0:19:19.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来个人跟我解释一下这是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can somebody tell me what the hell is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.29,0:19:20.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就快问完了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're almost done here, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.15,0:19:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你和你的儿子计划一同旅行是吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So you and your son are traveling together? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.65,0:19:26.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你们离开茂伊岛的时间不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then why are you departing Maui on different dates?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.00,0:19:31.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他要和一大家子先回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, because he's traveling back home with his family.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.62,0:19:35.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Surprise!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.26,0:19:36.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只在那呆6天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're only staying for six days.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.69,0:19:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-剩下来的时间只属于我们俩  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The rest of the time it's only you and me. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.42,0:19:42.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯呀  我就想跟我老公单独待一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm-hmm. I wanted to spend some time alone with my husband-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.80,0:19:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在泳池边上喝点鸡尾酒啊  睡睡懒觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}drink cocktails by the pool, sleep in.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.97,0:19:50.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在已经爱你到无以复加了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could not love you any more than I do right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.85,0:19:53.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还找到了一个裸体沙滩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I also found a topless beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.75,0:19:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我只能更爱你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.77,0:20:03.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊先生  旅途愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mr. Jackson, have a great flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.42,0:20:05.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请走左边  真漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's to the left. Oh, gorgeous!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.62,0:20:07.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  是复古衫  -他是在说莉莉吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, thank you. It's vintage. - Think he meant Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.67,0:20:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又说不准\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.47,0:20:11.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五点钟方向有个适合你的帅哥哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, there's another hottie for you at 5:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.11,0:20:13.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想必应该是个艺术家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think he's an artist.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.75,0:20:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是"观赏"鲸鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's whale "Watching."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.87,0:20:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"浣赏"鲸鱼  -"观赏"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Whale washing. - Watching.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.91,0:20:20.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"浣赏"  -差不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Washing. - That's close enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.13,0:20:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅途愉快  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Have a good flight, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.17,0:20:23.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  扮个僵尸给人看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Quick, do your zombie impression.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.78,0:20:26.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她不是喝醉了吧  -没有没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She hasn't been drinking, has she? - Oh, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.12,0:20:29.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在搞笑呢  再来一个"僵尸抱"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's- She's hilarious. Okay, let's do bride of Frankenstein.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.41,0:20:33.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太  太逼真了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's so, so good.

