[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.75,0:00:04.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的非得穿这些难看的毛衣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do we really have to wear these ugly sweaters?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.21,0:00:06.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让奶奶看到就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just until Grandma can see them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.59,0:00:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的领口太小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My neck hole is too small.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.75,0:00:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的弄得人浑身发痒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mine's itchy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.05,0:00:11.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我宁愿痒死也不愿意窒息死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I'd rather be itchy than chokey.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.69,0:00:12.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来  菲尔  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Phil. Hurry up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.92,0:00:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.18,0:00:15.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视频连接中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Connecting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.31,0:00:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登陆  佛罗里达  完毕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come in, Florida. Over.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.63,0:00:21.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom? Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.14,0:00:23.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  菲利普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, Philip.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.81,0:00:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平安夜快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Merry Christmas Eve!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.11,0:00:28.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平安夜快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Merry Christmas Eve!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[歧义：镜头拉低/声音低沉]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.07,0:00:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微低一点点  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A little- little lower, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.78,0:00:32.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平安夜快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Merry Christmas Eve!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.82,0:00:34.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你们送来的毛衣  -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks for the sweaters. - I-I- Oh, you're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.41,0:00:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们穿这些毛衣好看极了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You look beautiful in them, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.29,0:00:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老妈呢  -她正在快速下沉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where's Mom? - Mom is sinking fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.29,0:00:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在浴缸里泡澡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-oh. She's in the bathtub.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.08,0:00:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听懂了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.42,0:00:46.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有那种老式四脚浴缸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They have that claw-foot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.89,0:00:47.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  快来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.75,0:00:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  老爸  看我们家的圣诞树\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, pops, here's the tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.84,0:00:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些是你送给我们的装饰物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, uh, there-there's the, uh- there's the ornament you sent us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.84,0:00:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这儿  看到了没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right here. Right here. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.01,0:00:59.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是圣诞长袜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There are the stockings,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.05,0:01:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔把它们吊[死]在烟囱上的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}hung by the chimney by Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:05.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是那么搞笑啊  儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah! Still funny, Son.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.60,0:01:07.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是什么  -还那么搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What the hell is that? - Still funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.27,0:01:09.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么  看上去像是被香烟烫的洞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is that? That looks like a cigarette burn.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.28,0:01:10.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们有人抽烟了吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Was one of you smoking a cigarette? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.82,0:01:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  -你们谁在偷着抽烟吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Which one of you was smoking?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.45,0:01:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我  我呼吸系统有问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not me. I have a respiratory problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:16.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然不是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Obviously it wasn't you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.57,0:01:19.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-难道某人又吸烟又说谎吗  -亲爱的  快来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Now I've got a family of liars and smokers. -Honey, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.74,0:01:20.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得来看看这出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You gotta see this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.24,0:01:22.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的圣诞礼物是不是也是从商场偷来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you shoplift your Christmas presents too?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.56,0:01:24.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲利普  -海莉  不许脱那丑毛衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Philip? - Haley, keep that ugly sweater on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.79,0:01:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  圣诞快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, merry Christmas!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.31,0:01:42.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不是那种审判\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, it isn't that kind of a trial.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.64,0:01:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为他说他是圣诞老人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just because he says he's Santa Claus.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.73,0:01:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但直觉告诉我他就是圣诞老人  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I've got a feeling he is Santa Claus, Mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.02,0:01:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人不相信圣诞老人真的存在  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some people don't believe that. That's why-
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.26,0:01:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哭了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you crying?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.94,0:01:54.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是机器人吗  多么感人的电影啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you, a robot? It's a deeply emotional movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.32,0:01:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  亲爱的  你到厨房来帮我下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, miamor, I need you to help me in the kitchen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.32,0:01:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先让我们看完这部电影  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We gotta finish this first, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.50,0:02:00.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子从没看过《34街奇迹》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The kid's never seen Miracle on 34th Street.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.99,0:02:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为他一直和我家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's because he always
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.08,0:02:04.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起在哥伦比亚过圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}spends Christmas in Colombia with my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.16,0:02:07.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们看的是《萨拉萨尔和大熊拯救圣诞》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And all we see there is Salazar and El Oso Save Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.50,0:02:09.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听上去很经典啊 -确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sounds like a classic. - It is.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.07,0:02:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  能让我们看完电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, can we finish the movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.13,0:02:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和别人那么不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not like anyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.47,0:02:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定是圣诞老人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He must be Santa.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.55,0:02:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你可能是对的  苏西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think perhaps you're right, Susie.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.30,0:02:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么玩意啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.01,0:02:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么玩意啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.52,0:02:24.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-傻冒  -什么玩意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Inocente! - What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.81,0:02:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你说我们要一起看这部电影时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When you told me we were going to watch this movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.94,0:02:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就从网上下了这个恶作剧版的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a joke copy from the Internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.63,0:02:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是傻冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are the inocente!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.15,0:02:33.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像有点弄不明白状况了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, maybe I'm a little confused right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.73,0:02:35.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是傻冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is this "Inocente" Stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.21,0:02:38.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哥伦比亚  恶作剧是圣诞传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In Colombia, practical jokes are a Christmas tradition.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.07,0:02:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被愚弄的人就是傻冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The one that is fooled is the inocente!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.12,0:02:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在愚人节时才会恶作剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We tell practical jokes on April Fool's Day,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.62,0:02:45.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别再搞这一套了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So do not do that again.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.98,0:02:48.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Inocente."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会出现吗  搞得我兴致全无\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does it do it again? Ah, it's ruined.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.25,0:02:54.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  要排这么长的队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me with this line?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.01,0:02:57.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要找圣诞老人要回我刚浪费的45分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna ask Santa for the last 45 minutes of my life back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.68,0:03:00.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开心点  我们带着女儿在圣诞老人村呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you cheer up? We're in Santa's Village with our daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.34,0:03:02.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年前我们在哪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where were we a year ago?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.08,0:03:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个长队的最前面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were at the beginning of this line.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.93,0:03:07.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  某人需要融入这个节日  妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? Somebody needs to get in the holiday- son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.01,0:03:11.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不是他们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe it's not them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.24,0:03:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, it's them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.29,0:03:15.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.86,0:03:18.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3年前  我组织了一个唱诗班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Three years ago, I formed a caroling group.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.43,0:03:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字是"绿袖子颂歌班"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were known as The Greensleevers.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.24,0:03:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会在慈善活动现场和医院演奏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We would perform at charity events, hospitals-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.24,0:03:24.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时可是红遍大江南北\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They were very, very popular.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.12,0:03:28.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年  我的一名成员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, last year, one of my carolers-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.62,0:03:31.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德鲁  他发动了一场小小的政变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Andrew- staged a little coup.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.96,0:03:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.30,0:03:41.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把卡梅隆踢出了唱诗班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They kicked Cameron out of the group.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.40,0:03:59.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.15,0:04:01.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是"新"绿袖子颂歌班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're the New Greensleevers.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.00,0:04:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新绿袖子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The New Greensleevers?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.58,0:04:07.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是狠狠抽了我一巴掌嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there a slap mark on my face?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.12,0:04:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么让埃德娜唱低声部的合音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, why is Edna singing the low harmony?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.63,0:04:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观众像是因为震惊才鼓掌一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like people are applauding out of shock.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.78,0:04:12.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-随他们去吧  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let it go. - Why would-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.51,0:04:14.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  下一个  -终于啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, next. - Ah, finally.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.28,0:04:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我能  你能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa! I'm- I'm sorry. Can I- Could you-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.53,0:04:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个圣诞老人怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened to the other Santa?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.53,0:04:23.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我们排队真的排了很久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, we've been waiting in this line for a really long time,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.74,0:04:26.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只想要一个有圣诞老人样子的圣诞老人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we just want a Santa that actually looks like Santa.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.45,0:04:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.46,0:04:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  小卡  不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. Cam, it's not okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.03,0:04:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是莉莉过的第一个圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is Lily's first Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.39,0:04:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想确保一切都很完美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to make sure everything is perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.26,0:04:35.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要等那个胖圣诞老人  明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna wait for the fat Santa. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.31,0:04:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew this would happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.74,0:04:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我真不知道我们为什么雇佣这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I don't even know why we hired this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.30,0:04:40.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  连他的精灵都同意我的话  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? Even his elves agree with me. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.89,0:04:43.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到圣诞让你变得如此龟毛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't know Christmas made you so petty.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.17,0:04:47.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逊毙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lackluster!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.16,0:04:52.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate you!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.28,0:04:54.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不能接受你们吸烟  到底是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is unacceptable, and I want to know who did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.86,0:04:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nobody, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.43,0:05:00.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是沙发自己把自己烫了个小洞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess the couch did it to itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.21,0:05:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦的一天后回到家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess it came home after a tough day,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.66,0:05:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点了支烟  烧到了它自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}lit up a cigarette and then it burned itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.82,0:05:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗  可真是荒谬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that what happened? Because that makes no sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.46,0:05:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的烟民如果不站出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If whoever is responsible doesn't come forward,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.38,0:05:10.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会将你们三个统统作为惩罚对象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}your father and I are just gonna have to punish all three of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.63,0:05:11.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.88,0:05:13.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这不公平  -我能原谅你们抽烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's not fair! - I can forgive the smoking,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.88,0:05:15.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是不能原谅撒谎  -不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- but I can't forgive the lie. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.38,0:05:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽烟也不能原谅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or the smoking.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.51,0:05:21.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人主动承认  真没有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No one wants to confess, huh? No?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.05,0:05:23.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  知道接下来会怎样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's fine, 'cause you know what happens next?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.02,0:05:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们取消圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We cancel Christmas!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.92,0:05:28.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.94,0:05:30.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Dad, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.34,0:05:33.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔喜欢在孩子面前夸海口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil has a habit of making big pronouncements to the kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.99,0:05:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次我告诉卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time I told Luke...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.19,0:05:38.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他不把他的脏碗放进洗碗机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that if he didn't put his dirty dishes in the dishwasher,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.87,0:05:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就把脏碗放他床上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we would put them in his bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.33,0:05:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔的问题就是  坚持到底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil's problem is follow-through.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.87,0:05:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就没有碟子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We had no more dishes,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.71,0:05:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以最后只能用金鱼缸吃麦片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so we were eating cereal out of the goldfish bowl.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.42,0:05:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  猜猜我现在要去干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Guess where I'm headed?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.59,0:05:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把圣诞树砍了  就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To take down the tree. That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.01,0:05:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快坦白吧  -这是你们最后的机会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on, guys. - This is your last chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.59,0:05:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是谁做的  要勇于承担责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoever did this, just take responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.55,0:06:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要连累其他人  卢克  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't put the rest of us through this. Luke? No?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.14,0:06:06.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样吧  好吧  真砍了哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is really it. Okay? Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.06,0:06:10.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三  二  一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Three, two, one.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.11,0:06:14.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  再见  邓菲家的圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Good-bye, Dunphy Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.71,0:06:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  我估计你拿不到新车做礼物了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, I guess you're not getting that car.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.57,0:06:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能得到新车作为礼物吗  -不会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I was getting a car? - Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.17,0:06:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撒谎的  因为现在就流行撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was lying, because that's what we do now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.81,0:06:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲一家人都是撒谎精\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dunphys are liars.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.83,0:06:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当老大的时候  一切都以音乐为中心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I was in charge, it was all about the music.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.50,0:06:35.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他们要在唱完歌后  把拐杖糖扔给观众\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, what's with them tossing out candy canes after every carol?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.51,0:06:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是为了迎合  -我认为你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's pandering.  - I think you
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.99,0:06:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把糖又扔回去  已经表明了你的反感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}made that clear when you tossed them back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.91,0:06:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎样才能把这些东西都放进车里啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How am I supposed to get all this in the car?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.51,0:06:42.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我来帮帮你们吧  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let me give you a hand with that. - Uh, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.51,0:06:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  圣诞老人  -别再那么叫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks. Thanks, Santa. - Can't call me that anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.61,0:06:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚被炒鱿鱼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just got canned.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.39,0:06:48.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh- really?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.98,0:06:51.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是有一些人投诉  说我不够胖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess a couple people complained I wasn't fat enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.19,0:06:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.63,0:06:55.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想过胖又引发心脏病  现在就这下场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what I get for trying not to have a second heart attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.73,0:06:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  空间总是能腾出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you go. Always a way to make room.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.69,0:07:00.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我作为住在车里的人  给你们的箴言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take it from someone who lives in his car.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.70,0:07:02.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  非常感谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, well, thank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.66,0:07:04.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事儿  圣诞快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No problem. Merry Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.66,0:07:05.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  麻烦您\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, wait, wait. Um, please,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.92,0:07:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我给你些小费...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, let me give you a little something...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.96,0:07:09.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-感谢你过来帮忙  -不  没关系的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- for your troubles. - No, that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.58,0:07:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  真的吗  -你真住在车里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gosh. Really? Okay. -Do you really live in your car?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.50,0:07:13.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不过也没那么糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. It's not so bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.88,0:07:16.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子搬出去后  就宽敞多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's pretty roomy since the wife moved out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.15,0:07:19.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你今晚到我们家来共进晚餐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you come over to our place for dinner tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.77,0:07:22.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你当真  -是的  今晚可是平安夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Seriously? - Yeah. It's Christmas Eve.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.02,0:07:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总不能在你的车里过吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Y-You can't spend it in your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.05,0:07:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可真是好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow, that's really nice of you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.06,0:07:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带些什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, can I bring anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.50,0:07:29.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,番茄酱  酱油  吸管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ketchup, soy sauce, straws?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.35,0:07:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都有的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.35,0:07:34.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  你可以跟在我们车后面去我们家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, uh, why don't you follow us to our house?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.02,0:07:35.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  开着你的"家"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. In your house.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.53,0:07:38.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.82,0:07:40.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡梅隆  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cameron. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.12,0:07:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万事俱备  今晚9点整\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Tonight, 9:00 sharp,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.28,0:07:48.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们各自打开一份礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we open one present each.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:50.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡衣  我们就穿着睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pajamas- which we sleep in.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.47,0:07:52.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天早上7点  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tomorrow morning, 7:00 a.M., Manny,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.79,0:07:55.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在楼梯上拍圣诞照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}on the stairs for the Christmas picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.38,0:07:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们打开礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then we open presents.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.84,0:07:58.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哥伦比亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In Colombia,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.68,0:08:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们午夜时打开礼物  然后一直守夜到早上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they open presents at midnight and stay up till morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.18,0:08:02.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很确定他们确实是那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sure that they do,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.23,0:08:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过既然你没有在大街上看到山羊乱窜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but as you'll notice from the absence of goats in the street,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.82,0:08:06.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明我们并不在哥伦比亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we are not in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.52,0:08:08.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  我开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on! I'm kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.96,0:08:11.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不能融合点哥伦比亚传统习俗进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why can't we mix a couple of Colombian traditions in?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.02,0:08:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-比如呢  -比如烟火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Like what? - Like fireworks.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.56,0:08:16.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  哥伦比亚才没有烟火呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. You don't have fireworks in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.57,0:08:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们又想让我变成傻冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're trying to make me the inocente again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.32,0:08:20.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们有的  晚上的天空很美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we do. At night the sky is beautiful-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.76,0:08:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有圣诞的气氛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}very Christmassy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.74,0:08:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That doesn't make any sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.18,0:08:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个国家都有自己的传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, every country has their own traditions.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.53,0:08:27.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  在我们的文化里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In our culture, for example,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.20,0:08:29.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送圣诞礼物的  是婴儿耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the baby Jesus is the one... that brings the gifts,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.70,0:08:30.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是圣诞老人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not the Santa Claus.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.95,0:08:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那根本就不合理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that doesn't make sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.54,0:08:35.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个新生儿怎么能拿得动所有的礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could a newborn baby carry all those presents?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.48,0:08:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们连自己的手在哪都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They don't even know where their hands are.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.17,0:08:39.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少婴儿能穿过烟囱啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At least a baby can fit through a chimney.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.15,0:08:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么坐在婴儿耶稣的膝盖上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How would you sit on the baby Jesus' lap?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.70,0:08:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会压扁他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'd squish it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.76,0:08:44.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  明年我们会谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, next year we'll talk about
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.82,0:08:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们哥伦比亚的一些传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}some of your little Colombian traditions.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.64,0:08:49.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吗  或许  -"或许"就是不会的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay? Maybe. - I know what "Maybe" Means.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.72,0:08:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉你想要夺走我整个圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like you're trying to take away my whole Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.52,0:08:55.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不敢相信圣诞真没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe it's all gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.42,0:08:56.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸从不会坚持到底的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad never follows through.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定不是你的某个朋友烧了沙发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you sure one of your friends didn't burn the couch?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.48,0:09:00.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, don't look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.71,0:09:03.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们中只有一个人  曾经点火柴玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Only one of us was ever caught playing with matches.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.74,0:09:04.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.79,0:09:07.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一年前的事了  承认是你干的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was a year ago. Just admit you did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.82,0:09:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你承认吧  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You admit you did it! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.53,0:09:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我有个主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Look, I have an idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.79,0:09:13.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们记得斯巴达克斯那部电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you remember the movie Spartacus?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.61,0:09:17.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's what we do:
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.90,0:09:20.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  你去告诉爸妈是你做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, you tell Mom and Dad it's your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.42,0:09:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可我没有  -那没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I didn't do it. - It doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.59,0:09:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你招了后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because after you confess,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.30,0:09:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和海莉也会分别承认是我们做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley and I will each confess to the same thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.55,0:09:29.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那有什么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How does that do anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.55,0:09:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会因为我们保护彼此而感动的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They'll be so touched that we're protecting each other...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.02,0:09:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他们就会把圣诞节还给我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that they'll have to bring back Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.48,0:09:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.40,0:09:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么此计可行来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How does it work again?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.06,0:09:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会成为传奇的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're gonna pass into legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.68,0:09:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消了圣诞节的父母亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The parents who canceled Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.45,0:09:43.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you'd be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.49,0:09:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会把我们写进歌里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They'II write songs about us,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.98,0:09:47.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用那些丑陋的小泥人制作圣诞特价玩具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}make one of those Christmas specials with those ugly little clay people.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.95,0:09:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老是说我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're the one who always says
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.33,0:09:51.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对孩子时就狠不下心来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I shouldn't be such a pushover with the kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.49,0:09:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就这样表明自己的立场吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So this is where you decide to make your stand?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.56,0:09:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  -好吧  好吧  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really, Phil? - Okay. Okay, look.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.04,0:09:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  圣诞节会回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry. We're going to have Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.04,0:09:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家孩子那么有责任有担当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've raised our kids right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.16,0:09:59.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管谁做的  都会主动站出来承认错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoever did it will come forward.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.88,0:10:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然另外两个也会把他供出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or the other two will rat 'em out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.13,0:10:03.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.05,0:10:08.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Luke. What, uh- What can we do for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.72,0:10:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.39,0:10:15.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我玩了火柴  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was playing with matches. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.93,0:10:19.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你  你做的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You, uh- You did the right thing- Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.40,0:10:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承认错误是对的  不过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by confessing, but, um-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.40,0:10:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你犯了错  小家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is bad, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.11,0:10:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性质非常恶劣  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, really bad, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  你来处理一下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, you want to handle this?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.74,0:10:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  你刚才为什么不说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, Luke, why didn't you say something?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.83,0:10:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.51,0:10:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你爸爸和我对你失望至极\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, well, your father and I are extremely disappointed in you,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.55,0:10:40.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回你的房间去  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so- go up to your room. Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.46,0:10:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.53,0:10:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一会儿上去找你谈话  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll be up to talk to you in a minute. Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.00,0:10:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海莉  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Haley! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.42,0:10:46.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说话呀  -说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Say something! - About what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.34,0:10:48.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我收回刚才的招供  -怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, I take it back! - What is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.26,0:10:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们俩原本也应该招工的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These guys were gonna say they did it too,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.97,0:10:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你们就会以我们仨为傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you were gonna be proud of all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.76,0:10:52.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为什么要那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would we do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.60,0:10:54.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子满嘴胡言完全不能信啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what to believe with this kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.26,0:10:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子  不是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Liars! I didn't do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.10,0:10:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也不是我干的  -别看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, it wasn't me. - Don't look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.98,0:11:00.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-搞什么啊  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Seriously? - Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.10,0:11:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又没人承认了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nobody did it again?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.95,0:11:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, that's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.32,0:11:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜会怎样  圣诞节依旧取消\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess what? Christmas is still canceled.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.11,0:11:09.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无所谓的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's fine by me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.58,0:11:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明年再过吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's start working on next year.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.87,0:11:16.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了还有除夕  复活节  都不过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, and memo to New Year's Eve... and Easter-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.37,0:11:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Watch your back!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.66,0:11:22.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从海军退役后  算是开始环游世界了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, after I left the marines, I just kinda traveled the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.46,0:11:25.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我游走在各城之间  打些临时工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I go from town to town picking up odd jobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.13,0:11:26.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点像绿巨人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Kinda like the Hulk.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.80,0:11:30.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真巧啊  那正是我在部队时的绰号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's weird. That was my nickname in the corps-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.26,0:11:32.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的暴脾气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause of my bad temper.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.14,0:11:37.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  谢谢你们请我过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, thanks for having me over,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.39,0:11:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请我吃晚饭  帮我洗衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}having me for dinner, letting me do my laundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.73,0:11:41.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天本来很不顺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not been a good day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.02,0:11:47.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特  我有事要跟你坦白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, Scott, I-I have a confession to make.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.65,0:11:50.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I didn't, uh-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.24,0:11:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有清洗洗衣槽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't clean the lint tray,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.86,0:11:53.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你的衣服可能会沾上些毛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so, um, your clothes might be a little pilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.07,0:11:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no problem. That's the least of my worries.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.33,0:11:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们做的一切  我今天很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks for everything. You guys made my day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.37,0:12:02.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-至少可以以此补偿你  -什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's the least we could do. - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.42,0:12:05.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know... what I was saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.67,0:12:12.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们永远都别告诉他了  -完全正确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I just say we never tell him. - Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.82,0:12:16.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给了他钱  热食  帮他洗衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We give him some money, a hot meal, laundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.40,0:12:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们扯平了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think we're square.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.10,0:12:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意  行了  这个东西怎么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Agreed. Okay, how does this thing work?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.94,0:12:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该是按中间的那个按钮  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you just press that button right there in the middle. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.64,0:12:24.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天  -这有点...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my  - Okay. That...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.65,0:12:26.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇得有点太高了  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That seems a little high, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.36,0:12:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我才不要把莉莉放进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. I'm not putting Lily in that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.62,0:12:29.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直像是给宇航员训练用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like something astronauts train in.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.19,0:12:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚯嚯嚯  我来了  嚯嚯嚯  我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ho, ho, ho! It's me! Ho, ho, ho! It's me!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.53,0:12:34.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你爸来了  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's your dad. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.53,0:12:35.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.62,0:12:38.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你们带了礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I brought your presents.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.58,0:12:40.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是明天要见你吗  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aren't we seeing you tomorrow, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.33,0:12:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是给你们的平安夜礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These are your Christmas Eve gifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.70,0:12:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道规矩的  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know the drill. - Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.71,0:12:44.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在睡觉前拆开  里面是睡衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You open those up before bedtime. They're pajamas.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.51,0:12:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在保持这个传统啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still keeping traditions alive, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.09,0:12:47.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总得有人传承优良传统啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, someone has to.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.88,0:12:48.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家有两个哥伦比亚人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got two Colombians at home
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.95,0:12:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要把圣诞节变成五月节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}trying to turn Christmas into Cinco de Mayo.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.78,0:12:53.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那是墨西哥的节日  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know that's Mexican, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.71,0:12:54.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有什么区别呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, burrito, "Bur-right-o."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.06,0:12:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞节就是圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Christmas should be Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.01,0:13:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在楼梯上照相  热巧克力  拆礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Picture on the stairs, hot chocolate, opening the presents.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.14,0:13:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才应该是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was supposed to be
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.23,0:13:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里又添了小孩的好处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the good thing about having a kid in the house again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.27,0:13:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又能像我们以前那样过圣诞节了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can have Christmas the way we used to.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.29,0:13:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂你的意思了  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hear you, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.85,0:13:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我现在在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I was home right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.99,0:13:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定正在调一整浴缸的圣诞蛋酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd be mixin' up a bathtub full of eggnog
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.15,0:13:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力将一只油腻的乳猪  塞进圣诞老人的帽子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and trying to squeeze a greased hog into a Santa hat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.40,0:13:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我不怀念吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't think I miss that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.40,0:13:14.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.36,0:13:20.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点是那些已经是永不褪色的回忆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The point is that those are memories that I'll always have,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.30,0:13:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我有绝佳的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but now I have the perfect opportunity...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.54,0:13:24.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来和我的新家人去创造我们新的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to create new memories with my new family...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.41,0:13:26.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终有一日这些回忆也会不同寻常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that are gonna be just as special someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.29,0:13:29.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  小卡说得没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aw. No. Cam's right, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.29,0:13:31.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们每年都会创造新的传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We create new traditions every year.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.13,0:13:34.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁准备好去试试秋千了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, who's ready to try the swing?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.36,0:13:40.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子  记得提醒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, now remind me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.55,0:13:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天第一件事就是把这个放进烤炉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We put this in the oven first thing tomorrow
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.60,0:13:44.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为杰想要三点的时候吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause Jay wants to eat at 3:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.68,0:13:48.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  是你把这个蜘蛛放在冰箱里的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, Manny! Did you put this spider in the fridge?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.48,0:13:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  恶作剧嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. Inocente.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.61,0:13:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小家伙  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, papi, what's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.73,0:13:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想过个哥伦比亚式的圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to have Christmas like they do in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.22,0:13:56.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰把事情都搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay is messing everything up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.74,0:13:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  理解下他吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, try to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.84,0:14:02.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在杰的儿女尚小之时  他们有很美好的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay has great memories with his kids when they were young.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.24,0:14:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是想和你再现当年的美好回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he just wants to recreate them with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.75,0:14:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我能给杰的最棒的圣诞节礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, maybe the best gift I could give Jay would be...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.83,0:14:09.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是陪他像以前那样过圣诞节吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Christmas like he used to have it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.00,0:14:12.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个乖孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay, you're such a beautiful boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.63,0:14:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你长大以后  我会很怀念\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One day you're gonna grow up, and I'm gonna miss...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.44,0:14:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小时候所做得一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}all the things that you used to do as a little boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.93,0:14:20.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但如果那个所谓的圣诞老人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. But if this so-called Santa Claus...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没送我一件酒红色的晚礼服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}doesn't bring me a burgundy dinner jacket,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.48,0:14:24.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会有大麻烦的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we're going to have a big problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.23,0:14:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.98,0:14:31.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的不该让步吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would it really be so bad to back down?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.07,0:14:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样孩子们再也不会把我们的威胁当回事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And have the kids never take any of our threats seriously again?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.03,0:14:35.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.66,0:14:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许  孩子们会意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or... the kids could realize...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.53,0:14:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们放弃了做父母的权威  做出巨大的牺牲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that we're making a supreme sacrifice by giving up our power
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.28,0:14:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来拯救他们的圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to save their Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.00,0:14:49.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从某种意义上来说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which would, in a way, be
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.29,0:14:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会成为我们送给他们最棒的礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the greatest gift that we could ever give them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.79,0:14:54.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样反而会让他们更加尊重我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And which would paradoxically make them respect us even more.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.82,0:14:56.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  算我痴心妄想  想想刚说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, forget that. Go back one.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.51,0:14:57.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸老妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.14,0:15:01.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It- it was me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.22,0:15:02.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.64,0:15:06.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在学校发现了一根烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I found a cigarette at school,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.77,0:15:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里没人的时候  我抽了一口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and when no one was home, I- I tried it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.35,0:15:15.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我可能拿得离沙发太近了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I-I guess I held it too close to the couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.07,0:15:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.28,0:15:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可以不让我过圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can take my Christmas away,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.08,0:15:22.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但别让其他人也不能过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but don't take it from everyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.37,0:15:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能关心家人这点很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is very noble of you to care about the family,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.45,0:15:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你抽了烟  还撒了谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but you still smoked and lied.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.54,0:15:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的行为需要严厉批评\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's really bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.54,0:15:31.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在帮我去搬圣诞树吧  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Now help me grab the tree. - Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.92,0:15:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  艾丽克斯  回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, Alex, come on back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.47,0:15:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从12月26日开始  你被禁足一周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Starting December 26, you are grounded for a full week,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.63,0:15:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括除夕在内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that includes New Year's Eve.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.35,0:15:45.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是我...  -没有商量的余地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But, I was  - Yeah, non-negotiable. So...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.56,0:15:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.73,0:15:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正式宣布  圣诞节回来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's official! Christmas is back on!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.23,0:15:55.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -发生什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It is? - What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.90,0:15:56.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.40,0:15:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长袜  彩灯  装饰物  花环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stockings, lights, ornaments, wreath!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.57,0:16:00.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-各就各位  开始行动  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go, go, go! - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.78,0:16:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听着似乎是一件压力山大的工作啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that sounds like a stressful job to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.15,0:16:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没你想得那么严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not as much as you'd think.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.58,0:16:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是确保有一人是空弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They always made sure one of us had a blank,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.28,0:16:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就没人知道谁是致命一击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so nobody knew who took the fatal shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.80,0:16:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚餐实在是太美味了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was mighty tasty.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.83,0:16:14.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想呆得过久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't want to overstay my welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.64,0:16:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就先走一步了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You won't have me back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.05,0:16:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩好好享受今晚余下的时光吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys enjoy the rest of your night.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.66,0:16:20.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都是好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're good people.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.26,0:16:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特  等等  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scott. Wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.85,0:16:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了你洗过的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't forget your laundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.56,0:16:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢  多谢  多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Thanks. Thanks, thanks, thanks, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.45,0:16:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Merry Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.53,0:16:32.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特  也祝你圣诞节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scott, merry Christmas to you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.16,0:16:34.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也祝你...  他妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And happy. Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.00,0:16:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -是新绿袖子唱诗班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Oh. It's the New Greensleevers.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.44,0:16:37.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们以前是卡梅隆的唱诗班成员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're Cameron's old caroling group.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.78,0:16:38.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年他们把他开除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They kicked him out this year.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.98,0:16:41.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我从唱诗班开除就算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, it is one thing to kick me out of the group,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.90,0:16:43.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然还来揭我伤疤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but to rub my nose in it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.70,0:16:45.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去把洒水器打开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm turning on the sprinklers.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.04,0:16:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.70,0:16:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道报仇的快感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it feels good to get even.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.87,0:16:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Believe me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.87,0:16:53.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到别人眼中的恐惧很...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To see the fear in a man's eyes is-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.87,0:16:58.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有件事会让你更爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but there's something that feels even better.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.69,0:17:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是  宽恕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Forgiveness.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.76,0:17:02.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯科特  你不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scott, you don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.98,0:17:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前唱诗班就是我的追梦女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This- this group was my Dreamgirls.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.30,0:17:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[追梦女孩  美国著名百老汇音乐剧]
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.75,0:17:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就像是艾菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was Effie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.90,0:17:10.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道我今天做的最棒的事是什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what the best thing I did all day was?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.47,0:17:13.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅你们害我被炒鱿鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Forgiving you for getting me fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.40,0:17:29.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德鲁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Andrew.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.40,0:17:31.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体演出人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ensemble.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.04,0:17:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们今晚在我家门口唱歌绝非巧合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, I know it's no accident that you're here on my street tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.50,0:17:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我  我只想对你们说  你们唱得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I- I just wanted to say to you all that you sound great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.51,0:17:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  圣诞节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And... merry Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.45,0:17:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连你的道歉都走音了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Even your apology is off-key.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.71,0:17:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  没法忍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not cool, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.87,0:17:57.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是快溜吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I should, uh, probably scoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.24,0:18:00.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  但是  不是说要宽恕吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But- but- but what about forgiveness?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.00,0:18:03.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你人很好  而他是下三滥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were nice. He was naughty.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.98,0:18:10.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪去了这么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where were you for so long?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.16,0:18:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后抢购了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just a little last-minute shopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.03,0:18:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是什么  -波瓦洛[甜甜圈]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's this? - Bunuelos.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.08,0:18:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是谁  什么  -芝士馅饼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who? What? - Cheese fritters.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.04,0:18:18.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哥伦比亚圣诞节的传统食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a Colombian traditional Christmas food.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.16,0:18:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  新规定  从现在开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, new rule: From now on...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.17,0:18:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与哥伦比亚有关的事  只许在哥伦比亚做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we do Colombian things when we're in Colombia.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.75,0:18:25.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在美国  只许做与美国有关的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We do American things when we're in America.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.71,0:18:27.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  不许做你们的食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That means no more of your food,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.12,0:18:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许放你们的音乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}no more of your music...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.52,0:18:30.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其不许过你们疯狂的节日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and especially no more of your crazy holidays!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.97,0:18:36.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-傻帽了吧  -杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Inocente! - Ay, Jay!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.77,0:18:37.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  我说错了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Did I say it wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.93,0:18:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们刚刚的样子就是很傻帽嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You two are total inocentes!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.39,0:18:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们应该看看自己脸上的表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should see the look on your faces.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.98,0:18:43.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说一句  你知道在平安夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And by the way- You know how
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.13,0:18:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想买到烟火有多难吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}hard it is to get fireworks on Christmas Eve?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.07,0:18:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去  曼尼  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go, Manny. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.32,0:18:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  又是一份给卢克的礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All righty. Here's another one for Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.12,0:18:59.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看起来像一本书  -我已经有一本书了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Looks like a book. - I have a book already.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.29,0:19:02.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎么回事  我的老天  沙发在冒烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is that? Oh, my God. The couch is smoking.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.80,0:19:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阳光的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's sunlight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.38,0:19:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是装饰物的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the ornament.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.47,0:19:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真酷  像放大镜聚焦一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cool. It's like a magnifying glass.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.26,0:19:17.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪啊  沙发被烧出的洞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, how weird is that? It's burning a hole...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.35,0:19:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和艾丽克斯抽烟烧的洞刚好在同一个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in the exact same spot that Alex was smoking in.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.69,0:19:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉[瞧你蠢的!]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.56,0:19:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  你为什么要主动承担责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, why'd you take the blame?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.06,0:19:26.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想错过圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't want to lose Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.94,0:19:29.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是太高尚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is so stinking beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.86,0:19:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.86,0:19:33.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要  -来嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.70,0:19:34.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要  -来嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.87,0:19:37.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了  -熊抱抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, yes! - Bear hug!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.20,0:19:40.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你本打算因为一件我们都\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait a- You were going to take
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.49,0:19:42.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没做过的事情  而不让我们过圣诞节吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Christmas away for something that none of us did?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.96,0:19:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞节意味着放下过去朝前看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, um, Christmas is about moving forward.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.67,0:19:47.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没听过那个说法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've never heard that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.10,0:19:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实  亲爱的  你似乎是信口开河的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, honey, you did kinda shoot your mouth off.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.13,0:19:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还说我们是撒谎精\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You called us all liars.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.84,0:19:54.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你就是那样说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, you did, and then...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.05,0:19:59.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们别越说越起劲了  是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's not all get worked up. I made a mistake!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.39,0:20:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我犯错了  人难免会犯错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made a mistake. And people make mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.98,0:20:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但人们会弥补犯下的错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And they make up for those mistakes-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.30,0:20:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过  带全家人去意大利来弥补\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by... taking their family to Italy!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.36,0:20:16.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.82,0:20:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-迪兰能一起去吗  -当然  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can Dylan come? - Yeah! Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.41,0:20:25.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想来点鸡腿肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who wants some dark meat?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.54,0:20:29.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年的这个时候  我们就会经常谈论传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We talk a lot about tradition this time of year.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.25,0:20:31.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我们深爱着自己的传统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But as much as we love our traditions,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.05,0:20:34.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有时候我们最美好的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}sometimes our best memories come
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.16,0:20:37.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却来自最颠覆传统的时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from the times that are the most untraditional.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.34,0:20:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻帽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Inocente!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.22,0:20:44.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们记得爸妈发狂的那一年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We remember the year Mom and Dad went crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.60,0:20:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们记得圣诞老人打了颂歌者的那一年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We remember the year Santa punched out the caroler.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.11,0:20:56.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对我来说  今年是让"传统"这个词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But for me, this was the year that the word "Tradition"...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.11,0:20:58.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得更有意义的一年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}got a lot bigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.80,0:21:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.26,0:21:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.07,0:21:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被你整了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got me again.

