[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.09,0:03:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.09,0:03:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.09,0:03:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第六集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.14,0:00:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  伙计  该上学了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go, buddy. Schooltime.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.45,0:00:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  如果你待会和你闺蜜有约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, and Gloria, if you want to get together with the girls later,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.40,0:00:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以自己看看橄榄球赛什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could just, you know, watch the football game or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.13,0:00:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实他就是想看橄榄球赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That means he wants to watch a football game.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.17,0:00:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是和你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not talking to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.63,0:00:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要喝咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you drinking coffee for anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.63,0:00:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的文化习俗  我是哥伦比亚人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's my culture. I'm Colombian.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.92,0:00:22.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  这些法式吐司\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah? What part of Colombia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.46,0:00:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是哥伦比亚的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are those French toaster sticks from?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.66,0:00:26.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我不太确定你今天能看比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Babe, I'm not sure about the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.25,0:00:28.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为全家人都要过来烧烤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The whole family's coming over for the barbecue.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.60,0:00:30.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是今天吗  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's today? - See.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.52,0:00:32.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是俄亥俄州赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the Ohio State game.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.35,0:00:34.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样  每个人都能看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So? Everybody can watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.36,0:00:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢和不懂球的人一起看比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't like watching the game with people who don't know the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七嘴八舌乱指点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.70,0:00:39.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也会乱指点我的橄榄球比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You talk at my football games.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.37,0:00:40.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  你那个是足球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For one thing, it's called soccer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你们队整个赛季只得了两分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your team scored two goals all season.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:44.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我随便说也不会冒风险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not taking a big risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.91,0:00:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底喝了多少啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How much of this did you drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.91,0:00:51.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶了我吧  我今天得去攀绳呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give me a break. I have to climb a rope today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.96,0:00:54.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈妈  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Mom. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.32,0:00:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我40块钱吃午饭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I have $40 for lunch?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.82,0:00:58.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,40块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Forty dollars?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.92,0:01:01.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-学校还让我们买本书  -什么书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I also need a book for school. - What book?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.00,0:01:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想买条裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want a dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.60,0:01:07.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你撒谎撒得多失败吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you have any idea what a bad liar you are?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.42,0:01:08.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更担心的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd be more worried that
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.51,0:01:10.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她连一本书的名字都想不出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she couldn't come up with a single book title.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.82,0:01:12.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  快点  我们要迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, come on. We're late.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.00,0:01:16.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是第一次里外前后全都穿反了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm, there's a first- inside out and backwards.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.08,0:01:17.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少他没把衣服塞进...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At least it isn't zipped into his...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.90,0:01:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  真塞进去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. There it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.23,0:01:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人是"读书大智慧"  也有人是"市井小聪明"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, there's book smart, and then there's street smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.13,0:01:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  卢克属于第三类怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and then there's Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.43,0:01:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是  他只是好奇心重  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, he's just... He's just curious. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.81,0:01:31.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有着科学家的头脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's got this almost scientific mind...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.06,0:01:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及对知识的渴望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with a thirst for knowledge.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.24,0:01:36.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他像小爱因斯坦一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's like this little Einstein.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.58,0:01:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人会问"为什么"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Some people ask, "Why?"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.60,0:01:42.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卢克会问"为什么不呢"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke asks, "Why not?"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.85,0:01:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经常问"为什么"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I ask "Why?" a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.23,0:01:50.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在十码区  现在是五码区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're at the ten. We're at the five.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.59,0:01:53.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到达一码  爸爸  我们触地得分啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're at the one. Daddy, we're scoring a touchdown!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.14,0:01:54.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  小心别弄伤孩子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, please... please don't spike our baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.24,0:01:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么她穿得像汉堡神偷公仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is she dressed like the Hamburglar?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.83,0:01:59.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是裁判\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's a referee.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.67,0:02:01.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今晚一定要去我爸那里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do... Do we even have to go to my dad's tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.88,0:02:04.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在开玩笑吗  今晚是俄亥俄州赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me? We're playing Ohio State.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.27,0:02:06.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收集古董钢笔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I collect antique fountain pens.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.02,0:02:08.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很擅长日式插花技术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm quite adept at Japanese flower arrangement-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.66,0:02:09.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"花道"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}ikebana-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.51,0:02:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我曾是伊利诺伊大学的首发进攻内锋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I was a starting offensive lineman at the University of Illinois.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.29,0:02:15.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊讶吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.52,0:02:17.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不喜欢橄榄球  -你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't like football. - You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.30,0:02:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为维持恋情的一方面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought part of being in a relationship...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.22,0:02:21.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要爱屋及乌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was pretending to enjoy your partner's interests.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.07,0:02:24.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我真的喜欢做腌菜吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think I really loved home pickle-making?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.23,0:02:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  因为你确实喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, 'cause you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.60,0:02:26.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就喜欢一周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For a week,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.48,0:02:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到后来别人都以为我们是到处送腌菜的怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until we became the weird guys who gave everybody pickles.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.91,0:02:31.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马文  谢谢邀请我们到你温馨的家来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank you, Marvin, for inviting us into your lovely home.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.72,0:02:33.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  请收下这包腌菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here. Would you care for a sack of pickles?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.62,0:02:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was charming.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.37,0:02:36.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是腌菜工  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We were picklers, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.92,0:02:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you know what? Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.95,0:02:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你的小剪刀待在家里吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stay home with your little jagged scissors.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.72,0:02:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以继续弄你的剪贴簿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe catch up on your scrapbooking.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.76,0:02:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你也喜欢剪贴簿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come... You loved scrapbooking.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.37,0:02:45.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有吗  米奇尔  我有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did I, Mitchell? Did I?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.57,0:02:48.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  别以为搞个双重反问就是真的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop. Don't do the "Double question to prove a point" thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.16,0:02:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌别人那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate it when people do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.61,0:02:51.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  米奇尔  是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you, Mitchell? Do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.74,0:02:52.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了  莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop, Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.94,0:03:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  我们马上过来  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No problem. We'll be right down. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.24,0:03:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, honey. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.45,0:03:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校刚刚来电话了  卢克打架了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The school just called. Luke got in a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.09,0:03:23.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  他还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, geez. Is he okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.01,0:03:25.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没事  但老师想要我们去一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, he's fine, but they want us to come down there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.13,0:03:28.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在哪里  -我在带人看房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where are you? - I'm showing a house.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.24,0:03:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What house?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.59,0:03:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在打高尔夫球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm golfing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.74,0:03:39.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是那个叫德卡斯的小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bet it was that Durkas kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.27,0:03:40.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌那个小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate that kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.12,0:03:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是他突然挑衅卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He probably jumped on Luke
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.37,0:03:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而卢克只是反抗而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Luke just fought back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.82,0:03:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那小孩真讨厌  -他曾经取笑我的头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Kid's a menace. - He made fun of my hair once.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.34,0:03:46.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  他的家长可能在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shh. The parents are probably in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.18,0:03:48.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是睡觉把头发睡乱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I slept on it funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.20,0:03:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像他没有过一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like that never happened to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.99,0:03:50.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.90,0:03:53.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这里干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.79,0:03:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两个笨蛋在一起打架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These two knuckleheads were fighting each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.95,0:03:58.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -幸好是你啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - Could've been worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.35,0:04:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没准备好今天面对德卡斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was not ready to face Durkas today.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.00,0:04:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.65,0:04:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显  在操场上发生了骂人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, apparently there was some name-calling
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.11,0:04:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和斗殴的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and shoving on the playground.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.43,0:04:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师把他们分开的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By the time a teacher separated them,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.23,0:04:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克正坐在曼尼的胸上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke was sitting on Manny's chest.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.53,0:04:12.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卢克  那可不像你啊  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, that's not like you. - Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.51,0:04:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你是卢克的爸爸吗  -外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're Luke's father? - Grandfather.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.53,0:04:17.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那么曼尼的爸爸是  -哈维尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So Manny's father is... - Javier.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.89,0:04:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个疯子  就是从他身上遗传到的暴脾气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Crazy guy. That's where he gets his fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.05,0:04:23.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  你是  -他是我们的儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, you're... - He's our son.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.07,0:04:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的外孙  -我是他女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And my grandson. - I'm his daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.32,0:04:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那么你是  -他小舅舅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So you're... - His uncle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.24,0:04:30.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要再敢这么说  我还会坐到你的胸上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop saying that or I'll sit on your chest again.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.15,0:04:32.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  打架就是因为这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ho! Wait a second. Is that what this was all about?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.58,0:04:33.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直说我是他的外甥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He keeps calling me his nephew.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.76,0:04:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是我的外甥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are my nephew.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.82,0:04:36.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-闭嘴  -好了  好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Shut up! - Okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.75,0:04:40.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了  你们似乎是一家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm getting the sense that you're all related, uh, somehow.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.47,0:04:42.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  也许你们最好能回家自己解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So it's probably best if you work this out at home...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.31,0:04:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样孩子们就能回去上课了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so the boys can go back to class, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.94,0:04:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们很生气你们这样  小伙子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we're not happy about this, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.65,0:04:49.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是成熟的年轻小伙的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is not how mature young men behave.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.81,0:04:51.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这便条给"帕斯沃"老师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here's your note for Miss Passwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.12,0:04:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Passwater  意译为递水]
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.16,0:04:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不担心  他们都是好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I wouldn't worry. They're good kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.74,0:05:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是当某个孩子比较怪异时  会有点难处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just tough when one kid's a little different.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.56,0:05:02.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.75,0:05:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到她那么说了  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You heard how she said that, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.83,0:05:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"是的"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.17,0:05:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得卢克是怪异的那个  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She thought Luke was the weird one. Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.95,0:05:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她家孩子把自己的头卡在家具里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Her kid gets his head stuck in the furniture,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.75,0:05:14.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好意思说曼尼怪异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and Manny is the different one.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.35,0:05:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来告诉你什么怪异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will tell you what's weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.19,0:05:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的孩子并不怪异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our son is not weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.22,0:05:17.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪异的是她的孩子抹须后水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's weird is that her kid wears aftershave
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.84,0:05:19.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且打扮得像个伯爵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and dresses like a count.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.32,0:05:21.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们别请他们过来烧烤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think we should cancel with them for the barbecue.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.56,0:05:24.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们不去  只会把问题越闹越大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If we cancel, it'll just make this a bigger deal than it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.54,0:05:27.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让卢克和曼尼多相处一下对他们两个都好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It'll be good for Luke and Manny to spend some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.47,0:05:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许对你和歌洛莉亚也好  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Might be good for you and Gloria too. - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.96,0:05:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一直对我有意见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's always had a problem with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.25,0:05:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我该找出是什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I'm gonna find out what it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.00,0:05:37.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你最不该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the worst thing you could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.33,0:05:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当没发生过  忍忍就过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just sweep it under the rug.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.29,0:05:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可不是个"忍者"  -听我的没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm not a sweeper. - Trust me on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.49,0:05:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你们俩得谈谈这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you two need to talk it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.57,0:05:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟她没什么好说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't have anything to say to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.37,0:05:47.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才是有问题的那个  不是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's the one with the problem, not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.26,0:05:48.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底向着谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whose side are you on?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.58,0:05:50.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我的女儿  你是我的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's my daughter. You're my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.20,0:05:52.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们先理清重点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's remember what's important here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.74,0:05:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橄榄球赛马上就开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a football game on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.51,0:05:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想我的两个女孩相处得不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just hate it when my two girls aren't getting along.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.27,0:06:01.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么成你的女孩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How exactly is she your girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.37,0:06:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为聚会准备了一点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got a few things for the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.70,0:06:09.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉准备好要走了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is Lily ready to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.31,0:06:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  她准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah, yeah. She's ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.40,0:06:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.57,0:06:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很担心C·J·海托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just really worried about C.J. Hightower.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.29,0:06:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他脚踝受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}With the bad ankle,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.67,0:06:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他要怎么跑完三角线路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know how he's gonna run his corner routes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.55,0:06:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我男友刚刚说了什么呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did my boyfriend just say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.88,0:06:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听了你之前说的  我同意你的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, I heard what you said, and I thought, yes,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.22,0:06:28.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该多了解一下橄榄球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should try to learn more about football.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.80,0:06:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么做真是成熟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is very mature of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.93,0:06:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  橄榄球迷都能学会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figure, if football fans can learn it,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.90,0:06:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那能有多难呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how hard can it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.11,0:06:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你最聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's very elitist of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.75,0:06:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才刚刚起步  好不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm taking baby steps here, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.03,0:06:40.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我真的很期待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm actually- I'm really looking forward to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.38,0:06:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这不仅仅是比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause it's not just the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.70,0:06:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现场彩旗招展  锣鼓喧天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's-It's the bands and the drama, the pageantry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.78,0:06:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了还有球队的吉祥物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't forget about the team mascots.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.21,0:06:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们戴"宽领带"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They wear ascots?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.63,0:06:50.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  是"吉祥物"  有个"M"开头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Mascots. With an "M."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.91,0:06:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是在外人面前你就丢脸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That could have been very embarrassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.96,0:06:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.85,0:06:55.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I straight?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.10,0:07:01.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道你是直男还是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not sure what you are right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.21,0:07:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How ya doin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.80,0:07:05.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-外公好  -小美女好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Gramps. - Hi, beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.36,0:07:07.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  菲尔  见到你真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Phil. Good to see ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.00,0:07:08.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我猜猜  比赛开始了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me guess. Game's on?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.58,0:07:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just started.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.88,0:07:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. For you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.11,0:07:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's nice to see you, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.99,0:07:15.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天两次哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah! Two times today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.86,0:07:17.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抱两次好啊  -菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, well... - Uh, Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.46,0:07:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的意思是我们今天见了两次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She means we've seen them two times today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.80,0:07:22.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家听着  吃的在那边  喝的在那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, everybody, the food's in there. The drinks are in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.34,0:07:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我进屋去了  -等等  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'll be in here. - Hold on, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.94,0:07:27.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们不该忽视明显存在的一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think we should address the elephant in the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.31,0:07:30.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  曼尼  都过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, Luke, Manny. Bring it in.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.31,0:07:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  聚在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Huddle up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.28,0:07:34.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像打橄榄球一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Football.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.76,0:07:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于今天在学校里发生的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now in light of what happened at school today,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.59,0:07:40.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有什么想说的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}do you have any feelings you'd like to express?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.68,0:07:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得现在是个合适的表达机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think this is the proper forum...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.47,0:07:45.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  得了吧  你们两个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For god's sakes. All right, both of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.30,0:07:48.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个家里  我们是欺负彼此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, in this family, do we kick and punch each other,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.41,0:07:49.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是关爱彼此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or do we love each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.72,0:07:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关爱彼此  这就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Love each other. That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.94,0:07:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进屋去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'II be in the den.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.36,0:07:59.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带了些甜点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I brought dessert.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.40,0:08:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.40,0:08:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也做了派\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I make pie too.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.85,0:08:06.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派再多也不嫌多  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can never have too many pies, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.22,0:08:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, whoa. Whoa.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.05,0:08:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家深呼吸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody take a deep breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.85,0:08:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们面对现实吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's think about getting real.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.19,0:08:13.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.08,0:08:14.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么说"菲尔  别这样"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why "Phil, no"?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:16.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔要干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is Phil doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.29,0:08:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just gonna say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.25,0:08:18.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩之间的紧张气氛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's tension between you two.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.89,0:08:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经弥漫出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bam. It's out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.40,0:08:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要宰了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.85,0:08:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他是对的  而且我们应该谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think he's right, and I think we should talk about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.98,0:08:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想说这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what I'm talkin' about...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.83,0:08:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们谈谈  这个事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you two talking... about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.26,0:08:37.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢橄榄球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like football.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.84,0:08:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉很讨厌  这很奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley hates it, which is weird
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.96,0:08:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为里面全是男孩  也不必看书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because it's all boys... and there's no reading required.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.21,0:08:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  她每天早上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know that she spends
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.15,0:08:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少花45分钟弄她的头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at least 45 minutes every morning doing her hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.97,0:08:48.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且有的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then sometimes...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.50,0:08:50.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊  伊利诺伊队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go, Illini!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.65,0:08:52.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊  快冲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go! Right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.86,0:08:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我要和迪克·布特库斯一起看比赛了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Looks like I gotta watch the game with Dick Butkus.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.19,0:08:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[音同Dick Butt-kiss意思为鸡鸡-屁股相亲\N米奇以为是讽刺同性恋的做爱方式]
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.17,0:08:57.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  别这样  太冒犯人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad! Dad, come on. That's offensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.08,0:08:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  那人是伊利诺斯州\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, he's one of the greatest linebackers
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.99,0:09:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最棒的中后卫球员之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to ever play at Illinois...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.00,0:09:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是我自己的偶像之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and one of my personal heroes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.64,0:09:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道他的名字真是"亲屁股"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And his name is "Butt-kiss"?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.90,0:09:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're just choosing to...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.74,0:09:06.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.37,0:09:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  我以为你恐同呢  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, I thought you were being homophobic. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.40,0:09:11.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们有一整晚要相处呢  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We got all night. - Yes, we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.46,0:09:13.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要和我们一起看吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you joining us here? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.12,0:09:15.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  你知道吗  他正在钻研呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you know what? He's been studying up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.12,0:09:17.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说  我有点担心C·J·海托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gotta tell ya, I'm a little worried about C.J. Hightower.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.79,0:09:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧  他脚踝受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right? With the bad ankle?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.20,0:09:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好奇他怎么能完成三角线路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm wondering how he's gonna run his corner routes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.20,0:09:22.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海托不上场  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hightower's out. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.45,0:09:26.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那谁来跑三角线路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Then who is gonna run the corner routes?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.04,0:09:27.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来告诉你谁不会上吧  比林斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll tell you who it won't be- Billings.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太明显了  他在坐牢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's low. He's in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.33,0:09:32.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  他不会上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, wow. Yeah. Then no.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.02,0:09:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双侧边锋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Double tight end,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.64,0:09:35.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四分卫要冲到左边了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's gonna be a quarterback roll-out to the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.42,0:09:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们要成功了  -不可能  相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- They're gonna run it. - No, trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.54,0:09:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抢到位置了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's got the slot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.66,0:09:40.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到达阵区了  触地得分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In the end zone! Touchdown!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.11,0:09:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真幸运  也许  他们该考虑下闪电战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lucky call. Maybe they, uh, should've considered blitzing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.17,0:09:45.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪电战没用的  一边儿凉快去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Blitzing wouldn't have helped them. Get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.29,0:09:48.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  闪电战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, gosh. Blitzing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.84,0:09:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  我对橄榄球的兴趣突然消失殆尽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, my interest in football ended as suddenly and dramatically...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.29,0:09:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像《西区故事》在高潮时戛然而止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}as the climax of West Side Story.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.96,0:09:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个音乐剧迷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a musical theater fan.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.06,0:09:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊讶吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.14,0:10:01.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  说实话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. The truth?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.72,0:10:04.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候我觉得你不喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I sometimes feel like you don't like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.68,0:10:07.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门见山  重磅出击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Powerful, powerful stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.53,0:10:10.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  告诉我们你怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire? Tell us how that makes you feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.58,0:10:12.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时此刻  我感到怒火中烧啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right now, I'm feeling a lot of anger.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.12,0:10:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别跟我说  跟她说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, don't tell me. Tell her.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.45,0:10:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  我现在很生菲尔的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, right now, I'm really angry at Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.17,0:10:18.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑题了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's respect the process.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.49,0:10:21.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, I don't know
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.85,0:10:23.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你觉得我不喜欢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why you think I don't like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.32,0:10:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时  你在我面前会摆出那种表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes when you see me, you make that face.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What face?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.49,0:10:27.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.52,0:10:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我才没做过那种表情呢  -我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I do not make a face like that. - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.29,0:10:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那可是克莱尔的招牌表情  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That is so Claire. - Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.22,0:10:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见没  她对谁都那副表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? She does that with everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.02,0:10:35.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经习惯成自然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just her face.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.21,0:10:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是那种表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's not just the face.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.60,0:10:38.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从最开始到现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From the beginning,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.32,0:10:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我和曼尼在这个家不受欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel like Manny and I are not welcome in this family.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.98,0:10:42.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也太疯狂了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is so crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.40,0:10:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  一点都不疯狂  是我的真实感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's not so crazy. It's how I feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.04,0:10:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你那么想  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am sorry if you feel that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.60,0:10:54.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉  从我见到你的那一刻起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really am, because from the moment I met you,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.73,0:10:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想让你融入到我们当中来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have tried to make you feel comfortable with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.22,0:11:00.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这只是我自己胡思乱想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think it's all in my head?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.76,0:11:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  有点  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Kind- I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.90,0:11:06.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我们很欢迎你和曼尼加入我们家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, we really love having you and Manny in our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.68,0:11:07.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的  -真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:10.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你用不着这么有戒心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you don't have to be so defensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.47,0:11:13.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是有戒心  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I do that, don't I?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.10,0:11:14.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.53,0:11:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得应该拥抱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm feeling a hug.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.11,0:11:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想说三人群抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was thinking group hug,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.88,0:11:23.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但这也不错  -我要能去的话就去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But this is nice. - I'd be there if I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.07,0:11:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这还有人搂搂抱抱呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. There's hugging.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.94,0:11:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  不打电话会死啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, get off the phone already.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.34,0:11:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where did you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.87,0:11:28.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见他说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You heard him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.86,0:11:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说"一边凉快去"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He said, "Get outta here."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.84,0:11:31.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你真像个娇弱的小姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. You're such a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.58,0:11:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  反正我也想要喝杯啤酒的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad- I was coming to get a beer anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.64,0:11:35.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你道歉真有诚意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice apology.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice beer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.02,0:11:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  两个壮小伙来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, there are the little roustabouts.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.35,0:11:43.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看来你们和好如初了  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You look like you patched things up pretty good, huh? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.76,0:11:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能从孩子身上学到许多东西啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, we can learn so much from the children.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.14,0:11:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在再回头想想打架的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bet it seems kind of silly now
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.48,0:11:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是觉得当时很蠢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what you were even fighting about, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.06,0:11:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我笑他的口音  -什么口音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I made fun of his accent. - What accent?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.16,0:11:55.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我笑他每天的午餐都一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made fun of him for having the same thing for lunch every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.98,0:12:00.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我取笑他  因为他妈妈以前是挖煤的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made fun of him because his mom used to dig coal.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.94,0:12:01.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.89,0:12:03.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说你是个挖煤工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He said you were a coal digger.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:05.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我觉得该换个话题了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I think we can move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.99,0:12:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说我是个"挖煤工"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who said I was a coal digger?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.80,0:12:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what my mom told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.50,0:12:10.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是挖煤工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's a coal digger?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.98,0:12:11.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  他听错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetheart, he heard it wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.88,0:12:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那叫"淘金工"[傍大款]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's "Gold digger."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.78,0:12:14.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得过一会再打给你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna have to call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.26,0:12:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不记得说过这话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really do not think that I remember ever saying that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.95,0:12:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  你在车里这么说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you said in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.10,0:12:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你圣诞节这么说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You said it at Christmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.63,0:12:23.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还在墨西哥餐厅这么说过  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You said it in the Mexican restaurant- - Okay,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.33,0:12:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖儿子  你每天丢三落四\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mr. "Leaves His Sweatshirts at School Every Day...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.94,0:12:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天却记忆如神  真谢谢你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Suddenly Remembers Everything," Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.98,0:12:30.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说是我自己胡思乱想  哈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it was all in my head, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.70,0:12:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  歌洛莉亚  其实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, listen. Gloria, it was...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.88,0:12:35.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是一年前的事了  那时我还不了解你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like, a year ago, before I knew you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:36.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真行啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice going.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.94,0:12:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得我妈和我姐吵架了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now my mom and my sister are fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.73,0:12:45.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我说了众人都想说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I say something that everybody else is thinking,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.89,0:12:47.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是意味着我很刻薄呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}does that make me a mean person?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.49,0:12:50.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说我很勇敢呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or does it make me a brave person?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.39,0:12:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是一个有勇气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One who is courageous enough to
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.96,0:12:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶住压力  挺身而出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}stand up and-and say something...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.87,0:12:57.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在背后悄悄地说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}behind someone's back
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.06,0:12:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只敢在小孩面前说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to a 10-year-old.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.61,0:13:02.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在可是气疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she's pissed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.96,0:13:05.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  她甚至连房间都不愿意出了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. She wouldn't even come out of her room.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.82,0:13:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的非要说她是"傍大款的"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you really have to call her that- a gold digger?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.40,0:13:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  爸爸  那可是一年前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you know what, Dad? It was a year ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.43,0:13:14.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以人家自然而然会问啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it was a natural question to ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.27,0:13:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那么漂亮  那么性感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's a beautiful, hot woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.42,0:13:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却不那么  你懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you're not exactly, you know-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.35,0:13:21.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不那么什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not exactly what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.72,0:13:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  帮帮忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um- Mitchell, little help?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.94,0:13:26.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用  你说的挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You are doing great.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.46,0:13:29.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见了吧  所以说家事要忍着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, this is exactly why we sweep things under the rug-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.75,0:13:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样大家才不会受伤害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so people don't get hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.65,0:13:33.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是没错  但如果老是忍着憋着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, until you sweep too much under the rug.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.59,0:13:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矛盾就越积越多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then you got a lumpy rug.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.89,0:13:38.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矛盾爆发的危险也越大  也会惹祸上身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Creates a tripping hazard. You open yourself up to lawsuits.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.74,0:13:41.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岳父大人  你可以好长时间不眨眼啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boy, you can go a really long time without blinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.21,0:13:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  我是菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria? It's Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.73,0:13:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和你谈一会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I talk to you for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.13,0:13:56.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔总是说  "你要么是问题制造者"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire likes to say you can be part of the problem...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.05,0:13:59.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"要么就是问题解决者"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or part of the solution.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.14,0:14:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我则认为  解铃还须系铃人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I happen to believe that you can be both.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.97,0:14:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  克莱尔感到很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, Claire feels terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.52,0:14:08.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不你找她谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you talk to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.60,0:14:12.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  我知道她认为我是个挖煤的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? I know what she thinks- a coal digger.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她说的其实是傍大款的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know she's saying "Gold digger"?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.99,0:14:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.11,0:14:16.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道她这么说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I-I know she said that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.57,0:14:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那是很早以前的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that was a long time ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.35,0:14:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时她尚未真正了解你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}before she knew you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.10,0:14:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰是不是给我买好东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does Jay buy me nice things?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:24.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  当然了  全是好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes! Of course! All beautiful things.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.12,0:14:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这些  黄的  红的  蓝的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at this- yellow, red, blue.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.25,0:14:28.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五颜六色的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All the colors.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.67,0:14:30.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我没了这些就活不了了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think I can't live without this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.08,0:14:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿走啊  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take them away, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.77,0:14:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.82,0:14:37.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道你不穿内裤也没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we all know you'd be fine without underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:40.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我们知道你说的不是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, we know it's not about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.42,0:14:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我说的是我不被这个家庭所接纳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. It's about me not being accepted by my new family.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.64,0:14:46.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.71,0:14:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  听着  你是个大美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, look, you're a beautiful woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.10,0:14:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  你很有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In fact, you're probably one of those
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.28,0:14:52.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道自己是美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}beautiful women who doesn't even know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.21,0:14:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.49,0:14:55.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以克莱尔自然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So it's natural
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.96,0:14:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会对你和她爸的关系产生联想啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for Claire to wonder about you and her dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.31,0:15:01.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个保护欲很强的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This family's very protective of each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.49,0:15:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还记得克莱尔第一次带我去她家的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I remember the first time Claire brought me home.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.69,0:15:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为杰会觉得我配得上他家千金吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think Jay thought I was good enough for his little girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.41,0:15:10.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会  但是过了一段时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No way. But over time,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.64,0:15:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他意识到我和他一样深爱着克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he realized that I loved Claire as much as he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.19,0:15:15.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与此同时  米奇把小卡带进家门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And by then, Mitch had brought Cam home,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.97,0:15:17.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相比之下我就是金龟婿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so I was golden.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.31,0:15:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔只是需要些时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire just needs a little time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.08,0:15:22.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  过段时间后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then, trust me,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.41,0:15:24.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就会成为你最亲的闺蜜了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she'll be the most loyal friend you've ever had.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.43,0:15:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是要走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not leaving, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.84,0:15:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道  现在这儿闹得有点不愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, there's kind of a lot of drama.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:34.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们深受折磨  -我问你们点事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So we're torn. - Let me ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.32,0:15:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你姐姐说歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your sister said that Gloria
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.85,0:15:38.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会喜欢上我这种样子的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}would never go for anybody who looked like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.37,0:15:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说  基本上  你们和女人差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, you guys basically are like women.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.55,0:15:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们喜欢男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you look at guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.87,0:15:47.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.79,0:15:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是在问我们  你是否有吸引力吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're seriously asking us if you're attractive?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道自己算不上高帅富\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I know I'm no Erik Estrada or anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.25,0:15:54.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是好奇罢了  -爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm just curious is all. - Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.12,0:15:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果我出现在同志酒吧  然后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So if I was in one of your bars and-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.02,0:16:00.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,播着经典老歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Righteous Brothers were on, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.25,0:16:02.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.12,0:16:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  和我搭讪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know, check me out?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.82,0:16:08.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  你快要毁了做基佬的情调了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, you're really close to ruining gay for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.13,0:16:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那好  无所谓  -杰  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right, fine. Whatever. - Jay. Jay, now listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.78,0:16:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  我只是觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think it's- I just think it's
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.19,0:16:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一个儿子对父亲这么说实在太诡异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a little weird for a son to say this to his father.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.94,0:16:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我声明一下  我觉得你超性感的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But for the record, I think you're smokin' hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.30,0:16:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.67,0:16:21.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  百分百肯定  你绝对是我的菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, 100%. You're totally my type.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.21,0:16:22.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你既危险  又触手可及\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're dangerous, you're getable,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.42,0:16:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你荷包里又装着鼓鼓的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you have a little "Cashola" In your pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.19,0:16:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长相  身材  还是整体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Face, body, the whole-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.28,0:16:30.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从头到脚都特帅  我觉得  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The whole kit and caboodle, I think. Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.14,0:16:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那有7分吗  -9分  绝对的9分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What about a seven? Nine. For sure, nine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.34,0:16:36.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但你肯定知道的  -我有点低估自己了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But you knew that. - I might have lowballed a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.73,0:16:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是还有比赛呢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, isn't there a game on?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.41,0:16:42.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他太敏感  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Touchy. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.06,0:16:48.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  拜托  我们好好谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria? Come on, let's- let's talk about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.83,0:16:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可见过她破门而入过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've seen her kick in a door before.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.42,0:17:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我丈夫和你说了什么  或者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what my husband is saying to you or...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.52,0:17:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他浑身都是你的内裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why he's covered in your underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.84,0:17:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很显然我是看上他的钱了呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Obviously I'm trying to seduce him for his money.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.67,0:17:09.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就是这样的人嘛  对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause that's what I do, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.71,0:17:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我究竟要付出什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do I have to give back...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.56,0:17:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能得到大家的信任啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so that everyone trusts me? Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.57,0:17:17.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-耳环吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- These earrings? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.03,0:17:19.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是什么  手镯吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? This bracelet? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.74,0:17:21.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还是我的新裙子  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- My new dress? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.73,0:17:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没出声是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't respond because...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.75,0:17:32.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实关键不在于我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this shouldn't be about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.10,0:17:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在于你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It should be about you...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.91,0:17:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你  好好谈  一谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}talking to you... about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.70,0:17:43.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil? Honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.45,0:17:44.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  不用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.38,0:17:47.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.94,0:17:52.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该说些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know what to say
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.06,0:17:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能说我真的非常非常抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}except for that I am really, really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.97,0:17:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就告诉我一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just tell me one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.70,0:18:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于我和你爸的关系  你到底怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do you really feel that I'm with your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.14,0:18:01.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, well-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.35,0:18:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  一开始  我很难接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honestly, at first, it was hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.87,0:18:06.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  谁都不会期望有一天醒来后发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, you don't expect to wake up one morning...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.42,0:18:09.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多了一个比自己还年轻性感的后妈吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with a new mom who looks like she fell off a mud flap.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.44,0:18:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我正慢慢去习惯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But... I'm getting used to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.60,0:18:16.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  重要的是你能让他幸福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the important thing is you make him happy,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.62,0:18:19.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的各种方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which you do in- in so many ways,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.13,0:18:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五颜六色的方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so many colors.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.57,0:18:25.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们和好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are we okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.13,0:18:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没  -没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - No?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.32,0:18:31.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我在所有人面前出丑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You embarrassed me in front of everyone downstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.88,0:18:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  要我这么轻易就忘掉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, I'm supposed just to forget about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.11,0:18:35.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你想要怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you want me to do-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.48,0:18:37.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我也出丑  这样我们就扯平了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just embarrass myself so we're even?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.93,0:18:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳进泳池\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go jump in the pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.17,0:18:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Go jump in a lake 直译为跳湖  俗语  让某人离远点]
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.70,0:18:41.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是让我离你远点  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you mean go jump in a lake. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.43,0:18:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是让你穿着衣服跳进泳池\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go jump in the pool with your clothes on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.61,0:18:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样我就知道你的歉意了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then I know you're sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.23,0:18:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会跳的  歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna do that, Gloria.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.45,0:18:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那我也不会原谅你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Then I won't forgive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.16,0:18:53.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来个定位球  我们就输了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now a field goal beats us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.24,0:18:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩和好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you guys work that out?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.85,0:18:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多了  歌洛莉亚想让我跳进泳池\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Almost. Gloria just wants me to jump in the pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.88,0:18:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那好吧  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay then. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.85,0:19:03.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们咋就不来个突破  或者请求暂停啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If they could get a pass rush on 'em, something, a break.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.83,0:19:10.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太赞了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is so awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:12.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我妈浑身湿透很难看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. Mom does not look good wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.44,0:19:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚  这真有必要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria, is this really necessary?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.70,0:19:17.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  没事  如果我跳进泳池\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, it's fine. It's fine. If I need to jump in this water...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.52,0:19:19.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能证明我对歌洛莉亚的歉意  那我就跳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to prove to Gloria how sorry I am, I will do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.97,0:19:21.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.75,0:19:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来真的吗  你就不拦我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're serious? You're not gonna stop me?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.43,0:19:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干嘛要拦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would I do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.57,0:19:27.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我已经站这了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I am standing here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.11,0:19:29.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经证明了我的诚意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am showing you my willingness to-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.00,0:19:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.18,0:19:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你高兴了吧  -没错  我原谅你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you happy? - Yes! I forgive you!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.89,0:19:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拉我一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then give me your hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.26,0:19:44.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这招早就烂大街了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's the oldest trick in the book.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.87,0:19:46.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她要把你也拉进池里  -我才不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She's gonna pull you in there. - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.04,0:19:48.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我来帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.18,0:19:54.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有趣  但同时也给我们上了一课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is funny, but this is also a teaching moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.49,0:19:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吧  -好好想想  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah! - Think about...No!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.50,0:20:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大炸弹来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cannonball!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.48,0:20:10.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向后传球  失误了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The snap! Fumble!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.03,0:20:12.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会传球失误呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could he fumble that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.52,0:20:13.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪中卫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Center blew the snap.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.41,0:20:14.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我最讨厌这么说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what?I hate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.47,0:20:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前就是中卫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I played center,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.22,0:20:17.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是四分卫笨手笨脚  却让我背黑锅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I always got blamed for a quarterback's clumsy hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.59,0:20:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当过四分卫  这可能确实是你的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I was a quarterback, and it was probably your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.92,0:20:21.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果四分卫把手的位置放正确了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's impossible to fumble the ball...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.85,0:20:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传球怎么可能会失误呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when the quarterback has the proper hand placement.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.17,0:20:27.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要有女性认为老爸有吸引力那就太诡异了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's weird to think of a woman being sexually attracted to Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.12,0:20:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你知道什么才诡异吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you wanna hear weird?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.91,0:20:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡说他会在同志酒吧找老爸搭讪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam said he'd pick up dad at a gay bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.29,0:20:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唱的哪出啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh. How did that come up?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.26,0:20:34.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯  我正想忘记这事呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm, I'm really trying to block it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.02,0:20:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As far as I'm concerned,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.89,0:20:36.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸老妈也就上过两次床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom and Dad had sex two times.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.74,0:20:38.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Agreed.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.33,0:20:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  把你的手放到这上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, get your hands up there
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.90,0:20:41.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你要把我举起来一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like you're lifting me off the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.46,0:20:43.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我合为一体  杰  这就成了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Be one with me, Jay. There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.71,0:20:45.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不想吃点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you wanna get something to eat?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.38,0:20:46.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恶心得什么都吃不下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am never eating again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.74,0:20:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧传那该死的球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just snap the damn thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.61,0:20:51.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美  就是有点疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Perfect. That one kinda hurt.

