[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.09,0:02:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.09,0:02:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.09,0:02:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第八集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.50,0:00:06.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  要修下楼梯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah- Fix that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.70,0:00:14.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-早上好  -人家还在睡觉呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Morning! - I'm still sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.03,0:00:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-结婚纪念日快乐  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy anniversary. - Hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.41,0:00:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们还说我们不能长久  -对呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And they said we wouldn't last. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.29,0:00:23.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁说的  -你看你  太萌了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who said that? - Oh, look at you. You're cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.96,0:00:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快点  打开看看  -你又搞啥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go ahead. Open it. - What have you done?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.96,0:00:29.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  没什么  没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing. Something. Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.21,0:00:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-立体镜哇  -看看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's a View- Master. - Look inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们的相片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, it's us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.89,0:00:37.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我们多年轻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at how young we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.22,0:00:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你那时候烫的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God, that perm.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.81,0:00:41.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  那发型衬托出了我的脸型\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, it really framed my face.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.85,0:00:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么有个手镯的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is there a picture of a bracelet?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.27,0:00:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈  有可能搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Huh. Must be some kind of a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.73,0:00:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是什么玩意儿啊  -菲尔  不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What the heck is that? - Phil, you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.73,0:00:51.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你该不会  -有吗  有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What did - Did he, did he?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.22,0:00:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.90,0:00:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太漂亮了  亲爱的  我太喜欢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's beautiful. Oh, sweetie, I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.95,0:00:58.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  该看给你的礼物了  -该我啦  哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, your turn. - My turn? Where is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.33,0:01:00.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-梳妆柜上面  -哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's on the bureau. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.33,0:01:02.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然没看到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm surprised I didn't see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.50,0:01:06.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在哪  -就那儿  红色信封\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Where? - It's there. The red envelope.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.38,0:01:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  就  贺卡吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. So - - card?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.84,0:01:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你猜错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. That's where you're wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.23,0:01:15.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始亢奋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am so excited.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.38,0:01:19.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  优惠券\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. Coupons for...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.47,0:01:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费5次拥抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}five free hugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.14,0:01:24.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不喜欢吗  -开玩笑  喜欢死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You don't like it? - Are you kidding me? I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.60,0:01:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太有创意了  拥抱优惠券\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's so creative. Coupons for hugs,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.72,0:01:27.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实本来就不要钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which are usually free.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.02,0:01:30.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样就看起来很正式  真心不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But this makes it official, which is so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.40,0:01:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很骄傲能想到如此绝妙的点子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was so proud of myself when I thought of it...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.65,0:01:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为完全不知道给你买什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you're impossible to buy for.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.74,0:01:37.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从来就没有想要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You never want anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.41,0:01:39.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...我想要的东西嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, things I want:
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.41,0:01:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器狗  夜视镜  吸虫器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Robot dog, night- vision goggles, bug vacuum,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.24,0:01:45.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GPS手表  石头样子的音箱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}G.P.S. Watch, speakers that look like rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.12,0:01:47.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱我老婆  但她送礼物太他妈没谱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love my wife, but she sucks at giving gifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.21,0:01:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思我爆粗口了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry for the pay- channel language,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.06,0:01:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  哦  酸奶机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but- Oh, yogurt maker.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.29,0:01:51.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到我喜欢的那些东西就抓狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't not think of things I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.66,0:02:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道她什么时候需要换尿布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't tell if she needs a diaper change.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.46,0:02:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿了就该换了呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd think we'd be able to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.37,0:02:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  穿上这种尿布不好分辨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, with these diapers, it's hard to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.74,0:02:14.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三重防漏  -专业防漏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Triple leakage protection. - LeakLock.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.71,0:02:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特殊设计  呵护宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Contours to protect her little body.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.30,0:02:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严丝合缝  绝无渗漏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No gapping or chapping.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.47,0:02:20.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  你觉得我们是不是需要一晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, do you think that maybe we need a-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.47,0:02:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精彩夜生活  对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Night out. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.18,0:02:24.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  就是和一群成年人混几个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yes. Just a few hours with a couple of adults,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.60,0:02:26.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝点酒  不谈宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}few drinks, no baby talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.10,0:02:28.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会让我们成为更称职的家长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It'll make us better parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.74,0:02:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别诱惑我了  你的目的达到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop drilling. You've struck oil.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.14,0:02:32.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把孩子交给歌洛莉亚照看  然后出去玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll get Gloria to babysit. We're going out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.35,0:02:33.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沾了点口水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got some spittle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:35.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有吗  你觉得我们叫谁比较好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do I? You know who'd be fun to call?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.52,0:02:37.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-萨尔  -萨尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sal. - Sal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.53,0:02:39.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来跳舞狂欢吧  莉莉  好耶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, raise the roof, Lily. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.82,0:02:41.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要叫上萨尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're calling Sal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.31,0:02:44.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨尔绝对是我们在世上最好的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sal is our very best friend in the whole wide world.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.24,0:02:45.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们那么爱她的原因嘛...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The reason we love her so much...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.03,0:02:48.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是她绝对放得开  -绝对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- is she has absolutely no inhibitions. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.83,0:02:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还是在她喝酒之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that's before she starts drinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.30,0:02:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她一起玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hanging out with her...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.46,0:02:54.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像每天都是阿姆斯特丹周六狂欢夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is like an Amsterdam Saturday night every day of the week.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.13,0:02:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讽刺的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, ironically,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.21,0:02:59.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨尔被禁止进入阿姆斯特丹酒吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sal's not allowed back into Amsterdam.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.12,0:03:00.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪天都不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Any day of the week.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.17,0:03:02.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当然愿意照看宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course we would love to have the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.97,0:03:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的表哥表姐们今天晚上都要来过夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All the other cousins are sleeping over tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.43,0:03:06.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人多才热闹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The more, the merrier.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.82,0:03:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  晚上见  拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, see you tonight. Bye- bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.14,0:03:11.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉还来不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is Haley still coming?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.10,0:03:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是亲戚  再打她主意  我用水管喷你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're related. I will spray you with the hose.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.65,0:03:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的孙儿门都\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All the grandkids are
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.73,0:03:20.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来杰的夜间派对  算是家庭传统吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}coming over for Jay's Night. Family tradition.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.19,0:03:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都得穿睡衣  那是他们的最爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody wears P.J.'s, which they love.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.90,0:03:25.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的炒牛肉"杰"  其实就是炒牛肉酱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I make my famous sloppy Jays, which are really sloppy joes...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.70,0:03:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是我杰做的  他们也喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but made by Jay, which they love.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.58,0:03:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们一起看一个西部电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then we all watch a Western together,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.62,0:03:33.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不喜欢没关系  因为今夜以杰为中心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which they don't really care for, but hey, it's Jay's Night.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.79,0:03:36.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  安德鲁·艾德勒家里晚上有派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Mom, there's a party tonight at Andrew Adler's,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.67,0:03:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都要去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and everybody's gonna be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.42,0:03:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来不错  但是我有其他安排\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, that sounds like so much fun, but I have other plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.96,0:03:44.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有意思  但我指的是我要去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's hi- larious. But I'm talking about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.47,0:03:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真是"反常"啊  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That's unusual. - Honey,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.99,0:03:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你今晚要去外公家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you said you'd go to your grandfather's tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.68,0:03:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  所以才刚刚好嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, that's what's so perfect about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.10,0:03:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德鲁家离外公家只有几个街区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Andrew only lives, like, a couple blocks away from Grandpa's.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.51,0:03:53.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I figured that I could go-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.23,0:03:54.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你答应好了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, you made a commitment.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.81,0:03:58.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我真的想去嘛  还有每次我去外公那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I really want to go. Plus, every time I go over to Grandpa's,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.65,0:04:00.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼总是直勾勾地盯着我看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny just stares at me the whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.69,0:04:03.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可能如果你穿上胸罩  -艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Maybe if you wore a bra- - Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.45,0:04:05.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了嘛  我迫不及待想去外公那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? I can't wait to go to Grandpa's.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.78,0:04:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-家人对我来说就是一切  -因为你没朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Family means everything to me. - 'Cause you have no friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.29,0:04:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  因为我爱外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Because I love Grandpa.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.62,0:04:14.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一天比一天老了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he's getting older.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.71,0:04:17.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天知道他还能活多少年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who knows how many years he has left?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.13,0:04:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-外公要死了吗  -他们没跟你说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is Grandpa dying? - Didn't they tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.00,0:04:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  不要折磨你弟弟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, stop torturing your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.05,0:04:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你外公身体好得很\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Your grandfather is fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.72,0:04:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.01,0:04:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  会是谁呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hmm. Who could that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.26,0:04:32.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想到是某个特殊人物吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You expecting someone special?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.69,0:04:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.27,0:04:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还送花呀  -对不起嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Flowers too? - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.11,0:04:45.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道什么歉啊  这花太漂亮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, what are you apologizing for? They're gorgeous.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:49.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点过火  什么立体镜啊  手镯啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's too much. With the View- Master and the bracelet...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.20,0:04:51.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花啊  还有气球啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the flowers and the balloons-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.24,0:04:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有气球  -栓在你的汽车上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Balloons? - They're attached to your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.03,0:04:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想让你因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just don't want you to feel bad...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:57.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只准备了优惠券  心存愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about your little... coupons.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.00,0:04:59.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait a minute. You- You
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.16,0:05:01.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得你的礼物只有优惠券\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}thought the coupons were your only present?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.46,0:05:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-开什么玩笑  -难道不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you kidding me? - They aren't?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.59,0:05:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是  菲尔  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Oh, Phil, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.44,0:05:07.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们的结婚纪念日哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's our anniversary.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.55,0:05:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些优惠券只不过是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those coupons were just, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.03,0:05:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的前戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a fun little way to kick off the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.93,0:05:14.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真正的礼物晚上就到  你绝对会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your real present is coming tonight, and you're gonna love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.60,0:05:16.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.23,0:05:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.60,0:05:20.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没准备\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.61,0:05:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so screwed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.86,0:05:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个充满回忆的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, this place brings back so many memories.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.07,0:05:29.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦  天啊  -萨尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God! - Sal!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.20,0:05:33.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来  起来  快过来  熊抱抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get up! Get up! Get in here! Big bear!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.28,0:05:35.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小崽崽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my baby cub!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.54,0:05:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  看看你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. Look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.29,0:05:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  你们发现有什么不同了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! You guys notice anything different?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.05,0:05:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是头发变长了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your hair's longer, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.38,0:05:43.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是  -是不是洁牙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. - Did you get your teeth bleached?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.38,0:05:45.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  给你们点提示  波波波波大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Let me give you a little hint. Ba- boobs!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.01,0:05:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -哇噢  叹为观止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, my God. - Oh, wow. Those are sensational.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.88,0:05:51.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  你懂的  要感受一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, right? You wanna touch 'em?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.22,0:05:53.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽是基佬  也懂捏乳之妙  你没意见吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gay, not dead. Are you okay with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.89,0:05:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  你百香果代基里酒喝多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. You're drinking a passion- fruit daiquiri.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.51,0:05:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.02,0:05:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行了  快来吧  -抓奶龙爪手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, get in there. - I'm coming in.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.11,0:06:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉喜欢  那歌声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Lily likes that, that... singing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.28,0:06:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  那能让她放松  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes. It relaxes her. - Oh, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.83,0:06:20.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉肯定是聋子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So Lily's deaf.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.08,0:06:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小捣蛋们来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There are my little stinkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.84,0:06:26.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -外公好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Howdy. - Hi, Grandpa.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.59,0:06:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-进来  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on in. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.13,0:06:29.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哈罗  -哈罗哈罗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hola. - Hola, hola.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.88,0:06:31.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好呀  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, hello there, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.76,0:06:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消停消停吧  小色鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take it down a notch, Jethro.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.39,0:06:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好疯玩了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you guys ready for some fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.22,0:06:38.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.60,0:06:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  外公  你永远活在我的心中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you, grandpa, and I'm never gonna forget you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.19,0:06:43.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  快松开  小家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, okay. Back at ya, champ.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.81,0:06:47.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔喔  今天可是睡衣派对  你们的睡衣呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa, whoa, whoa. This is a pajama party. Where's your P.J.'s?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.23,0:06:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我包里面  我得跟你说件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, they're in my bag. I need to talk to you about something.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.53,0:06:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想和迪兰去参加派对  外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She wants to go to a party with Dylan, grandpa
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.33,0:06:53.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.91,0:06:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我朋友安德鲁·艾德勒家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's at my friend Andrew Adler's.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.24,0:06:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离这里只有几个街区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He lives three blocks from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.66,0:06:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-只有几步路  -对呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh. Walking distance. - Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.72,0:07:00.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实不好意思开口的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I wouldn't ask you this,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.39,0:07:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我喜欢来你这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because I love coming to your house,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.11,0:07:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这次派对很重要  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but it's kind of an important party, and I-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.79,0:07:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人请你去他家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Somebody invites you over,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.70,0:07:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总不能让人家难堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the last thing you wanna do is insult them.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:09.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是说呀  -很高兴我们达成了一致\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Exactly. - I'm glad we agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.97,0:07:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦天啊  那么容易  太爽了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. That was so easy. This is awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.36,0:07:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[杰那句话的意思是\N他请海莉来  海莉也不应该拒绝]
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.47,0:07:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真不明白刚刚是怎么回事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You really don't understand what just happened there, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.31,0:07:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海莉  换上睡衣  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- P.J.'s on, Haley! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.23,0:07:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自愿提供我的卧室让她换衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I would be happy to let her change in my room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.82,0:07:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会是谁呢  是你期待的某个特殊人物吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who could that be? Are you expecting someone special?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.53,0:07:36.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.16,0:07:39.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啊  我只知道门口有个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing. I just know that there's someone at the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.83,0:07:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇滚吧   菲尔·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Rock on, Phil Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.33,0:07:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘭  感动落泪吧你  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bam! Read it and weep, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.84,0:07:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦  -是伊茨啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh. - It's the Iz.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.18,0:07:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -斯班道芭蕾乐队的伊茨·拉法提啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who? - Izzy LaFontaine from Spandau Ballet.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.85,0:08:00.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自"死怕"什么的"迪茨·荡铁"耶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dizzy Dontaine from Spa, Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.70,0:08:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他反应过来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's got it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.56,0:08:04.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他反应过来了  只是有点懵  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's got it. He's just seriously freaking out. - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.19,0:08:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔爱死斯班道芭蕾了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil loves Spandau Ballet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.85,0:08:09.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们第一次接吻  车上放的歌就是《真实》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That song "True" was playing in the car the first time we kissed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.07,0:08:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们的定情之歌  所以我谷歌了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's our song. So I did some research,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.69,0:08:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现主吉他手就住在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}found out that the lead guitarist lives,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.28,0:08:16.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离这里大概40英里外的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like, 40 miles from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.36,0:08:17.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话簿里就有他电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was in the phone book.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.74,0:08:18.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛回到了80年代\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How '80s is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.87,0:08:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没喜欢过斯班道芭蕾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never liked Spandau Ballet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.62,0:08:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们的婚姻史上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our entire marriage,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.32,0:08:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就没提到过斯班道芭蕾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never once mentioned Spandau Ballet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.96,0:08:25.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至连名字都念得不对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I even pronouncing that right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.00,0:08:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天来给我们开私人演唱会的是吉他手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here to play a private concert for us is the guitarist-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.71,0:08:32.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是贝司手  -兼主唱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Bass player, actually. - And lead singer-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.88,0:08:35.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是伴唱  伴唱  -斯班道芭蕾的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, backup, backup. - Of Spandau Ballet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.22,0:08:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在理查德·米勒和马丁·坎普之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Between Richard Miller and Martin Kemp.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.04,0:08:38.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  是他们呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, those guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.18,0:08:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想死你们了  -哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I miss you two guys so much. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.56,0:08:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想死了  敬我们  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So, so much. To us. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.77,0:08:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-敬我们  -敬我们  三个火枪手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- To us. - To us, the Three Musketeers.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.36,0:08:56.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡波  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cabo! - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.61,0:08:59.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧混蛋  我们谈了很多次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, you bastards. We've been talking about it forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.41,0:09:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说定了  我们要去卡波  快点快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're doing it. We're going to Cabo. Let's do it. Let's do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.04,0:09:02.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.71,0:09:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊行啊  肯定会很有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yes. Yes. That would be fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.25,0:09:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有趣吗  开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fun? Are you joking?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.66,0:09:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特酒  加上你们  以及我的波波\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Margaritas, you guys, these guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.46,0:09:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会终身难忘的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna be epic.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.65,0:09:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们得找人照看下莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but we need to find someone for Lily.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.53,0:09:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, okay. Um,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.42,0:09:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去和女招待调情  你们给我多少钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}how much are you gonna pay me to go make out with the waitress?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.93,0:09:19.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  等等  是哪一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. Now, wait. Which one?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.16,0:09:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻的还是年老的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The old one or the young one?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.46,0:09:23.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻的10美元  年老的20\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ten for the young one, 20 for the old.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.51,0:09:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,30块钱都归我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am about to make 30 bucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.73,0:09:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我得问问莉莉的情况  -现在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm just gonna go check on Lily real quick. - Right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.14,0:09:30.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  马上就好  -但是我要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. It'll just take a second. - Well, I'm just-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.27,0:09:32.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们会错过我和黛西小姐调情的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're gonna miss me sluttin' it up with Driving Miss Daisy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.49,0:09:33.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[《为黛西小姐开车Driving Miss Daisy》为一部电影名]
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.82,0:09:34.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就一小下  -很快的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It'll just take a second. - Real fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.44,0:09:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们应该"弄死"宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should kill that baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.78,0:09:41.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -你们应该"联系"宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? - You should call the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.12,0:09:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱死你们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you guys so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.49,0:09:46.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她是不是说  -我怕怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did she just- - I'm scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.58,0:09:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没好牌了  -我想我有一对好牌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got nothing. - I think I have a very good pair.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.04,0:09:53.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你胸前那对是好牌  亲爱的  -我也弃牌了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You sure do, honey. - And I got squat.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.17,0:09:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没什么好牌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think I have anything either.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.96,0:09:57.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑呢  那是顺子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you kidding me? That's a straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.97,0:09:59.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -她赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - She wins.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.93,0:10:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You won.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.64,0:10:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我赢了  -真棒  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I win. - You got it, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.39,0:10:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我觉得该奖励自己一听汽水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I think I deserve a soda.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.52,0:10:07.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干得好  海莉  -你看见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Good job, Haley. - Did you see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她还说不会玩呢  -她都不知道自己赢牌了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "I don't know how to play." - She didn't even know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.65,0:10:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她应得的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, she deserves it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.02,0:10:16.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.03,0:10:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老天  你吓坏我了  -你怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Gee, you scared me. - How did you-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.82,0:10:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灯灭了  要是不马上换\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lightbulb went out. You don't change these right away,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.56,0:10:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头就懒的换了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you never get around to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.49,0:10:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.47,0:10:26.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在周围的一切"状况"  我看得一清二楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I can see everything that goes on around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.50,0:10:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很有这方面的经验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've had a little practice at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.54,0:10:32.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉的小花招我全部见识过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley wasn't throwing anything at me I hadn't seen before
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.29,0:10:34.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她妈妈和某人当年都耍过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from her mother and then some.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.67,0:10:36.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜没人能逃得出我的手掌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But nobody gets off The Rock.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.96,0:10:40.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  这首歌  在美国不怎么流行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right. Here's a track. Wasn't so popular in America.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.51,0:10:42.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在荷兰登上过排行榜的第六名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got to number six on the Netherlands charts though.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.84,0:10:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那整个夏天  我在阿姆斯特丹简直寸步难行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That whole summer I couldn't walk to the corner in Amsterdam
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.68,0:10:46.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是女歌迷围上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without mobs of birds coming up
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.64,0:10:48.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热情地要和我共饮泡泡鸡尾酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and asking me for the double bubble.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.52,0:10:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  快开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, just play it, I think. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.64,0:10:53.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他  他太棒了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's- He's awesome, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.60,0:10:54.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.59,0:10:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*今夜*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Tonight*
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.70,0:10:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*良宵*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*So right*
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.73,0:10:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*良宵*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*So right*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.09,0:11:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*爱人*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Lover*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.35,0:11:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你的爱人在等你的吻呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Phil, I think your lover wants a kiss from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.64,0:11:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.74,0:11:07.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  老兄  别像亲吻妹妹那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on, man. She's not your sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.34,0:11:08.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快深情长吻一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give her a proper snog.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.25,0:11:13.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.59,0:11:15.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那玩笑开得不好  不好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's a bad joke. Not funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.33,0:11:19.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妹妹因为糖尿病并发症失去了一条腿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My sister lost her feet to complications from diabetes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.32,0:11:21.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你倒杯水吧  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Can I get you some water there, guy, or-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.01,0:11:24.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -有茶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - You got tea?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.09,0:11:26.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有的  我去倒  -要甘菊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes, of course. I'll get that. - Chamomile.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.43,0:11:29.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好好享受就行  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You don't miss a minute. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.85,0:11:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  怎么  瞧瞧我做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. Why did- You know, look at what I'm doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.81,0:11:35.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我把自己弄成主角了  真是扫兴  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm- I'm making it all about me. What a downer. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.06,0:11:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-今晚的主角是你  让今夜此生难忘吧  -没没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's your evening. Let's make it great, man. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.07,0:11:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说几个曲子吧  我全部照唱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Name your playlist. I'll do it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.85,0:11:41.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就经典曲目吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, um, just the classics.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.28,0:11:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-几首出名的  -那是肯定的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Let's play the hits. - We'll get to the hits, obviously.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.57,0:11:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说旧专辑的曲目吧  B面最喜欢哪首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go to the back catalog, man. Favorite B- side.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.32,0:11:50.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思  只不过我最记不住歌名了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's fun. Yeah, that's fun. Uh, just- I'm so bad with titles.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.16,0:11:50.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼来听听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hum it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.41,0:11:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-*今夜*  -那是我刚才弹的那首  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- *Tonight*  - I just did that one, didn't I? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.58,0:11:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才在我脑海里回旋  那这首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why it's in the noodle. So I guess-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.47,0:12:07.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是哪张专辑里的  -第二张  好像是第二张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. What album is that on? - Second. I wanna say second.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.60,0:12:08.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封面是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's on the cover?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.46,0:12:11.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个巫师  要么就是海景画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a warlock, I think, or a seascape.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.97,0:12:13.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巫师  噢  《千年日出》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Warlock. Oh. Millennium Sunrise.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.22,0:12:13.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是《千年日出》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Millennium Sunrise.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.88,0:12:15.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有《千年日出》这张专辑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There is no Millennium Sunrise record.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.90,0:12:18.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你根本就不是粉丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What- What? You're not a Fandau.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.14,0:12:20.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚在门口  你都不知道我是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You didn't even know who I was at the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.61,0:12:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你的眼神就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I saw it in your eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.40,0:12:22.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please don't say anything to Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.56,0:12:23.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她弄错了  -我是被耍了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She made a mistake. - Am I being punk'd?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.86,0:12:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此事对她太重要了  我不想伤害她的感情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This means so much to her, and I don't wanna hurt her feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.16,0:12:28.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的感情  那我的感情呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Her feelings? Well, what about my feelings?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.27,0:12:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的事业啊  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is my career, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.49,0:12:32.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的音乐曾是人们的最爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, my music was the soundtrack to people's lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.29,0:12:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却一文不值了  你觉得这是什么感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I'm nothing. How do you think that feels?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.01,0:12:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太侮辱人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is really humiliating.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.12,0:12:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别别  别走别走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. Don't go. Don't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.87,0:12:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你俩干嘛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. What are you guys doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.75,0:12:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他允许我摸这把吉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He let me touch it!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.42,0:12:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说了"弄死"  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I think she said "kill," Cam. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.51,0:12:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是开玩笑的  她一直都挺黑色幽默的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe it was just a joke. She's always had a dark sense of humor.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.26,0:12:50.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒是  还记得她的万圣节装束吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's true. Remember her Halloween costume?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.26,0:12:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[德国民间史诗《尼贝龙根之歌》中的英雄人物]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.26,0:12:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她扮成齐格弗里德和罗伊的结合体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When she came as Siegfried and part of Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.81,0:12:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才不久的事情  -对对  就是个玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It was too soon. - Yeah. Yeah. This was just a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.06,0:12:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  好了她来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Yeah. Here she comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.89,0:12:59.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧  我提一下莉莉  看她什么反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I'm gonna bring up Lily. We'll see what she says.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.69,0:13:01.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-给她看点照片  -付钱吧  小妞们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Show her some pictures. - Pay up, bitches.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.90,0:13:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又端酒过来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whoa. More drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.40,0:13:06.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费的哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Free drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.70,0:13:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-萨尔  你得看看这些照片  -是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sal, you've got to look at these pictures. - What are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.16,0:13:11.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莉莉在动物园  -真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's Lily at the zoo. - Oh, cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.87,0:13:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看这张  -萌死了萌翻了萌得要流泪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Look at that one. - Cute! Cute. Cutie, cutie, cute, et cetera.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.54,0:13:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们得带莉莉去卡波\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you guys are gonna have to bring Lily to Cabo,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.75,0:13:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你们走哪儿都带着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}now that you're the guys that always bring Lily?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.75,0:13:23.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这个嘛  -行吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, you know- - Yeah, probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.30,0:13:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要把她丢进大海里  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I will throw her in the ocean. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.76,0:13:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我要去尿尿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said I gotta go pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.09,0:13:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行了  这回不是我们听错了  -绝对不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, that wasn't even close. - Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.14,0:13:35.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  要说点什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, what do we do? Do we say something?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.91,0:13:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么提这事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How do we even bring it up?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.73,0:13:40.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她威胁我们的宝宝  你担心的竟是开场白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She threatened our child, and that's your concern- a segue?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.61,0:13:42.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道是怎么回事吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know what this is? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.94,0:13:46.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-头生子综合征  -什么玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is first- child syndrome. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.11,0:13:47.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是头生子原本非常幸福快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's where the first child is happy,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.82,0:13:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二个宝宝出生以后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then the second child comes along,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.70,0:13:51.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头生子就开始嫉妒小宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the first child gets jealous of the second child
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.67,0:13:53.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后闹脾气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and starts acting out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.20,0:13:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  忒有道理了  可萨尔不是我们的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. That's brilliant, except Sal's not our child, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.41,0:13:59.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想看啊  我们曾经那么照顾她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think about it. Listen, we've practically done everything for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.33,0:14:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她流泪时  我们给她温暖的怀抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've held her when she's cried.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.83,0:14:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她无法走路时  我们背着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've carried her when she couldn't walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.21,0:14:05.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就差没教她如何蹲马桶撒尿了  -伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- We've done everything but potty- train her. - Um- Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.61,0:14:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我在想  -不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I was thinking- Oh. - Oh. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.55,0:14:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去卡波的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When we go to Cabo,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.43,0:14:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要找个带池滨酒吧的酒店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we have to find a hotel with a swim- up bar,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.64,0:14:17.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来回回地跑厕所  太他妈傻逼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause this going back and forth to the bathroom is a fool's game.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.81,0:14:20.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行  继续喝吧  -萨尔  我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay, let's get more drinks. - Sal, we got to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.69,0:14:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是关于莉莉的  -噢  我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's about Lily. - Oh, shocker.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.52,0:14:25.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -你觉得有没有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - Do you think it's at all possible...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.65,0:14:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你有那么一丁点嫉妒她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that maybe- maybe you're jealous of her?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.03,0:14:30.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  说毛呢  -只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What? What? - It's just-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.95,0:14:33.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也不确定  -我不  你干嘛这么问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't know. - I don't- Where- Why would you say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你拒绝看她的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, because you won't look at any pictures of her...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.95,0:14:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说要弄死她  要把她丢进大海什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you talked about killing her and throwing her in the ocean.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.58,0:14:40.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那完全是玩笑嘛  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that was a joke, you guys. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.97,0:14:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  把小野洋子的照片拿来瞧瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. Show me the pictures of Yoko.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.55,0:14:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[日本人  被认为是导致披头士乐队解散的重要原因]
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.03,0:14:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, it's...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.10,0:14:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑来着  别这样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a joke. You guys! Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.65,0:14:48.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是亚洲人嘛  还拆散了我们的小团体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause she's Asian, and she broke up our group.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.63,0:14:50.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...只是  听着  我们得承认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I- I just- Look, let's at least
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.90,0:14:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的关系和从前不太一样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}acknowledge that things have changed between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.93,0:14:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.77,0:14:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉的出现  不会使我们对你的爱减少丝毫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because Lily's here doesn't mean we love you any less.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.43,0:14:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-绝对不会  -到底怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. Absolutely not. - What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.60,0:15:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以前那么亲密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We used to be really close, and
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.03,0:15:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没事就给我打电话  现在你们压根不给我打了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you used to call me a lot. And now you never call me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.60,0:15:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是我们  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, but we- - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.77,0:15:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周我做了个噩梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And last week I had a really bad dream,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.02,0:15:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在想  "我要给他们打电话"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I was thinking, "Okay, I'm gonna call them."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.90,0:15:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就觉得  "不行  不能打给他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then I thought, "Oh, no, you can't call them...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.70,0:15:16.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把小宝宝吵醒了怎么办啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you might wake up their baby."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.95,0:15:19.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们随时欢迎你的来电  -随时欢迎  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You can always call. - Oh, honey, always call us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.41,0:15:21.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  真抱歉当时没有陪着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I'm sorry we haven't been there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.14,0:15:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我们在你身边呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're here now, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.29,0:15:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.92,0:15:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好点了吗  -我觉得你沾上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Feel better? - I think you just put a little-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.92,0:15:31.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口水吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Spittle?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.30,0:15:37.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她睡着了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did she just fall asleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.54,0:15:39.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望莉莉也能这么容易入睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wish Lily would fall asleep like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.60,0:15:41.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给她8杯龙舌兰就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give her eight shots of tequila.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.19,0:15:50.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不明白她怎么就不睡觉呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't understand why she's not falling asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.44,0:15:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道原因  -电影来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I have a theory. - I got the movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.74,0:15:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  去弄点爆米花吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, why don't you go fire up some popcorn?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.74,0:16:00.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在找这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You looking for these?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.33,0:16:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你偷走了我的鞋  -不  我剥夺了你的自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You took my shoes? - No, I took your freedom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.96,0:16:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  孩子  今晚不是属于你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, kid. It ain't your night.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.29,0:16:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you being like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.29,0:16:09.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想去那个派对  也就两小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just wanted to go to that party for, like, two hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.96,0:16:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来这会儿都回来了  你同意一下会死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would've been back by now. Would that have killed you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.22,0:16:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是虎母无犬女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's just like her mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.38,0:16:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛这么折磨海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you treating Haley like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.47,0:16:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  是她在耍性子吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me? She's the one acting like a pill.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.64,0:16:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她并非是刻意跟你唱对台戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're taking this too personally.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.68,0:16:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在海莉那么大的时候  也很爱自己的外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I was Haley's age, I loved my grandfather,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.52,0:16:26.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但同样很爱去派对和男孩子们玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I still wanted to go to parties and be with boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.06,0:16:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂我懂  克莱尔也一样  还有米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I know. So did Claire... and Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.40,0:16:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.27,0:16:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是跟我对着干  绝对没有好果子吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You try to put something over on me, you're gonna lose.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.11,0:16:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎样  你要把这事儿闹大吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what? Now you're gonna make this into a big game?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.82,0:16:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想多和他们共处  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm trying to keep 'em around a little bit longer, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.42,0:16:44.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天知道我还有多少个这样的夜晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, who knows how many nights like this I got left?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.87,0:16:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我已经开始想你了  -这孩子今天有毛病吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I miss you already. - What's wrong with this kid tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.54,0:16:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去厨房给大家帮忙  我就来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go in the kitchen and help out the guys, and I'll be right in.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.38,0:16:57.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想多和外孙女在一起是好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's great that you wanna spend time with your granddaughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.30,0:16:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但真的要以这种方式吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but is this really the way?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.55,0:17:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -你是个好外公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Fine. - You're a good abuelo.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.88,0:17:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她在楼上  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She's upstairs. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.65,0:17:11.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.86,0:17:15.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -出来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah? - Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.49,0:17:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来找海莉去派对的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're here to take Haley to the party, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.49,0:17:21.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -她在屋里呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - She's in the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.95,0:17:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did you know I was here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.54,0:17:27.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次见菲尔就是在那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is how I first met Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.09,0:17:33.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  外公  我们11点就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks again, Grandpa. We'll be back by 11:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.55,0:17:36.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我会去找你的  -我想也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I will track you down. - I believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.09,0:17:38.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是什么味道  -炒牛肉"杰"  去尝尝吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's that smell? - Sloppy jays. Help yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.97,0:17:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩好多呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's plenty left.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.89,0:17:43.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  炒牛肉"杰"是因为你叫杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Sloppy jays because your name's Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.72,0:17:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谐音很正\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.72,0:17:47.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信她喜欢这种脑残货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can't believe she's into this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.06,0:17:49.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我给你来一盘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you want, I'll fix you a plate.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.90,0:17:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  太好了  -不去派对了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, definitely. That'd be great. - But what about the party?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.86,0:17:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就走  就...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We can go in just a minute. Just let-
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.93,0:17:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  是《枪战》  我特喜欢这电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no way. The Gunfighter. I love this movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.90,0:18:00.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan, the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.03,0:18:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...是牛仔哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. But... cowboys.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.95,0:18:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别抗争了  海莉  男人永远都是孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't fight it, Haley. They never grow up.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.62,0:18:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -我去厨房拿杯咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thanks. - I'm going to the kitchen for an espresso.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.87,0:18:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有人需要什么吗  -不了谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Anybody need anything? - No, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.63,0:18:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.42,0:18:15.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二  三  四\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two, three, four.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.67,0:18:21.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时正值1991年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The year was 1991.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.87,0:18:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国沉浸于"沙漠风暴"行动中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}America was immersed in Desert Storm.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.12,0:18:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[1991年美国等针对伊拉克的打击行动]
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.55,0:18:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与此同时  在国内  另一股风暴正袭来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Meanwhile, stateside, another storm was brewing...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.58,0:18:32.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我心中袭来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.86,0:18:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太蠢了  对吧  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- This is stupid, isn't it? This is- - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.86,0:18:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很傻吗  菲尔  -不不  请继续  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is it stupid, Phil? - No. Just keep- keep going, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.95,0:18:41.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-非常有情调  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's wonderful. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.69,0:18:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在弗里特利餐厅共享晚餐后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}After a romantic dinner at Fratelli's,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.02,0:18:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞涩的情侣为对方献上了初吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a certain nervous young couple shared their first kiss...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.08,0:18:52.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而广播里正是这首歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}as the radio played this song.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.47,0:19:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*太真实*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*So true*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.46,0:19:02.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*似乎滑稽可笑*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Funny how it seems *
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.77,0:19:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*时机恰好*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Always in time*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.03,0:19:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*美梦却总不能成真*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*But never in line for dreams*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.03,0:19:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*四脚相对  深深相爱*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Head over heels when toe to toe*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.51,0:19:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*那声音是*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*This is the sound of-*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.49,0:19:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  不行  抱歉  我办不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? No. No. Sorry. Sorry. Not gonna do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.07,0:19:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.94,0:19:23.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-出什么事了  -你知道这首歌的名字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What's going on? - Do you even know the name of this song?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.99,0:19:26.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"破"  -《真实》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- P- "True."
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.37,0:19:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《真实》  -《真实》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- "True." - "True."
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.20,0:19:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是假装的  瞧出来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right. This is false. See?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.12,0:19:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会为"假人"演奏"真实"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna play "True" for someone who's false.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.12,0:19:34.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他甚至根本不知道我们乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, he doesn't- He doesn't even know the band.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.58,0:19:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-更不是粉丝  -他知道这个乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's not a fan, a Fandau. - Yes, he does know the band.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.61,0:19:37.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当然知道啊  这是我们的定情之歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Of course he does. 'Cause this is our song.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.14,0:19:39.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱这首歌  快和他说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You love this song. Tell him this is our song.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:42.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  你说啊  菲尔  -这不是我们的定情之歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Right. Tell him, Phil. - It's not our song, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.84,0:19:43.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的歌是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our song is
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.38,0:19:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"黑暗中的管弦乐"乐队的《如果你离开》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"If You Leave" by Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.55,0:19:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死!  -你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-OH!  - Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.68,0:19:50.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常确定  我在我们的婚礼上唱过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pretty sure. I sang it at our wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.52,0:19:52.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  我真是个蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'm an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.52,0:19:53.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  他才是蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, actually, he's the idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.81,0:19:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是首分手歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He fell in love to a break- up song.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.40,0:19:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别理他  今晚多美好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ignore him. This is beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.12,0:19:59.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很喜欢  -我不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I love it. - I hate this. I hate this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.27,0:20:02.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如此温柔贴心  我却不能给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're so sweet and nice, and I can't even give you...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.11,0:20:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份像样的周年纪念礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a decent anniversary present.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.15,0:20:07.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太爱你了  但我觉得你可能永远不会知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you so much, and I feel you just are never gonna know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.49,0:20:09.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  我知道  -你真的知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know it. I know it.  - You do know it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.88,0:20:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然了  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes.  - You do?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.73,0:20:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个礼物多好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And this is an awesome gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.54,0:20:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-知道为什么吗  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You know why? - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.58,0:20:19.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们有新歌了  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You just gave us a new song. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.09,0:20:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们又黏糊起来了是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sort of brought you back together, eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.59,0:20:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-算是吧  -差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Seems. - Sort of.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.30,0:20:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"爱火重燃"  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Rekindled fires of a dying passion? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.80,0:20:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给低劣的谎言照射一丝希望的曙光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shot a ray of hope into this gloomy suburban lie?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.18,0:20:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别废话了  哥们  -快演奏吧  伊茨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- All right, buddy. - Just play it, lzzy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.43,0:20:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,献给克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For you, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.34,0:20:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我知道*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*I know this*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.03,0:20:40.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*爱很真实*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Much is true*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.12,0:20:47.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我知道*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*I know this*
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.77,0:20:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*爱很真实*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}*Much is true*
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.21,0:21:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她太可爱了  -可不是嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- She is so sweet. - Isn't she?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.63,0:21:05.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个小天使\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like a little angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.09,0:21:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我抱抱她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me hold her.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.51,0:21:14.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank God.

