[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.09,0:01:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.09,0:01:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.09,0:01:18.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第二十三集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.10,0:00:06.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好啊  莉莉  -你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Aloha, Lily. - Aloha.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.27,0:00:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  得再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, wait. Let's do it one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.21,0:00:08.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小狗狗挡住小脸蛋了  -的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- The doggy was blocking her face. - Yeah,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.36,0:00:09.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-回去再来  -我不要  我不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go back. - No. No! No.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.85,0:00:10.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不要再来第三次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're not doing it a third time.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.98,0:00:14.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧谁来了  茂伊岛上最美的人儿  夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There she is- the prettiest white woman on Maui. Milady.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.73,0:00:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  当年克莱尔和我本来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, Claire and I were supposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.36,0:00:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是要来夏威夷来度蜜月的  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- go to Hawaii for our honeymoon. - Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.44,0:00:21.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可出现了点状况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But something else came up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.84,0:00:24.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我怀上了海莉  -都是哥的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I got pregnant with Haley. - My bad!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.27,0:00:25.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们甚至连像样的婚礼都没办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We didn't even have a proper wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.76,0:00:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就随便挑了一个礼拜二去法院登记了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We just went down to the courthouse on a Tuesday.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.37,0:00:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从此就被判"无期婚姻"徒刑  且不准假释\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The judge sentenced me to life with no chance of parole.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.60,0:00:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时可是你求我嫁给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You begged me to marry you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.94,0:00:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我求了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's true. I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.52,0:00:38.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点  我的娘子  来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Hold on, my bride. Allow me!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.91,0:00:39.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.88,0:00:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪漫一下  天呐  你真重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Being romantic. God, you're solid.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.81,0:00:43.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  快放我下来  慢慢来  好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, put me down. Go on. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.85,0:00:45.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.01,0:00:47.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们把这次假期当成在度蜜月吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's turn this vacation into a honeymoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.02,0:00:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我可是带着孩子来旅行的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweet pea, I'm a mom traveling with my kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.88,0:00:50.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说  这不是度假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For me, this is not a vacation.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.31,0:00:51.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是出差  跟我走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a business trip. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.53,0:00:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.39,0:00:59.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太漂亮了  -大家好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's beautiful. - Aloha!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.21,0:01:02.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎入住四季酒店茂伊店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi! Welcome to the Four Seasons Maui.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.91,0:01:04.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎样  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you think, Manny?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.92,0:01:07.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宾至如归啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm home.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.34,0:01:25.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们居然还有自己的房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe we have our own hotel room.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.63,0:01:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  这里还有个熨斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Score! There's an iron in here!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.97,0:01:30.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能把房间弄得整洁点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you want to keep our room neat?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.70,0:01:32.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一有客人来怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, in case we entertain.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.42,0:01:33.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who would we entertain?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.73,0:01:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到儿童俱乐部里有好多可爱的小姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I noticed some lovely tweens down by the kids' club.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.33,0:01:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准我们能在泳池边找个机会搭讪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe we can find a nice spot near them by the pool...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.40,0:01:40.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再奉上一杯"处女红"鸡尾酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and send over a couple of virgin mai tais.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.64,0:01:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们没准喜欢我们这种成熟老练的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They may be interested in two sophisticated men like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.40,0:01:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是浴室战神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am a bathroom martian!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.17,0:01:53.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来自伟大的卫生间星云\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am from the nebula of the Great Toilet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.94,0:01:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我来一个你们这里最大的芝士汉堡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want the biggest cheeseburger you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.58,0:02:00.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把沙拉换成薯条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Instead of salad, I want fries.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.70,0:02:02.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把水果换成辣薯条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Instead of fruit, I want chili fries.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.24,0:02:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  亲爱的  别玩手机了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, sweetie, put the phone down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.73,0:02:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快涂点防晒霜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and put on some sunscreen. Please?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.69,0:02:08.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得时刻盯着这些孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have got to stay on these kids all day,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.61,0:02:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不然他们准得晒伤  -绝对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- or else they're gonna burn. - Totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.35,0:02:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就早上涂了那么一小点防晒霜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They put on the littlest bit of sunscreen in the morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.05,0:02:14.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就以为没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they think it's got them covered for the-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.22,0:02:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是在透过我的墨镜偷看歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you watching Gloria in my sunglasses?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.09,0:02:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她在做慢动作  还是我在胡思乱想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is she moving in slow motion, or is my brain doing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.83,0:02:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  认真点  -继续说  我听着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil, this is important. - Go ahead. I'm glistening.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.57,0:02:23.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  大家好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.71,0:02:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正要去看世界上最大的榕树\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're on our way to see the world's largest banyan tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.71,0:02:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人想一起来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does anybody want to come?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.77,0:02:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会吃饱了撑着  要离开这片仙境\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, why in the hell would anyone want to leave paradise,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.97,0:02:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去坐闷热无比的车只为看一棵树\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}take a hot bus ride to see a tree?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.64,0:02:36.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最欣赏卡梅隆的一点是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The great thing about Cameron is that,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.18,0:02:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他勇于探索  和我一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}uh, he's adventurous, like I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.81,0:02:40.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都喜欢入乡随俗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We-We both like to immerse ourselves in the culture
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.24,0:02:41.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多地了解本地居民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and really get to know the locals.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.62,0:02:43.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的朋友遍布全球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've made friends all over the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们至今还和伊伦加保持着联系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're still in touch with Elunga,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.96,0:02:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我们在坦桑尼亚狩猎旅行时认识的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a man we met on safari in Tanzania.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.84,0:02:50.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们经常寄旧衣服给他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We actually send him... all of our old clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.64,0:02:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们结识时  他还是个很善良的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was a very nice man when we met him,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.30,0:02:54.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就最近的回信来看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but based on his recent letters,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.78,0:02:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点担心他已经变成军阀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a small fear he's become a warlord.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.83,0:03:02.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我要去健身房运动下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. I'm gonna go to the gym to work out a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.23,0:03:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要一起来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to come with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.08,0:03:05.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚特地叫了一根超长吸管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just ordered an extra-long straw
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.28,0:03:07.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是为了不想坐起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to avoid accidentally doing a sit-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜谁来电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.39,0:03:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.47,0:03:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干吗  蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up, jackass?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.64,0:03:15.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐  你个二逼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy birthday, you dumb son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.32,0:03:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天才是我的生日  蠢蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Birthday's tomorrow, moron!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.97,0:03:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞不懂你们兄弟俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never understood this relationship.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.95,0:03:21.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-63岁了对吧  -没想到你还会数数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So, 63, right? - Hey, you can count!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.76,0:03:23.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得老爸就是63岁死的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know Dad was 63 when he died. Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.12,0:03:26.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂  - 多谢提醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello? - Thanks for reminding me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.30,0:03:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  是他不懂得好好保养身体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, don't worry. He never took care of himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.46,0:03:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是吃垃圾食品  喝得烂醉如泥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ate like crap and drank too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.45,0:03:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他呢  艾琳在求我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, Irene's begging me for-
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.21,0:03:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我  歌洛莉亚  我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Gloria, wait up. I'm coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.22,0:03:42.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想要不要给我们预定一个夫妻按摩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, I was thinking we book a couples' massage.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.75,0:03:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正巧看到一对在做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I accidentally looked in on one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.18,0:03:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没看到我之前可放松呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They seemed really relaxed until they noticed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.63,0:03:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  够了  快挂电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, that's enough. Get off the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.19,0:03:49.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  裤子拉拉好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, pull up your trunks!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.91,0:03:52.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿这身泳衣真好看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This bathing suit looks great on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.03,0:03:54.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢夸奖  海莉  别打了  快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, sweetie. Haley, come on. Off the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.35,0:03:56.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  凯拉把她的头发拉直了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No way. Keira got her hair straightened?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.59,0:04:00.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  为表达对你的爱  我决定这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, consider this a grand gesture of my love.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.60,0:04:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.59,0:04:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.83,0:04:06.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你都做了什么  -菲尔  你在想什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What did you do? - Phil, what are you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.59,0:04:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那手机可贵呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is an expensive cell phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.18,0:04:09.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好戏才刚刚开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.78,0:04:12.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好准备吧  我要向你展开攻势了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buckle your seat belt, lady. You're being wooed.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.56,0:04:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在自然界中  雄性通常会吃掉幼崽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In nature, fathers are known to eat their young.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.77,0:04:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为幼崽好吃吗  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it because they're delicious? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.10,0:04:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为它们想给雌性伴侣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's because they want to give their female-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.31,0:04:22.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如熊啊  长颈鹿啊  随便什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}bear, giraffe, what have you-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.74,0:04:24.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个甜蜜的蜜月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the honeymoon they never had.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.81,0:04:28.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事先声明  我不是说吃孩子是可以原谅的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just to be clear, I'm not condoning eating your kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.42,0:04:30.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我知道长颈鹿这么做的本意是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I sure as heck know why giraffes do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.50,0:04:33.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.00,0:04:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-起床来  懒虫  -别闹了  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come on, sleepy! - Ay, Jay!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.37,0:04:45.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起床  宝贝  别赖床了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, honey! Get out of bed!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.04,0:04:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚预订了个划艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just booked us on an outrigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.52,0:04:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可今天是你的生日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it is your birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.09,0:04:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不想睡个懒觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't want to sleep in?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.15,0:04:49.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快来  -不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Come here. - No, no,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.90,0:04:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚从健身房回来  猜我刚举起多重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just came from the gym. Guess how much I benched.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.72,0:04:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道  500磅  -500磅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't know. 500 pounds? - 500 pounds?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.42,0:04:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我是叉车啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What am I, a forklift?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.45,0:04:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实话和你说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To tell you the truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.24,0:04:59.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老弟那通电话把我吓惨了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that call from my brother scared the hell out of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.04,0:05:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定尽快练回健康身材\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I decided to get in better shape quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.34,0:05:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想步我老爸的后尘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Didn't want to end up like my old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.12,0:05:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他算是死于他热爱的事业中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Although he did die doing what he loved-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.64,0:05:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝向来店里的嬉皮士提供服务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}refusing service to hippies who came into his store.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.12,0:05:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼是有史以来最差的室友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny is the worst roommate ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.14,0:05:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看到什么都要叠起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything he finds, he folds.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.85,0:05:16.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  忍忍几天就过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, it's only for a few more days.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.54,0:05:18.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚还做了火灾演习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Last night we had a fire drill.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.66,0:05:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是整个酒店  就我俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not the hotel. Just us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.88,0:05:22.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们好啊  -你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, guys. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.69,0:05:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天准备去哪探险呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, what's today's big adventure?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.64,0:05:29.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打赌孩子们肯定都想和你们去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll bet the kids want to go with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.19,0:05:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是去个好地方  薰衣草牧场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it is a big one- the lavender ranch,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.93,0:05:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那里种45种不同的薰衣草哦  -45种哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- where they grow 45 different varieties of lavender. - Forty-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.63,0:05:37.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到没  孩子们  45种不同的薰衣草哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hear that, kids? Forty-five different varieties.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.41,0:05:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  实在说不动他们  祝旅途愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I can't sell that. Go with God.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.11,0:05:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就没人和我们抢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Well, more lavender for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.59,0:05:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔和我初遇时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When Mitchell and I first met,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:46.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能夸大了我对探险的狂热之情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I may have exaggerated my interest in adventurous travel...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.02,0:05:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我有很多此类经历\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by implying that I had any.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.35,0:05:50.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他偏偏最爱我这点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it's one of the things he loves most about me,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.58,0:05:52.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致我现在不能道出事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I can't tell him the truth now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.20,0:05:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像路易斯告诉克拉克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It would be like Lewis telling Clark
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.48,0:05:56.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他其实不喜欢徒步一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that he didn't like to walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.00,0:05:57.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,补充说明一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Side note.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.70,0:06:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路易斯和克拉克夫夫是我们的一对好朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're very good friends with a couple named Lewis and Clark.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.71,0:06:02.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉克在新奥尔良买了一块巨大的地皮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Clark bought a big, sparkly belt in New Orleans
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.68,0:06:05.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将之与政府当年购买路易斯安那州相提并论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that he calls his Louisiana Purchase.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.12,0:06:08.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  海莉一直偷我的ipod\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, Haley keeps stealing my iPod.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.31,0:06:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的歌都在手机上  你让我怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All my music is on my phone. What else am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.60,0:06:13.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼整天看新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny watches the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.46,0:06:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连你们都不怎么看新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys don't even watch the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.23,0:06:17.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aloha. Hi. Sorry, folks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.08,0:06:18.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这泳池是成人专用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This pool is for adults only.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.67,0:06:21.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别回头  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't turn around. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.42,0:06:22.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我的  往前走就是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trust me. Just keep walking.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.77,0:06:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你们要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait! Where are you guys going?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.54,0:06:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爹妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.32,0:06:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What just happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.92,0:06:33.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到时能一边喝薰衣草茶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, so we can drink lavender tea
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.86,0:06:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边吃薰衣草饼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}while eating lavender scones.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.33,0:06:38.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒  一整天都这么过还是怎么着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, neat! So, is this an all-day thing or-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.82,0:06:40.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  我知道你在想什么  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. I know what you're thinking, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.99,0:06:43.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我们还有时间参观捕鲸村落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry. We'll still have time for the whaling village.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.43,0:06:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Good. So-
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.41,0:06:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.29,0:06:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不行  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I can't. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.45,0:06:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.73,0:06:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know I said
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.45,0:06:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那种慵懒不爱动的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not a stay-by-the-pool type of guy,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.89,0:06:57.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我骨子里就是  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I really am, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.09,0:06:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.05,0:06:59.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是喜欢探险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm saying that I like adventure,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.32,0:07:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可也用不着每分每秒都投身于此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but not every minute of every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.03,0:07:02.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能自己一个人去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you just go by yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:04.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是薰衣草农场啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But... the lavender ranch-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.44,0:07:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注定要两个相爱的人一起享受的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's- It's something two men are meant to do together.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.02,0:07:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-到底去不去  -我去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- On or off, folks? - Well, I'm on.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.32,0:07:12.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.80,0:07:17.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想你错过了什么  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think about what you're missing, Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.34,0:07:19.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个牧场都是薰衣草哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's an entire ranch full of lavender.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.21,0:07:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得再天花乱坠都没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not making the compelling case you think you are!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.68,0:07:29.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小兔崽子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you little monkey!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.51,0:07:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别光站着  给我下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No standing around! There you go!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.95,0:07:34.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一个下来咯  下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here goes another one! There you go!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.00,0:07:36.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一个下来咯  下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here comes another one! There you go!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.40,0:07:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你是我们家的小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you were one of ours!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.47,0:07:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  当心点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jay! Be careful!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.46,0:07:44.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别伤着人家  特别是你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna hurt somebody- like you!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.57,0:07:45.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太惬意哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't get too comfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.48,0:07:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我刚定好了网球场  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I reserved us a tennis court. - Yay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为嫁给一个老头的好处之一是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought that one of the advantages of marrying an older guy...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.34,0:07:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活能过的轻松点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was that I was going to be able to relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.65,0:07:56.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他又是游泳又是跑步又是划船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But all this swimming and running and rowing-
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.61,0:07:59.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直跟我的同胞们偷渡来美国的过程差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's just like how some of my relatives got into this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.87,0:08:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know- Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.10,0:08:04.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我们结婚时更漂亮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You look prettier now than the day we got married.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.13,0:08:06.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你也更帅了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey. And you are even more handsome.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.33,0:08:08.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有在浴室里偷偷练俯卧撑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did push-ups in the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.23,0:08:10.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真"幽默"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.18,0:08:12.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真好  -我一直都这么好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You're nice. -I have always been nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.30,0:08:14.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一直很幽默\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've always been funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.80,0:08:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.92,0:08:20.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom! Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.33,0:08:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别理她  可能是在叫其他人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ignore her. That could be anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.82,0:08:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔和克莱尔·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil and Claire Dunphy?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.70,0:08:30.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  亲爱的  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, Haley, honey? What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.14,0:08:32.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去和隔壁的一些孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna go get some shaved ice at the hotel
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.28,0:08:33.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去吃点刨冰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}next door with some kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.89,0:08:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么孩子  -就是在泳池边的那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- What kids? - Just some kids I met at the pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.27,0:08:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  我得去看看  -克莱尔  别去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. Um- I should go with her and - Claire, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.93,0:08:41.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得学会放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have to learn to let go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.22,0:08:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把家庭度假变成度蜜月  要坚持做到哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Turning a family vacation into a honeymoon takes commitment.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.30,0:08:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做到  猛虎之眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can do it. Eye of the tiger.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.63,0:08:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.91,0:08:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-至少得见见他们  -不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I should at least meet them. I - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.80,0:08:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这可不是猛虎之眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is not eye of the tiger.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.82,0:09:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  海莉  亲爱的  玩的开心点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, Haley, honey, go and have fun,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.29,0:09:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但可不能上陌生人的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but don't get in anybody's car...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准时回来参加你外公的生日  知道了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and be back in time for your grandfather's birthday dinner, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.47,0:09:11.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.06,0:09:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  快去快回  -再见  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay! All right! - Bye, honey!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.34,0:09:15.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.45,0:09:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这感觉真是又诡异又舒爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That feels weird and good all at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.21,0:09:22.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  刚刚我也靠在那喷头上呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know. I was leaning up against that nozzle a minute ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.93,0:09:29.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  -你回来啦  感觉怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey. - Hey, you're back. How was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.40,0:09:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡梅隆  那真是我这辈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah! Cameron, it was the most incredible thing
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.42,0:09:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见过最美的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've ever seen in my entire life.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.00,0:09:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -你到我在那碰到谁了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Really? - You know who else was there?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.13,0:09:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -艾尔顿·约翰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Who - Elton John.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.63,0:09:38.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不会吧  -真的  他也被美景深深吸引了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No- -Yes, and he was so blown away by the beauty of it,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.22,0:09:39.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐在用薰衣草装点的钢琴前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he sat down... at their lavender piano
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.94,0:09:40.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演奏了一曲《小舞人》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and played "Tiny Dancer."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.96,0:09:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我顿感心有灵犀  因为他也热爱探险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we bonded, because he too likes adventure.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.55,0:09:45.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这些都是真的吗  -不  当然是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did that really happen? - No, that didn't really happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.59,0:09:46.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.51,0:09:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想报复你抛弃我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}trying to get back at you for bailing on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.78,0:09:50.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  如果你真想和我一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. If it means anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.19,0:09:51.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这什么也不做也很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we've been relaxing here doing nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.96,0:09:54.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许明天你能和我们一起  -不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Maybe you can join us tomorrow. - No, I can't- I just don't-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.47,0:09:56.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我实在不觉得放松有什么意思  -我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't find relaxing that relaxing. - I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.61,0:09:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生性如此难再改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are who you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.71,0:09:59.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-蕾拉妮  -来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Leilani. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.35,0:10:02.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我想可能是我受我爸妈的影响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? I think it's because of my parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.03,0:10:04.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  奇普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It always is. Kipu!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.34,0:10:05.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  和我爸妈一起度假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, vacation with my mom and dad
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.86,0:10:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像坐在两个雕像旁边一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was them sitting around like statues...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.94,0:10:11.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和克莱尔唯一能找到的乐子就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when, the only thing that me and Claire could do for excitement was-
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.08,0:10:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐着听自己的皮肤晒得吱吱作响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was sit around and listen to my skin sizzle.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.70,0:10:17.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真可怜  苏 -来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You poor thing. Sue? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.21,0:10:19.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是为什么  每当我出来度假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, that's, like- That's why, when I'm on vacation,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.48,0:10:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想出去见见当地人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to go out and meet the locals.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.27,0:10:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让自己融入当地的文化  明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to immerse myself in the culture, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.97,0:10:26.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想一整天都这么懒洋洋的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to sloth around- Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.07,0:10:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的个嘎嘎  太舒服了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweet Lady Gaga, that is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.67,0:10:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.52,0:10:37.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's this called?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.72,0:10:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.37,0:10:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好奇  是我们浴室里的沙子没弄走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm curious. Is there any sand left on the beach,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.52,0:10:48.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是你带回我们浴室里来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or did you bring it all up to our bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:50.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了  老妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.59,0:10:52.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你现在又坐在我的亚麻夹克上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And now you're sitting on my linen jacket.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.83,0:10:54.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不能有件像样的东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I can't have nice things.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.68,0:10:57.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起  我不知道它在那  -没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh. I'm sorry. I didn't know it was there. - It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.92,0:10:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  快停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.60,0:11:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚可是要穿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm wearing that tonight!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.75,0:11:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你的衣服弄皱咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm wrinkling your linen! I'm wrinkling your linen!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.21,0:11:05.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你逼我的  滚出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh! You know what? Out!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.58,0:11:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚出去  这样不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want you out! This isn't working!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.86,0:11:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管你去哪里  只要别在这就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't care where you go, as long as you don't stay here!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.78,0:11:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.96,0:11:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听不懂"出去"两个字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What don't you understand about "Out"?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.07,0:11:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走就走  我去和我姐姐们住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. I'll just move in with my sisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.07,0:11:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁小便都不能瞄准  到处都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no! Who will pee all over the bathroom floor?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.94,0:11:24.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时还在刷牙呢  高难度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was brushing my teeth at the same time.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.99,0:11:26.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我试试看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You try to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.81,0:11:28.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天都做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What'd you do today?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.27,0:11:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我打了个盹  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I napped. - You did?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.22,0:11:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我好几年都没打过盹了  -感觉很棒  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I haven't napped in years. - Yeah. It feels good, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.53,0:11:35.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  又奇怪又舒爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm-hmm. Good and weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.11,0:11:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像无边泳池里的那个喷头一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kinda like that one nozzle in the infinity pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.08,0:11:38.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  菲尔把那给占了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wouldn't know. Phil was hogging it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.84,0:11:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错觉还是莉莉真的比以前更放松了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it me, or is Lily more relaxed here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.61,0:11:43.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的错觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yes. She is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.60,0:11:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她是受到我们的影响了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think it's because she's really picking up on our energy, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.33,0:11:49.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像要是我们紧张了  她也会跟着紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like, if we're tense, she's gonna be tense.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.08,0:11:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们得把这种正能量带回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I think we need to bring this new energy home.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.97,0:11:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以使我们更好地为人父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna make us better parents-
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.22,0:11:54.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你关了  -什么  什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You blocked the - What? What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.88,0:11:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没带她出来  -我以为你带着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You didn't bring her out! - I thought you had her!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.86,0:12:02.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  让我来为你画张像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Let me paint you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.67,0:12:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  会不会太重口味了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sweetie. That is so creepy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.21,0:12:07.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人都到哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where is everyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.94,0:12:12.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我来说说大家的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Let me just say what everyone's thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.63,0:12:13.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的夹克太皱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My jacket's a mess.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.89,0:12:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本不该这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It wouldn't be,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.05,0:12:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可有人竟然用熨斗来烤奶酪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but someone used the iron to make grilled cheese.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.00,0:12:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有面包  有奶酪  外加一个熨斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had bread, I had cheese and I had an iron.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.96,0:12:22.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What was I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.19,0:12:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  别胡闹  我们不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kids, kids. We don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.22,0:12:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hola, hola!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.48,0:12:30.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我迟到了  杰去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey. So sorry I'm late. Where is Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.31,0:12:31.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是和你在一起吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.30,0:12:33.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啊  他早就下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, he came down long time ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.00,0:12:34.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我去找找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't worry. I'll go have a look around.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.99,0:12:36.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  他也许正在海里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, he's probably in the ocean trying to
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.86,0:12:38.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用牙齿拖船呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}pull a tugboat with his teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.85,0:12:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看谁来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, look who decided to join us.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.18,0:12:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你姐呢  -她在浴室狂吐呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And where is your sister? - She is in our bathroom throwing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.53,0:12:46.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, what happened? -
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.78,0:12:48.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到她现在的样子也很痛心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not going to like this as much as I do,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.76,0:12:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她喝多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but she's drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.97,0:12:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道不该纵容她的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I knew I never should have let her-
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.86,0:12:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有戏看咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.56,0:12:58.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢保证我们的浴室肯定更恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guarantee our bathroom is still messier.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.14,0:13:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐  莉莉  电梯到哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God! Lily! Where is the elevator?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.14,0:13:08.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管了  我走楼梯去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where- I don't know! I'm taking the stairs!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.50,0:13:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  我们来救你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily, we're coming for you!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.14,0:13:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你这是要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you. Where you headed?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.11,0:13:20.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得先前在泳池  你说服我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, remember earlier in the pool when you convinced me...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.56,0:13:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手让海莉去和隔壁的陌生人去玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to let Haley go next door with complete strangers?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.82,0:13:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你当时完全同意的  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- And you were totally on board. - Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah, well,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.82,0:13:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她现在喝醉了  还在上面狂吐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she got drunk, and now she's upstairs throwing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.71,0:13:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她还是个孩子  谁给她的酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But she's just a kid. Who would serve her?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.76,0:13:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们  亲爱的  我们亲手奉上的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We did, honey. On a silver platter.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.34,0:13:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说服我要放轻松  随她去玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You convinced me to relax and let go,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.78,0:13:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看落下什么结果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and now this happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.13,0:13:37.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  别太为我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry, but we shouldn't feel bad...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.61,0:13:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因共享二人世界而付出的代价自责\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}About wanting a little time for ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.24,0:13:41.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  这不是在度蜜月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, this isn't a honeymoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.18,0:13:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经为人父母  你得放弃那个想法了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have kids. You have got to let this go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.00,0:13:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在起  我不会让他们离开我的视线一步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From now on, I am not losing sight of them for two seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.30,0:13:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都别想逃过我的法眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing gets past me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.26,0:13:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到杰了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you find Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.52,0:13:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点担心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm getting worried.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:53.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  我得去处理一下海莉的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry. I have to deal with Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.69,0:13:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  亲爱的  我去处理海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. You know what, sweetie? I will deal with Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.54,0:13:57.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你继续去找找老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You go see if you can find Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.30,0:13:58.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去外面找找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll look for him out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.81,0:14:03.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  你个小家伙是要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily, where are you going, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.77,0:14:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.78,0:14:11.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对不起  -我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm so sorry. - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.57,0:14:13.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想些什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. What were you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.38,0:14:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个孩子有身份证  她就买了些酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One of the kids had an I.D., and she bought some drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.24,0:14:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喝了一口  结果就止不住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I tried one, and then another one.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.02,0:14:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.65,0:14:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  的确很傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Yes, it was stupid,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.96,0:14:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你还算幸运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but you are really lucky
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.45,0:14:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有遭遇更可怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that this did not end as badly as it could have.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.28,0:14:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们从小教育你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is why we always say to you...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.01,0:14:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦喝醉  就会犯糊涂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when you drink, you make bad decisions.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.33,0:14:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道  只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know, I know. I just-
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.20,0:14:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前一分钟还在返校节派对上喝酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One minute you're having wine coolers at homecoming,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.98,0:14:40.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the next...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.68,0:14:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我克莱尔就火遍全校了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the game of Truth or Claire sweeps your high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.44,0:14:47.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你没骂我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks for not yelling at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.64,0:14:50.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  那样就太狠心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey. That would just be cruel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.10,0:14:52.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会等到你酒醒了再骂你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'II wait till you feel better to yell.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.08,0:14:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我永远不会好起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think I'll ever feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.68,0:15:00.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次喝酒都会这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does this happen every time you drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.10,0:15:03.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.54,0:15:05.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.38,0:15:09.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.12,0:15:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.45,0:15:17.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.14,0:15:20.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我起不来了  一躺下我腰就折了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm stuck. I laid down, my back went out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.04,0:15:23.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我会帮你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Well, don't you worry. We're gonna get you out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.62,0:15:26.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抓着我  -好的  菲尔  这样做也许不大好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Grab on. - Yeah, you know, Phil, this might not be the best-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.06,0:15:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.71,0:15:29.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要像飓风一样震撼到你[歌曲名]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just gonna rock you- like a hurricane.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.11,0:15:31.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑  你应该听不懂  来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm kidding. You're too old to get that. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.25,0:15:32.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  干嘛不去找工作人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. Why don't you just get someone who works here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.69,0:15:33.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, this is gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.84,0:15:36.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And now- Oh, wow!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.22,0:15:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抽筋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's spasming.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.53,0:15:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别动  -我不想...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't move. - No. I don't wanna get-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.54,0:15:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说一下  我很感谢你给我们这次度假的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By the way, I just want to thank you for this trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.45,0:15:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我一生中最美好的一次度假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really been a vacation of a lifetime.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.38,0:15:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此地绝无基情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nothing weird!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.77,0:15:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aloha.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.87,0:16:05.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把钱包放在前面口袋了  所以才...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I keep my wallet in my front pocket, so that's-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.08,0:16:07.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬地顶着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's what that is.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.24,0:16:15.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的脖子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Neck... going.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.49,0:16:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.12,0:16:27.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有人在吗  帮帮忙  -快叫警卫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Anyone! Anyone, help! - Alert security!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.36,0:16:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封锁这个岛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seal off the island!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.18,0:16:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This- This way! This way!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.33,0:16:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.41,0:16:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是在找人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aha. You looking for someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.61,0:16:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  我们担心死了  都怪我们说话说忘记了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily. We were so worried. We just got distracted.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.50,0:16:43.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们真是白痴  -别自责了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, we're idiots.  - Ay! Don't beat yourself up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.25,0:16:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去也老是把曼尼弄丢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I used to lose Manny all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.70,0:16:49.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我把你爸也给丢了  这种事很平常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now I lost your father. These things happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.29,0:16:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's right, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.45,0:16:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是不是说我爸失踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did she say my father's missing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.81,0:17:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们总说会抽时间  可总被生活琐事缠绕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We say we'll make time, but life gets in the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.67,0:17:04.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我们的确已经为人父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I know we're parents,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.06,0:17:05.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但难道不能同时做亲密爱人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but can't we be lovers too?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.78,0:17:07.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也许是我最糟糕的一次生日了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This may be my worst birthday ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you are!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.30,0:17:10.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hi, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.97,0:17:13.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被卡在吊床上  当时实在太搞笑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was stuck in a hammock. It was actually really funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.38,0:17:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我趴在他身"上"大概20分钟  -你好走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I was on top of him for, like, 20 minutes. - You need to go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.75,0:17:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good night. Honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.51,0:17:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的背疼发作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My back seized up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.67,0:17:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话  都是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, because you overdid it
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.99,0:17:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你接了那通电话后运动过量了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}after that phone call about your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.11,0:17:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信我已经和他当时一样老了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe I'm as old as he was.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.92,0:17:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  坐这缓缓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. Sit down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.41,0:17:35.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你会喜欢他的  我父亲  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You'd have liked him- my old man. - I'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.84,0:17:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也会很喜欢你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he'd have loved you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.21,0:17:41.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那老家伙可是魅力十足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My God, that guy- He was a charmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.16,0:17:42.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就是那种类型吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mmm, I know the type.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.86,0:17:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起度过了很多欢乐时光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we had a lot of fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.80,0:17:47.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我要告诉你点事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'll tell you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.03,0:17:51.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的家庭度假可一点都不像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our family vacations were nothing like this here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.58,0:17:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年在伊利湖畔租的农舍里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One week a year in a rented cottage on Lake Erie,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.67,0:17:56.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的蜘蛛都有这么大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}spiders this big.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.19,0:18:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒蛮希望他能看到我们过上好日子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just wish he could have seen how things turned out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.11,0:18:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你继续这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if you keep going like this,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.65,0:18:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你马上就能亲自告诉他了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe you can tell him yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.25,0:18:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我也行  因为你也会把我害死的  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or I can tell him, because you're about to kill me, Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.63,0:18:11.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得腿  胳膊和背  全身上下都在痛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My legs, my arms, my back- everything is sore.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.30,0:18:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你"折腾"得筋疲力尽是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So I wore you out, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.95,0:18:15.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  别得意忘形  老家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, no, no. Don't get cocky, old man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.06,0:18:17.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐下去至少还能再站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I sit down, I can still get up. Eh.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.22,0:18:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  过来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, uh- Okay, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.18,0:18:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come here. Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.04,0:18:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的假期过的很愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The rest of the trip went better.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:28.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉的头不再晕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley's room stopped spinning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.03,0:18:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  没错  -接着一个猴子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes, it is. - And a monkey-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.66,0:18:30.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看谁来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There she is!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.58,0:18:32.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你好阿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey! Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.53,0:18:34.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要来点松饼荷包蛋吗  太美味了  -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you want some eggs Benedict? So creamy! - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.80,0:18:36.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.84,0:18:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰如愿以偿地度过了他想要的轻松假期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay got back to the vacation he always wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.92,0:18:49.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇和小卡也出去观光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Mitch and Cam managed to do some sightseeing...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.28,0:18:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在香蕉园里游览了一番\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at a working banana plantation-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.11,0:18:53.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莉莉  -在那貌似他们又丢了莉莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Lily! - Where they promptly lost Lily again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.44,0:18:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛要把她打扮成和丛林一个颜色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why did you dress her in jungle prints?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.30,0:18:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我觉得那样可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I thought it would be cute!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.04,0:18:58.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会感觉她又回到了越南\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's gonna think she's back in Vietnam!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.77,0:19:01.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  莉莉  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily! Lily, honey!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.30,0:19:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和克莱尔  我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me and Claire, we-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.39,0:19:05.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们度过了一段美好时光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we had a great time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.21,0:19:07.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们仍没能度成蜜月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But we never did get that honeymoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.23,0:19:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我对这次的度假期望太高了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I just expected a little too much from this vacation.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.20,0:19:13.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这份心意在就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were so sweet to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.86,0:19:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想想真蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was dumb.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.20,0:19:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你说的那样  我们的激情消缺了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like you said, the thrill is gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.51,0:19:19.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我从来没这么说过  -不  的确没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I never said that. - No, it's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.57,0:19:24.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我们可以再把时间稍微调回点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But wait. Put a few seconds back on the clock.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.53,0:19:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们可是很积极的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The kid still has a few moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.42,0:19:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.08,0:19:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞明白为什么我们不能有个像样的蜜月了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figured out why we couldn't have a honeymoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.50,0:19:34.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们还没有举办过婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because we never had a wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.57,0:19:35.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.61,0:19:39.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是猜不透你到底是喜欢还是讨厌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I still can't tell if you think this is lame or cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.33,0:19:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我当然喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, it's incredibly cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.00,0:19:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看来我终于可以陪你走完红地毯了  -老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Looks like I finally get to walk you down the aisle. - Daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.03,0:19:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还得你带着我走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ow! You better walk me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.75,0:19:50.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我尽量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I'll do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.25,0:19:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天欢聚一堂  共同来重温\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're here today to celebrate the renewing of the marriage vows...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.57,0:19:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔和克莱尔喜结连理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of Phil and Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.13,0:20:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天  他们选择重申对彼此的爱意坚定不移\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}On this day they've chosen to reaffirm their love for each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.69,0:20:03.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在可以亲吻你的新娘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You may kiss your bride. Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.85,0:20:06.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我郑重宣布  他们依然是夫妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I present to you, still as husband and wife,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.29,0:20:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲夫妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mr. And Mrs. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.59,0:20:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你乘坐茂伊岛直飞洛杉矶的航班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Welcome to the nonstop flight from Maui to Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.02,0:20:45.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢你选择美国大陆航空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank for you choosing Continental Airlines.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.28,0:20:46.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.98,0:20:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, honey,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.94,0:20:50.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我有什么不测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if anything were ever to happen to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.40,0:20:52.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你能再婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I would want you to get remarried.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.00,0:20:53.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.74,0:20:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应得很快嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was a little fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.19,0:20:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱想  我只是想让你开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. I just want to make you happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.70,0:20:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.33,0:21:03.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你有未来再婚的人选吗  -应该是薇姬·康洛伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Any idea of who you would remarry? - Vicky Conroy probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.37,0:21:04.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和我一个办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She works in my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.52,0:21:06.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做事很有条例  孩子们都很喜欢她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's very organized. The kids love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.09,0:21:09.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们在说薇姬吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you guys talking about Vicky? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.25,0:21:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  她棒极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mom, she's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.76,0:21:16.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想让你知道  要是我有什么不测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just so you know, if something were to happen to me, I-
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.99,0:21:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会发生不测的  别乱说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Something's gonna happen to you, all right.

