[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.34,0:03:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.34,0:03:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.34,0:03:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第一季第十九集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.17,0:00:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天山姆·莱利踢足球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Today Sam Riley kicked a soccer ball...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.50,0:00:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狠狠砸中某小孩  他眼珠都爆出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it hit another kid so hard his eye popped out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.91,0:00:09.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.24,0:00:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  眼珠真爆出来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? His eye popped out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.28,0:00:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-算了  -钻被窝咯  明天周六大日子哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Never mind. - Well, gotta hit the sack. Big Saturday tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.09,0:00:16.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  某人过生日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's right. It's somebody's birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.44,0:00:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止生日  iPad要开卖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not just that. The iPad comes out-
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.60,0:00:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我生日这天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}on my actual birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.86,0:00:23.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是乔帮主和上帝勾肩搭背地说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like Steve Jobs and God got together to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.01,0:00:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们爱你哟  菲尔"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"We love you, Phil."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.97,0:00:25.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩意儿到底棒在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is so great about that doohickey anyhow?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.70,0:00:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"玩意儿"  艾丽·梅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Doohickey," Elly May?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.70,0:00:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[60年代电视剧角色  天使外表傻妞心]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.11,0:00:31.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电影院  图书馆  音乐商店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a movie theater, a library and a music store...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.23,0:00:34.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都集成在那神奇的小本里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}all rolled into one awesome pad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.48,0:00:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,图书馆知道吗  是个看书的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A library is a place where people get books.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.92,0:00:39.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电影院知道吗  是个约会的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A movie theater is a place where people go on dates.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.52,0:00:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把沙滩椅装到车里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I better load the beach chair into the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.88,0:00:42.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明早好坐着排队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna need it for the line in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.51,0:00:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, honey. Hang on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.49,0:00:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生日怎么能排一天队呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't spend your birthday in line.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.04,0:00:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会排一天啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, not the whole day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.30,0:00:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我6点去  不用你惦记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have to be there at 6:00, you'll forget about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.52,0:00:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-10点就买到啦  -我去排怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Then I'm out by 10:00. - Why don't you let me do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.82,0:00:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔  没必要吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire, you don't have to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.65,0:00:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是没必要  但我想替你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I know, but I want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.53,0:00:56.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  你生日这天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that way on your birthday
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.68,0:00:59.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一睁眼  面前就是新玩具啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you'll wake up and you'll have your brand-new toy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.52,0:01:02.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.55,0:01:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将之称作"玩具"是大不敬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, in spite of you calling it a toy,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.03,0:01:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但明天貌似会超过我曾过得最开心的一个生日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this is shaping up to top the best birthday I ever had.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.48,0:01:11.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝  再不用听那故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank God we don't have to hear that stupid story
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.11,0:01:12.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么地方来着  -在欢乐地带球场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- about that place... - It was called the Fun Zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.68,0:01:13.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那年我11岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was 11.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.67,0:01:16.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连续击中10个直线快球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hit 10 straight fastballs in the batting cage.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.82,0:01:18.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我的铁哥们杰夫·斯威尼冒出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then my best friend Jeff Sweeney stepped in
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.87,0:01:20.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我正中胯下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and took one in the groin.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.84,0:01:22.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喊道  又中两"球"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I yelled out "Ball two!"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.23,0:01:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人爆笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everybody laughed.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.25,0:01:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时我就知道  我很搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was when I knew I was funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.61,0:01:30.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.78,0:01:35.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B-E-L-I-E-V-E  相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}B-E-L-I-E-V-E. Believe.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.99,0:01:38.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中间不是E-I吗  你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you sure there's not an "E-I" In the middle?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.48,0:01:40.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不  是I-E  -好样滴  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- No. It's "I-E." - Good, papi!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.40,0:01:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绕不晕你  你老师也别想成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I can't fool you, then your teachers can't fool you either.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.79,0:01:45.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师没必要绕晕我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think they're trying to fool me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.31,0:01:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我给菲尔买了什么生日礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait until you see what I got Phil for his birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.32,0:01:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天维购物淘到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I found it on the SkyMall catalog.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:53.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啧啧  不是那种会说话的闹钟吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay. It's not one of those talking alarm clocks?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.33,0:01:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"6:05啦  6:25啦  醒醒啦醒醒啦"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"It's 6:05. It's 6:25. Wake up. Wake up."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.04,0:02:00.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比那个棒多了  一套紫檀木棋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Even better. A rosewood chess set.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.05,0:02:01.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  不如我等会再包装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As matter of fact, before I wrap this thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.53,0:02:02.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先来一局怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what say we take it for a spin?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.86,0:02:04.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧曼尼  我教你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Manny. I'll teach you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.12,0:02:05.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会下的啦  他老爸教过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He knows how to play. His father taught him.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.95,0:02:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要教他正经下法  不是哥伦比亚版的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna teach him real chess, not the Colombian version.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.95,0:02:10.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们这  棋子是用来下的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We actually use the pieces to play the game,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.64,0:02:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是用来藏毒走私的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not smuggle stuff out of the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.34,0:02:15.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你也少来玩我这哥伦比亚女子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know one Colombian piece you won't be playing with later.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.65,0:02:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼快来  试试你能耐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, come on. Let's see what you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.24,0:02:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会让你大吃一惊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'll be surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:21.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(193,210)}让他赢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.09,0:02:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼棋艺高超  杰的棋品可不咋滴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny's an excellent player, but Jay is a grumpy loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.88,0:02:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输了就生闷气  吊脸子  还摔门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He mopes, he makes the face, he slams the door,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.84,0:02:31.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摔完门还不承认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then he said he didn't slam the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.49,0:02:34.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他赢比较好啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's better that he wins.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.67,0:02:41.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, I got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.74,0:02:47.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:51.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  别哭啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's okay. It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.57,0:02:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  -别吵我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Cam! - Leave me alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.75,0:02:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  莉莉房里有个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a...there's a man in Lily's room.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.54,0:03:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉房里有个人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a man in Lily's room!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.84,0:03:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大棒走起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's go time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.04,0:03:14.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.98,0:03:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我是我  别打  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.73,0:03:18.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.92,0:03:20.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邻居的监控器和我们串线了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We must have just heard a neighbor with the same monitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.68,0:03:21.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  要是有蜘蛛闯入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boy, if a spider would have broken in here,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.39,0:03:26.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你捏个报纸也就能吓吓它而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he would have been in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.94,0:03:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灯光烧烤夹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Light-up barbecue tongs.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.73,0:03:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就给菲尔准备了这破礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This was the lame gift I got Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.37,0:03:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以5点起床排队  我郁闷吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, was I bummed to get up at 5:00 and wait in line?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.64,0:03:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不会  我总算能给老公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, because I was finally getting my husband
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.56,0:03:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买到梦寐以求的礼物了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}something that he really, really wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.87,0:03:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和他一样兴奋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was every bit as excited as he was.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.94,0:04:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.83,0:04:19.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.79,0:04:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天输给我  没生气吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hope you're not upset about our chess match yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.28,0:04:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一盘怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, what do you say we play again?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.14,0:04:25.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我挺好  -态度不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm good. - That's the spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.72,0:04:27.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你下载的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Downloaded this for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.94,0:04:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿童级国际象棋入门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's kind of a kid's guide to chess.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.31,0:04:32.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  杰  我好得很\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Jay. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.17,0:04:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下棋不无聊的  可以很有趣嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nah, it's not all dry like that. They have fun with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.91,0:04:37.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  可以用蜡笔给小人上色呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, you can color in the little players with your crayons.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.80,0:04:39.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真让我兴趣大增\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now you are making me want to play again.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.78,0:04:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有兴趣就对了  我们来打个赌吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now we're lighting a fire. Let me toss this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.60,0:04:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果终有一天  你下赢了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you beat me, if that day should ever come,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.44,0:04:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就给你...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll give you-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.56,0:04:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你那块表  -哟  早看上了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I want your watch. - Wow, you had that loaded up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:54.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成  来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Game on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.12,0:04:58.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  你先下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, I want you to go first.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.00,0:05:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住  努力清出中路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now remember, try to open up the middle of the board.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.29,0:05:04.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你该走两步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd have moved that guy two spaces.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.71,0:05:06.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更有攻击性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More aggressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.01,0:05:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皇后也别那么早出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you don't want to bring your queen out that quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.30,0:05:12.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  它应该守在原地的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, now you could've protected that with that,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.38,0:05:13.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它一动  就露了...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but now you're vulnerable-
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.45,0:05:16.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-将军  -哈?  什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Checkmate. - Huh? What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.15,0:05:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么将的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How'd you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.85,0:05:22.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定猜不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You will not believe what's going on
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.93,0:05:24.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克和黛比家出了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at Jake and Debbie's house.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.00,0:05:27.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -和我们串线那家  肯定就住附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Who? -The people on the monitor. They must live nearby.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.52,0:05:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他家太狗血了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So much drama.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.33,0:05:32.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克跟黛比说  他要加班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Jake told Debbie that he had to work late.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.66,0:05:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黛比打给他老板\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So she called his boss
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.01,0:05:36.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现没加班  抓包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and found out that he didn't. Busted!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.51,0:05:37.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就打了一早上电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So she spent all morning on the phone
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.71,0:05:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她妈妈哭啊哭啊哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}crying and crying and crying to her mother...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.89,0:05:42.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说如果杰克再"加班"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and said if Jake has to work "late" one more time,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.91,0:05:44.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就要离婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she's filing for divorce.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.96,0:05:48.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吗  我端上狗血大菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it? I give you that tasty dish
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.66,0:05:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就只"哈"一声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and all you give me is a "Huh"?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.20,0:05:52.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起小卡  昨晚我吓呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I'm s- Cam, I froze last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.39,0:05:53.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I froze.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.57,0:05:55.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为莉莉有危险  就吓呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought Lily was in danger and I froze.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.91,0:05:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你没有  你立刻行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But not you. No, you sprung right into action.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.32,0:06:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还拉风地说了句"走起"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You even had the cool "It's go time" line.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.60,0:06:03.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是本能啦  我做过一年交管员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That comes to me naturally. I spent a year as a crossing guard.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.57,0:06:05.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  我算是什么爸爸啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, I mean, what kind of parent am I
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.01,0:06:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连自己的家人都保护不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if I can't even protect my own family, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.34,0:06:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真想有那么一次无所畏惧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just once I would love to be the guy with no fear...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.56,0:06:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来  该  该出手时就出手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who can stand up and, I don't know, you know, kick some ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.15,0:06:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那小粉拳挥得真萌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're so cute when you're angry with your little fists.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.24,0:06:18.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想把你装进口袋里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just wanna put you in my pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.38,0:06:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸下楼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think he's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.18,0:06:24.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-来了吗  -来了来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's coming? - Here he comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.29,0:06:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  -生日快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad! - Happy birthday!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.59,0:06:29.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们  帅呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys! That's awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.13,0:06:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁送来的气球  -小卡和米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, who are these from? - Cam and Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.06,0:06:33.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,典型的基情温馨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Those guys are a class act.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.67,0:06:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给你做早餐呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're making you breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.52,0:06:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法式华夫饼哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}French waffle cakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.24,0:06:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜猜  两片法式吐司夹华夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me guess: One waffle in between two pieces of French toast
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.85,0:06:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面裹着煎饼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}wrapped in a pancake.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.47,0:06:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nailed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.36,0:06:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来吧孩儿们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bring it in here, monkeys.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.74,0:06:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸爱你们  快过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Love you! Get over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.59,0:06:50.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.59,0:06:51.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.93,0:06:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说史上最棒的女人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean the greatest woman in the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.04,0:06:56.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在苹果店门外排队呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She is standing in line at the Apple Store,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.13,0:06:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要实现我所有的生日愿望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}making all my birthday wishes come true.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.51,0:07:00.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看味道怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's see how these bad boys taste.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.38,0:07:02.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别碰  -老天  烫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, no... - Son of a... Oh! It's hot!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.66,0:07:05.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事吧  -刚出炉是吧  真是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you okay? - Fresh out of the oven? That is...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.82,0:07:07.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要冰块吗  -要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you want some ice? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.83,0:07:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  真是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, man! This...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.14,0:07:12.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-舒服多了  舒服舒服  -对不起  老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, that feels better. That feels better. - Sorry, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.44,0:07:14.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  太诡异了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it actually- That feels weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.54,0:07:15.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换了种疼法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That burns in a different way!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.71,0:07:20.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤盘别洗啊  我皮还黏在上面呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't wash this until we see if I can get my skin back. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.65,0:07:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me see it!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.24,0:07:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  派对要晚上才开始呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Your party's not until tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.92,0:07:29.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're just gonna have to wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.91,0:07:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看包装袋嘛  留在车里了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just let me see the bag. Did you leave it in the car?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.75,0:07:33.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对啊  -谁招待你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah! - Hey, who'd you deal with?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.39,0:07:35.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是叫莫哈吗  他们管他叫"兽男"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was it a guy named Mehar? They call him "The beast."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.28,0:07:37.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矮个子  他肯定忙着疯狂搬货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's a tiny guy. He must've move a ton of product.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.39,0:07:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊胃口哈  我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I kinda love that you're making me wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.36,0:07:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是史上最棒老婆啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are the best wife ever!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.03,0:07:45.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史上最棒  绝对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are the best wife ever!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.14,0:07:46.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没买到iPad\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't get you the iPad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.60,0:07:48.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到的时候已经卖光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got to the store and they were all out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.97,0:07:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.34,0:07:52.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂  我网友都买到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't understand. My online buddies got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.85,0:07:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高考落榜君和机器兄8点才到店里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}SAT800 and Brobot didn't get there until 8:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.18,0:07:56.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定比他们早\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you definitely got there before they did,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.47,0:07:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是六点半就去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because you got there at 6:30.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.61,0:08:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  你没早去吗  你上哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no! You didn't get there at 6:30? Where were you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.62,0:08:02.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我闹钟定了五点的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I set the alarm for 5:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.85,0:08:04.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起床下楼  结果又睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got up, I came downstairs, I fell asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.62,0:08:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊  老天爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Oh, my goodness.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.20,0:08:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了什么  我做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What have I done? What have I done?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.12,0:08:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我该自己去的  -亲爱的  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I should've done this myself. - Sweetie, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.79,0:08:12.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周会补货的呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're gonna get more in next week.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.53,0:08:13.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Next week?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.58,0:08:16.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让抢鲜族等下周  你太残忍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the worst thing you can say to an early adopter.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.22,0:08:18.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上哪去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.40,0:08:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找个重视别人生日的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To a place where birthdays still mean something.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.83,0:08:30.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去开门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll get that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.03,0:08:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-曼尼  -米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hi, Manny. - Mitchell?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.65,0:08:35.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有何贵干呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing here at...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.77,0:08:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在时间  周六下午4点17分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}4:17 on a Saturday afternoon?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.03,0:08:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来还老爸的工具包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I'm just returning my dad's belt of tools, so-
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.08,0:08:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周六下午4点17分吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}At 4:17 on a Saturday afternoon?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.46,0:08:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没别的事可干了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you have something better to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.07,0:08:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-装扮成功吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So, were you a big hit? - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.14,0:08:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你借这玩意多半是参加化妆派对嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just assumed there was some kind of costume party.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.49,0:08:53.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡扮印度阿三是不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was Cam the Indian?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.86,0:08:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  跟你说  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. For your information, Dad,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.46,0:08:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们确实是在家建了东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we were actually doing a little construction at the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.67,0:08:58.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What'd you build?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.80,0:09:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼品包装小站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A gift-wrapping station.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.63,0:09:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真够基情的哈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we're back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.69,0:09:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢了  -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- So, thank you for that. - You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.98,0:09:08.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你记不记得我11岁时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, uh, Dad, do you remember when I was, probably 11...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.98,0:09:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你教我拳击  我半途而废来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you were teaching me how to fight, and then I quit?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.28,0:09:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你说你要学的招数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, when you said everything you needed to learn
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.77,0:09:14.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《西区故事》那种歌舞片里都有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you'd learn from West Side Story.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.64,0:09:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  -花拳绣腿好用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah. - How'd that work out for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.29,0:09:18.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪天斗了舞  一定告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I'm ever in a dance fight, I'll let you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  你还想教我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, yeah- Is the offer, uh, still good?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.34,0:09:25.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  你和小卡闹矛盾啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? What's the matter? You got problems with Cam?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.47,0:09:27.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会呢  你咋猜那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No! Why would you say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.87,0:09:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  和男人同居哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, come on. I mean, you know, sharing a room with a guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.26,0:09:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟我弟弟睡过上下铺  天天暴力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bunked with my brother. I know that can get pretty rough.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.77,0:09:35.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和小卡可不睡上下铺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't "bunk" with Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.45,0:09:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  我就是想学点自卫术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, I just wanna learn a little self-defense, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.04,0:09:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得哪招  耍来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Show me what you remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.12,0:09:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现  现在吗  -来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Right now? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.04,0:09:46.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  老天  拇指外扣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, uh- Gosh, uh- Thumbs out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.27,0:09:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  乖仔  -然后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thumbs. Attaboy. - And then-
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:56.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不咋漂亮  是不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That wasn't- That wasn't very pretty, was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.19,0:09:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  恐怕是太"漂亮"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what? Maybe it was a little too pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.64,0:09:59.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.01,0:10:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起飞了哈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here it goes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.38,0:10:03.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Oh, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.05,0:10:05.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.42,0:10:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你起跳点太低了  才没飞起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think the problem is, you're not jumping from high enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.22,0:10:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去车库顶试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You should get on top of the garage.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.60,0:10:12.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  别害你小弟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex, stop trying to kill your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.24,0:10:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  妈妈要求助你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, guys, I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.42,0:10:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得给老爸找个iPad来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We've gotta find your dad one of those iPad thingies.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.64,0:10:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  给你朋友群发短信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Haley, text everyone you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.80,0:10:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯  Facebook  推特什么的都发一圈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex? Facebook, chat, tweet, buzz, bling,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.63,0:10:22.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂那些玩意  你要通过一切渠道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know! Just do what you have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.11,0:10:24.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万找个iPad来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have got to find one of these iPads. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.32,0:10:26.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克小可爱  别挡路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke? Sweetie, that means stay out of everyone's way
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.61,0:10:28.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也别吸氢气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and stop inhaling the balloons.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.89,0:10:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪有吸氢气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not inhaling them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.23,0:10:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少撒谎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.96,0:10:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did she know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈有没教你  别坐陌生人的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Didn't your mama teach you never to take a ride from a stranger?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.01,0:10:43.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放假了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got a little vacation time coming up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.17,0:10:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上月球好好玩吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Have fun on the moon!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.82,0:10:47.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近身体不爽是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not feeling too well lately?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.76,0:10:50.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来看看医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe you should come see the doctor...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.04,0:10:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥帮你解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'll get rid of it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.64,0:10:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞎嚷嚷啥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.41,0:11:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请注意  参加菲尔生日派对的朋友们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Attention. If you're here for Phil's birthday party,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.22,0:11:03.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请到野餐区集合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they're gathering in the picnic area.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.45,0:11:05.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔的生日派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil's birthday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.42,0:11:07.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老婆知道我会来这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My wife knew I'd be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.14,0:11:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我准备了派对哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She put together a whole party for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.06,0:11:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这能弥补iPad的事儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Does that really make up for not getting an iPad?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.60,0:11:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你交心了  你可别挑拨我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't make me sorry I shared that with you. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.76,0:11:15.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜啦各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.64,0:11:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侬好呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Howdy-do!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.31,0:11:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,广播说菲尔的生日派对在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I just heard the announcement for Phil's birthday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.45,0:11:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对的  拐弯就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. It's right around the corner.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.40,0:11:28.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -好好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Awesome. - Have fun!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.61,0:11:30.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Thanks, my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.49,0:11:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰激凌蛋糕吗  真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ice-cream cake? Ice-cream cake's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.78,0:11:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  生日快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy birthday, Phil!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.82,0:11:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太帅了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.36,0:11:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-生日快乐  -生日快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.58,0:11:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy birthday, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.12,0:11:54.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-生日快乐  -玩得开心呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy birthday. - Have a really good birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.79,0:11:57.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看到蛋糕了吗  -超棒的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Did you see the cake? - Oh, yeah. It's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.03,0:12:01.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.77,0:12:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我哄小孩睡觉呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, that's fine, I'm just putting the baby down.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.81,0:12:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是杰克  出轨的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's Jake. He's the one that's having an affair.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.97,0:12:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道的  -明晚没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I know. - Yeah, I can do it tomorrow night.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.32,0:12:11.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我老婆编个谎就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll just give my wife some excuse.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.53,0:12:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋汉子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Men are pigs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.80,0:12:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那也没办法  -有呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I don't really have a choice, do I? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.62,0:12:17.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别劈腿不行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You could not cheat on her! How about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.72,0:12:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得给她个惊喜嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it has to be a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.67,0:12:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我跟她外婆说起意大利语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When she hears me speaking Italian to her grandmother,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.94,0:12:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷偷摸摸这么长时间也值了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it'll be worth all this sneaking around.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.17,0:12:26.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  我猜错了  他是个好男人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lily, I had it backwards. He's wonderful.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.33,0:12:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我就说要加班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry. I'll just tell her I'm working late.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.22,0:12:29.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行杰克  别那么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Jake, don't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.39,0:12:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说加班你就惨了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the worst thing you could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.96,0:12:31.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安啦[意大利语]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Buonanotte.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.15,0:12:33.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏了莉莉  我们要怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, Lily, what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.22,0:12:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得帮帮他们啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have to fix this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.54,0:12:38.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我就教你几招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Mitchell, I'm gonna teach you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.99,0:12:41.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本的巴西柔术吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a couple of basic Brazilian jiu-jitsu moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.23,0:12:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  来打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, just attack me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.06,0:12:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry- What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.07,0:12:48.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,释放你内心的怨恨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take any deep-seated anger you may have,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.30,0:12:49.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲过来打我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}get a running start and come at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.71,0:12:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  我没记恨过你啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, I don't have any deep-seated anger.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.17,0:12:52.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得那次万圣节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Remember that Halloween when
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不让你扮奥利维亚·纽顿-约翰吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wouldn't let you go as Olivia Newton-John?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.11,0:12:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了吧  借力打力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You see what I did? I used your momentum against you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.81,0:13:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷西柔术创始人教我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I learned this choke from the Gracie brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.65,0:13:02.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这招叫"伏狮锁"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's called the lion killer- mata lella.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.10,0:13:06.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-懂  -试试挣脱  挣一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Okay. - Now try to get out. Try to get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.52,0:13:07.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-难不  -挣不开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- See? - I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.90,0:13:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挣不开就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, all right. Now-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.50,0:13:10.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要晕了  -这招就厉害在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Passing out... - See, the beauty of this is,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.88,0:13:12.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用贸然攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you don't have to make the first move.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.76,0:13:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对手可能会轻敌嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, chances are your opponent's gonna be overconfident.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.47,0:13:16.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为你是个菜鸟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna think you don't know anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.96,0:13:19.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而被骗  就显得很二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Basically, he's being suckered into thinking-
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.89,0:13:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  曼尼这小子耍我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny. Manny, that little bastard, he hustled me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.00,0:13:26.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.09,0:13:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, crap. Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.51,0:13:34.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得  吸气  加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, crap. All right. Come on. Breathe.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.36,0:13:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好小子  快醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Attaboy. You all right? Coming around.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.34,0:13:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我怎么趴地上了  -醒过来  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Why am I on the floor?-  Come on, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.31,0:13:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  我又没买着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, I just struck out again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.84,0:13:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托给点好消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Please tell me you have some good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.66,0:13:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格氏又进了一批货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, so The Grove just got a new shipment.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.13,0:13:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我短信你地址\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm texting you the directions now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.33,0:13:52.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好  真棒真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! Okay, that's good. That's good. That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.48,0:13:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就去  立刻滚去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm there. I'm on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.97,0:14:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小子把我手表骗走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That kid stole my watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.32,0:14:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-啥  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Huh? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.62,0:14:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他骗我跟他下棋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He hustled me at chess.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.17,0:14:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是保证让他赢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you promised you were gonna let him win.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.07,0:14:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我让他赢了一盘  -等等  你也知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I did the first time. - Wait a minute. You're in on it too?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.26,0:14:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  换派对衣服去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, go and get dressed for the party.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.82,0:14:13.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能洗个澡吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do I have time for a steam?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.48,0:14:14.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行  但要快  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, but a quick one. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.32,0:14:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛叫他输给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why tell him to lose to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.77,0:14:18.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一输棋就发小孩脾气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you're like a baby when you don't win.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.91,0:14:20.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乱踢东西  皱眉头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}With the kicking and the eyebrows...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.75,0:14:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还狂吃瓜子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the angry eating of the sunflower seeds.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.03,0:14:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, that's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.23,0:14:29.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输给小天才  我怎么会不服气呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't mind losing to a chess genius, which Manny obviously is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.10,0:14:31.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他天才  他还没我下得好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Chess genius? He's not even as good as I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.34,0:14:32.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你下棋不怎么样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not that good in chess.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.39,0:14:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-蜜月那次输给我了啊  -我让你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I beat you on our honeymoon. - Or did I let you win?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.05,0:14:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才没让我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You didn't let me win.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.58,0:14:41.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干嘛要把皇后送入你的魔爪  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would I sacrifice my queen for your pawn, Jay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.66,0:14:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop saying that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.05,0:14:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  宝贝  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, honey, hi. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.88,0:14:59.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸的蛋糕送来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They guy came with Dad's cake,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.82,0:15:01.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可它缺了一块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but just so you know, it's missing a piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.77,0:15:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你偷吃老爸蛋糕了吗  -没啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Luke, did you take a bite out of your father's cake? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.65,0:15:07.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别撒谎  卢克  -我哪有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Stop lying, Luke. - I'm not lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.66,0:15:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦对  我用你的卡付了钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}By the way, I used your credit card to pay him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.82,0:15:10.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.84,0:15:12.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, that's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.39,0:15:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把钱包留给你们就是为这个的嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whatever. That's why I left the wallet there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.41,0:15:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.83,0:15:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.83,0:15:23.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把钱包留家里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I left the wallet there! I left the wa-
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.70,0:15:24.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可怜的老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your poor father.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.59,0:15:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们乱成一团\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All this running around,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.39,0:15:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定以为没人在乎他生日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he's gonna think nobody cares about him on his birthday.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.35,0:15:29.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来点蛋糕吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More cake?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.05,0:15:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  小菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why not, Little Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.97,0:15:33.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我也没地儿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got no place else to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.60,0:15:47.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  先生  打扰你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sir! Sir! Sir, hi. Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.38,0:15:50.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点唐突\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, yes. I know this is highly unusual,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.03,0:15:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要你帮忙  挽救一段婚姻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I need your help to save a marriage.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.85,0:15:54.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近有对夫妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There is a couple in this neighborhood...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.51,0:15:57.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为一个小误会  快要离婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that is about to get a divorce for a simple misunderstanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.20,0:15:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们叫杰克和黛比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Their name is Jake and Debbie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.93,0:16:00.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道您宣过誓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I know you've taken an oath...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.81,0:16:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能泄露他人住址\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to not tell people where other people live,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.81,0:16:03.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也尊重您\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I respect that,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.69,0:16:05.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们能不能想办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but maybe we could work out some sort of
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.15,0:16:06.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设计一套暗号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}super secretive spy signal,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.90,0:16:08.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如你挠左耳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where if you scratch your left ear,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.65,0:16:09.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗示我他们住在左手边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know, maybe they live on the left,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.87,0:16:11.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果挠右耳  就是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and if you scratch your right ear, they live on-
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.34,0:16:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就住这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They live right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.60,0:16:18.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会说出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This conversation never happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.45,0:16:23.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抱歉晚了  -感谢上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sorry. - Oh, thank God!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.76,0:16:25.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.05,0:16:27.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸把我整晕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad just put me to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.38,0:16:29.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他给你讲催眠的打猎故事了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The hunting story.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.35,0:16:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hmm. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.56,0:16:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你可不能插队  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my gosh, no. You can't cut the line. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.54,0:16:35.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我本来就排这  -哪有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I was here. - Uh-uh.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.06,0:16:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我排了一个半小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I've been here for an hour and a half
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.20,0:16:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没看见你  你这是插队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you haven't been, so you cut the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.31,0:16:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你管我  -这位先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Whatever. - Whoa. Excuse me, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.36,0:16:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好像没弄清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think you understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.23,0:16:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以插队的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're not getting in front of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.35,0:16:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定点啦  红毛小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Calm down, gingerbread.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.33,0:16:49.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你走还是不走  -不走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Are you gonna move or not? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.40,0:16:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.98,0:16:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then you leave me no choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.45,0:16:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.30,0:16:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晕吧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.87,0:16:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  快晕过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.93,0:17:00.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没晕啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.98,0:17:03.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔你干什么  放开他  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell, what are you doing? Get off of him. - Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.37,0:17:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他就要晕了  -才没有呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's about to go to sleep. - No, I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.55,0:17:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要打架  三位请出列\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, folks. Break this up. You three- out of line.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.60,0:17:09.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉先生  我和他们无关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no. I'm sorry, sir. I didn't have anything to do with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.94,0:17:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是排队买iPad而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just waiting in line to get an iPad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.82,0:17:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不认识他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't even know this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.57,0:17:14.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  我得用你的信用卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. I need your credit card.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.92,0:17:17.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是他挑事  -闭嘴  你怎么还不晕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- He's the problem. - Shut up! You're supposed to be asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.05,0:17:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事我拿到了  -放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- It's okay. I have it. - Get off!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.41,0:17:19.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我拿到了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I've got it. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.58,0:17:21.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的卡  我没犯事  没犯事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've got your card. I'm good. No, I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.83,0:17:23.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我排在这呢  这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm good. I'm here. I'm here!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.98,0:17:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要给我老公买iPad啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've gotta get my husband an iPad!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.55,0:17:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐的秘诀就是  别期待太多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Key to a good birthday? Low expectations.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.22,0:17:32.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为能有iPad  期待错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thought I was getting an iPad. I was wrong about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.30,0:17:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为球场有惊喜派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thought I was getting a surprise party at the batting cages.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.00,0:17:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  大菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, Big Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.90,0:17:40.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  说到底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guess when it comes right down to it,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.19,0:17:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就跟被踢中蛋蛋的杰夫·斯威尼一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we're all just Jeff Sweeney taking a fastball to the plums.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.33,0:17:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  蛋糕掉地下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, um, Dad, your cake fell off the counter,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.05,0:17:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小卡舅夫正补救呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but Uncle Cam's trying to fix it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.91,0:17:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只会偷吃掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.10,0:17:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,披萨一直都没送来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the pizzas never showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.85,0:17:57.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没来就没来呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And they won't!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.61,0:17:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基情小气球啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, balloons.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.76,0:18:01.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得  反正没法知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine. I guess we'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.30,0:18:02.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么现在见分晓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or we can find out right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.46,0:18:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  棋盘给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, Manny, give me the chess set.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.11,0:18:07.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-送我棋盘啊  -待会再给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, it's a chess set. - Yeah. You'll get it later.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.03,0:18:08.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得决一死战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We got something to settle now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.27,0:18:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-往里走  - 生日快乐  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Go in there. - Happy birthday, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.36,0:18:11.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定快乐哟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Happy happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.76,0:18:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好香  克莱尔烤了干酪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that Claire's baked brie I smell?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.26,0:18:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.43,0:18:20.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡小卡  你不会相信的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Cam, Cam, you'll never believe what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.20,0:18:22.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-生日快乐  菲尔  -当然啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Happy birthday, Phil! - Sure!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.69,0:18:23.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝不会相信的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You'll never believe what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.62,0:18:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和人打架了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got in trouble for fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.34,0:18:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还挽救了一段婚姻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we saved a marriage.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.77,0:18:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-今天真是史上最棒  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well, this is the best day ever. - It really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.16,0:18:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ain't it though?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.33,0:18:36.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  看我这招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look at this, papi, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.02,0:18:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.24,0:18:41.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别唱《冠军之歌》[皇后乐队名曲]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can't sing "We Are the Champions"...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.00,0:18:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的皇后都没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without your queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.96,0:18:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  要是我输了  我就烧掉这房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it! Listen, I lose and I burn this house down!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.85,0:18:51.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看这儿  -亲爱的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ah, but look at this... - Honey, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.89,0:18:53.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们闹什么呢  太滑稽了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are we doing? This is ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.70,0:18:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们总有个要赢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One of us is gonna win the game,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.99,0:18:58.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个就不爽  只会两败俱伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the other's gonna feel lousy, and we both lose.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.05,0:19:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成啊  把我的礼物扔地上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, just leave my birthday present on the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.73,0:19:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好老婆  她已经赢定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's my girl. She had me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.55,0:19:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没戏了  我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There was no way I could win. I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.29,0:19:11.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好她不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just glad she didn't know it yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.25,0:19:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需两步  就能杀他个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two moves, and then-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.50,0:19:15.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是个下棋高手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm a very good chess player.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.63,0:19:17.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我更是个好老婆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm a better wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.74,0:19:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-买到了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, did you get it? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.88,0:19:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸爸怎么样  -古怪  更古怪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How's your dad? - Acting weird... er.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.16,0:19:27.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老婆  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, wife. - Honey, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.37,0:19:29.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是这样  -妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Um, listen... - Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.53,0:19:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  等会再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, Luke, hang on one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.86,0:19:33.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆  没关系啦  我已经没感觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, it's okay. I don't feel things anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.57,0:19:35.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可我想让你...  -妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But, sweetie, I want you to feel... - Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.21,0:19:38.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克我一会就来  你上哪去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, I'll be with you in just a second. Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.27,0:19:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去院子里拿铲子  清理我的蛋糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just heading out to the yard to get a shovel for my cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.77,0:19:43.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老妈  -卢克你要干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mom. - Luke, what do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.04,0:19:44.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上了老爸的电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I went on Dad's computer,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.74,0:19:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联系了他的宅男网友们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}contacted some of his geek friends,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.05,0:19:48.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说老爸快死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}told them that he was dying
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.84,0:19:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个iPad才能瞑目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and his last wish was an iPad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.11,0:19:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  我怎么教你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, what have I told you about-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.73,0:19:55.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个人很同情  就送来台多余的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One of them felt so bad, they brought over an extra.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.85,0:20:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  你拿到了  你这个乖仔撒谎精\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. You got it. You beautiful little liar!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.80,0:20:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here comes Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.02,0:20:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想吃蛋糕呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who wants some cake?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.16,0:20:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前想  可我不想吃...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I used to, but I don't desire food any-
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.85,0:20:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你买到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my God. You got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.78,0:20:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了半天不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All this time I said I didn't care,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.26,0:20:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我真想要  超想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I do care. I care so much!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.14,0:20:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-想吹蜡烛吗  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Do you want to blow out the candles? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.14,0:20:24.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹吧  使劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go on. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.84,0:20:26.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然真能吹灭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It did not just do that!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.86,0:20:28.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是真的  -老婆我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yes, it did! - Honey!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.43,0:20:33.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧这刚出炉热乎乎的iPad啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, who's ready for the first day of the rest of their lives?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.29,0:20:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-菲尔  生日快乐  -看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Phil, happy birthday! - Look at this!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.60,0:20:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我能摸摸吗  -摸  别掐  摸摸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Can I touch it? - Yeah, not so hard, but touch it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.21,0:20:41.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸它  别摸  摸  别摸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Touch it, but don't touch it. Touch it, but don't touch it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.20,0:20:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不该怀疑你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm so sorry I ever doubted you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.46,0:20:48.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.89,0:20:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝送来了那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank God that guy came over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.42,0:20:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did he say his name was?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.76,0:20:53.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没说  肯定是位天使\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He didn't. Must be an angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.20,0:20:55.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗  说我是天使呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did you hear that? I'm an angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.42,0:20:58.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-或者是个变态  -对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Or some creepy perv. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.36,0:21:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么知道的  恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How did he know? Eww.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.43,0:21:05.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我该报警吗  -没错  报警吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Maybe I should call the police. - You should call the police.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.04,0:21:08.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这就报  -他们从此幸福地生活在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I'm gonna call the police. - And they lived happily ever after.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.59,0:21:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别啊小卡  你上哪去  才刚开始精彩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, Cam. Where are you going? It was just getting good.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.60,0:21:13.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想听  多好的节目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want- That's my program.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.67,0:21:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.69,0:21:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也爱你  亲爱的  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I love you too, honey. - Oh. Okay.

